so you know who these two guys are the
LeBron and then the professor so if you
had to rate these two guys what would
you rate the guy on the right then I'm
gonna give him I'm gonna give him a
seven gone to love I'm gonna give him a
three dang okay three you're not you're
not a believer in all that YouTube stuff
nah nah it's all staged and stuff so if
you had to pick one of these guys to
beat won't be one who would you pick oh
for sure this boy over here the
professor what would you say is a
weakness in this game man he's trash
he's just trash and my endurance he
won't be able to keep up with me bro I
won't be able to keep over to you all
right man what's the knock on this game
you think just from seeing it online
nice handles trash
I gotta work on my handle for sure okay
yeah I mean then I got to hide on him
he's a little little man
[Music]
[Applause]