woof
a big tornado
here
[Applause]
Mr Pelican a tornado is coming please
stop selling balloons and go home
watch a tornado
you need to go home too little yak
everyone attention
everyone
attention everyone
[Music]
daddy we need to go to the basement a
tornado is coming
it's okay it's okay okay our house is
very strong
don't worry relax
[Music]
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador
hello hello
Papio find out who called just now leave
it to me okay
so call us from Mr yak's House this is
the location this is strange why does it
keep moving
it's moving so fast and in circles it
can't be they're caught up in the
tornado let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
ice cream cone is chasing us
oh
that's not an ice cream cone it's a
tumbleweek tornado
oh
oh no it's a giant tornado
everyone get out of the car and go to
low-lying places
it's coming
Watch Out Mr Raccoon don't stand next to
the telephone pole what what
what Joe
get down
we're Sheriff Labrador
Sheriff Labrador
oh where is he Adobe under your feet
[Music]
a pot lid and a toilet these are things
in a house
huh
oh no the racks are in the tornado they
may get thrown out at any time goby
papilum let's go save them okay
oh no the car can't be used now what do
we do
[Music]
I have an idea
clap you use this as a tire got it goby
help me carry the mattress to the car
and use it to save the ax
[Music]
let's go
hey Daddy what if we fall down
we're warmed Daddy has strong arms
Hallelujah
oh they're falling down hold on tight
[Music]
[Applause]
oh thank goodness we're safe
[Music]
Sheriff labrador's safety talk
kids if you run into a tornado you need
to evacuate to a safe place immediately
such as a basement or inside a sturdy
house
if you are in a car stop the car and get
out right away and find a low-lying
place to take cover also remember to
stay away from trees telephone poles and
billboards because they might hurt you
please keep these in mind
underground strange sound
it's a big monster
are you there sweetie
[Music]
playing around with the toilet again no
I'm not
um
let's go it's time for bed
[Music]
Oh
Daddy Daddy what's the sound
oh
who is it at this time of the night
[Music]
most
what's going on oh there there's a ghost
in the building
there's no ghost in the world kill me
[Music]
let's go have a look
[Applause]
[Music]
who's pretending to be a ghost
[Applause]
[Music]
they're buffaloes it is not funny at all
sorry we didn't mean it we heard a
strange sound it was so scary
[Music]
thank you
let's go
here's the buffalo's house let's get
inside
foreign
[Music]
over there
look it's coming from here and here
[Music]
is the sound grooving I found it
smell
huh
[Music]
sounds like it's coming from the pipes
Papillon we need your backup
got it
[Music]
Sheriff Labrador
how can I help you there's something in
the pipes I need you to search there got
it
sir
they're pretty and hard work it will be
a great help
[Music]
there were so many things stuck in the
pipes
look something's moving
follow it no problem
[Music]
come on
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go downstairs
foreign
[Music]
it's my fish how did it get here I'm
sorry I dropped it in the toilet while
playing in the bathroom
[Music]
Sheriff Labradors safety talk
kids the toilet is not a toy toilets are
connected to sewer pipes and there are a
lot of dirty things in the pipes
so don't play with water in the toilet
and don't throw things into it
it'll clog the toilet and cause a big
problem
breath fake child
oh
it looks so yummy
are you okay watch where you're going
police they don't know they don't know
no no little frog
he's been looking for you why are you
here by yourself thank you police
officer bye
they're acting weird isn't it strange
there might be something going on let's
follow them watch out
they're gone oh no where did they go
let's go that way
hey we almost got caught by the police
stop nagging we need to find the child
to kidnap today
two donuts please oh sorry they were
just sold out
oh Mommy Mommy I want a donut
my chance
watch me it smells yummy
[Music]
oh where's my donut
I got it now it's time
Mommy I want a donut wow it's so yummy
sweetie give one to little rabbit here
you are oh wow thanks
[Music]
thank you so much little foxy you're so
sweet
oh my God
oh you have such big ears
[Music]
and you're wearing such big shoes
oh no she's suspecting us
[Laughter]
sweetie why don't you admit a rabbit go
play with this car
little rabbit let's play together
where's the button ah there it is
be careful don't go too far I'll miss
rabbit your dress is really beautiful
thanks your shoes are beautiful too
let's go shopping later on oh where are
they a little rabbit a little box
where are you
see you
[Music]
Miss Rabbit what's going on Sheriff
Labrador my child is missing please help
me find her
where did you last see her in front of
the donut shop she went with little fox
to play with a toy car and I was
chatting with Miss Fox oh where's Miss
Fox oh miss Fox is missing too could it
be the weird Fox mom and son we met oh
no I think they kidnapped little rabbit
[Music]
the tire marks of the toy car
let's go
on the fox where are we now I want to go
back
nobody's here you can't go back
I'm not little fox I missed your Fox
you disguised as a boy
guess what I was in Disguise too
leave her alone oh no it's the police
don't worry you're safe now
sweetie
stop right there hey hey
hurry
watch out
see you later
foreign
you can't get away throw them off the
track turn right
you'd better stop huh they're gonna
catch us
this way no that way
watch me
[Music]
nobody can run away from me
don't worry
tariff Labrador safety talk
[Music]
kids you should beware of strangers
even if it's a kid you should always be
careful of who you meet
never take anything they give you and
never go with them because they could be
with other kidnappers
please remember that what
[Music]
falling disasters
hey
[Music]
I'm Sheriff Labrador
what throwing things don't worry we'll
be right there
[Music]
trash is everywhere where is she huh
wow
help me
Miss Hedgehog
Sheriff Labrador someone's been throwing
things down from above lately
oh please find out who did it don't
worry
there's no case that I can't solve
d
[Music]
um
let's go
[Music]
so you were watering the plants
Mr elephant it's very dangerous to put
flower pots on the balcony rail they
might fall down oh I'm sorry I'll take
them down right now
over there let's go
[Music]
stop stop what you're doing good
oh
[Music]
wow I'm so sorry ah you were just
playing with a yo-yo
[Music]
where is the suspect
you better run away if I catch you
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
it's disgusting
this is so much fun
over there let's go
huh nobody's here look at these
these are footprints
hmm
[Music]
this is strange the footprints stopped
right here
hmm
where's the suspect hiding
uh oh police officer you'll never catch
me yeah
[Music]
huh
there you are no no they found me
[Music]
stop right there
so you're the one who did it
that'll help too
[Music]
that's it for today guys
he's so sneaky
don't worry he can't run away
[Music]
why is it so slippery
nobody can run away from me I'm so sorry
[Music]
Sheriff labrador's safety talk
kids throwing things down from above is
very dangerous
that's because even a little rock can
seriously hurt someone when it falls
from a high place
remember never throw things down from a
high place
little Rhino was taken by an alien
[Music]
my kite is going to be so cool
it is
[Music]
[Applause]
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador
he always taken by an alien
what an alien
look over there
can't be an alien something's not right
let's follow it
no one can run away from me not even an
alien
balloons
alien it's an alien it's an aliens
laughs
[Applause]
[Music]
it's over there let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
let's go with little Rhino right now
oh it's gone oh man it got away
a kite spool
could it be a kite
not an alien
[Music]
that's why it was flying with the Wind
[Applause]
oh my goodness that must be it we need
to catch the kite and save little Rhino
this is
we need your support copy that
shooting let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
find the direction of the wind let's go
no problem leave it to me
oh
[Music]
my God
it really is a kite
healthy please
hang in there little Rhino we're coming
to get you
what's up
oh
my God
[Music]
[Applause]
we're all fine
[Music]
three
Sheriff Labrador safety talk
[Music]
kids kites are very strong when they're
flying which is why you should only fly
them with your parents never do it alone
also always be careful when you're
flying kites and not to get tangled by
the string or trip over it lastly the
string of a kite is very thin so make
sure to wear gloves to protect your
hands please remember that what
monster on the street
daddy hurry let's show at the Rainbow
Theater will start soon okay but always
save me first
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff Labrador I
saw a monster on the road it was so
scary a monster we'll be right there
[Music]
huh where are they
huh
[Music]
Labrador a monster showed up on the road
all of a sudden and I had a car crash
because of it
it was so scary
there's no such thing as a monster
but we saw it please find the monster
don't worry
there's no case that I can't saw
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
I found some Footprints
[Music]
they came from the other side of the
guardrail over there
the person that caused the car crash
must have jumped over the guardrails to
cross the road
do you remember what the Monster looked
like
its hair was like a bird a bird's nest
its nose was red and its mouth was very
big
like this
exactly that's how it looked the monster
looks so scary
I don't think it's a monster it looks
like the clown from The Rainbow Theater
now they will be a clown show at the
Rainbow Theater tonight we were on our
way there Toby let's go
look over there the monster is a clown
my goodness you're late you need to be
on stage right away don't worry I took a
shortcut I'm never late
gorilla oh you broke the traffic rules
you're under arrest oh no
stop right there
[Music]
is this a new show
foreign
[Music]
get him
don't go over the guard rail
later
yeah
[Music]
that was so scary gorilla you broke the
traffic rules you're coming with us to
the police station I'll never go over
the guardrails again as a shortcut
[Music]
Sheriff Labrador safety talk
kids we need to follow the traffic rules
always use sidewalks wherever you go and
don't go over guard rails as a shortcut
if you do you might get in a car
accident and your life might be in
danger as well remember what we've
learned today
[Music]
the ghost at midnight
foreign
oh oh
what's wrong
oh don't be afraid sweetie mommy's here
oh
where's your sister
a ghost
[Music]
missing
please help me find her
a ghost don't worry we'll be right there
my daughter was sleeping in this room
and suddenly she disappeared
Hey kid there's no such thing as a ghost
but I saw it it was white and its eyes
were bright and green it was so scary oh
sheer Labrador please save my daughter
don't worry no there's no case that I
can't solve
let's search sister monkey's room first
[Music]
this is a photo of sister monkey
there are only child's footprints on the
windowsill
and there's no sign that the window was
forced open
I don't think she was taken by anyone
so there's no ghost
[Music]
hmm
it's coffee coffee
[Music]
the ghost is coming
huh
[Music]
huh who's there
they are fireflies
[Music]
I'm Gonna Get You
ghosts
[Music]
Sheriff Labrador the ghost has just
dropped this
[Music]
a ribbon
and a flashing headband
I know what it is
[Music]
no one can run away from me
why are you helping the ghost it's not a
ghost
[Music]
it's sister monkey
our children should be sleeping at home
at night why are you out and scaring
people like that I'm sorry I couldn't
fall asleep so I came outside to play
sister monkey did you drink this
yes I was thirsty so I took it from the
fridge and drank it
coffee is for grown-ups children can't
sleep if they drink it oh I see
oh I'll be careful of what I drink from
now on
Sheriff Labrador safety talk
kids coffee is a drink that's only for
grown-ups because if children drink
coffee they can't fall asleep at night
and it's not good for their health also
tea and drinks that contain alcohol are
not for children either and you
shouldn't drink them
please keep that in mind
woof
never play with caterpillars
[Music]
uh
a caterpillar
it looks funny
[Music]
who are they all scared of caterpillars
oh
[Music]
ouch
hey Sheriff Labrador so many
caterpillars are in there it's really
scary
[Music]
the caterpillar
it feels like something
[Music]
another caterpillar
oh my neck
[Music]
my nose oh no the caterpillars are
venomous
the treatment is all done you'll feel
better soon
caterpillars usually live in the woods
they won't leave there by themselves
unless someone moves them on purpose
oh I remember
when I was doing Tai Chi this morning
I saw Little Wolf catching caterpillars
in the bush
[Music]
Little Wolf must be scaring people with
caterpillars we need to stop him now oh
[Music]
[Applause]
it's so fun to scare people with
caterpillars let's call my caterpillar
Army
[Music]
why is my arm so itchy
it's getting worse caterpillars
oh my God
stay away from me
it's Little Wolf
over there
let's go
[Music]
get off me oh so many caterpillars
phew
[Music]
the caterpillars are everywhere
be careful let's go okay
[Music]
let's get out of here
huh uh
[Music]
hey hey
aha I have an idea
Super Tornado
oh poor kid
I'll never catch caterpillars again
[Music]
Sheriff Labrador safety talk
kids some caterpillars and bugs are
venomous if they bite you the spot might
get red swollen and itchy or even worse
remember not to touch them and never
play around with them
[Music]
also if a bug lands on you don't just
grab it with your hand gently remove it
with tools
please remember that
super Cape man
[Music]
well they're awesome
attention all citizens there's a burglar
going around digging tunnels and
stealing things if you find any clues
about the suspect please contact us it's
so scary don't worry I'll keep the bad
guy away with my Escape
foreign
[Music]
nobody's here this is my chance
here's my cave attack
[Music]
hey
yeah see even the burglar's scared of me
stop right there
wait stop
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador
[Music]
what we'll be right there
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
every door my brother went after the
burglar what he might be in danger
let's go find him now
[Music]
hurry
ouch
[Music]
now let me go please I'll give you all
of my treasure here take it all
[Music]
oh why it's just a kid
[Applause]
man
you dare try to trick me
it's okay you're safe now
stop stop
right there
stop
hey stop right there
ah it's a dead end you have nowhere to
run oh no
[Music]
you'll never catch me
it's so hard
[Music]
oh no he got away
watch me
[Music]
oh man he's so sneaky
I have an idea
[Music]
oh
you think you can catch me no way oh
what's that smell
oh it stinks
nobody can run away from me
all right
Sheriff Labradors safety time
[Music]
kids if you run across bad guys don't
panic and don't try to show off and be a
hero never try to fight them
stay calm and stay away from them and
ask for help from your parents or a
police officer
please keep that in mind
a big shark is coming
[Music]
don't worry wow
here you are oh
hi I'm the new police officer
nice to meet you officer Papillon
I have lots of useful tools they'll be
handy for operations
[Music]
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador the sheriff's
Labrador the shark is
hello hello let's go to the beach right
now
so windy
[Music]
it's like me
all right
lovely time's over bye bye
[Music]
that was so scary
you guys are awesome
[Music]
but he isn't back yet
we'll go find him right now
laughs
he is over there
[Music]
hurry he's a danger
the shark's so strong run everybody
we need your help
it's the smart rescue boat it's fully
automatic
whoa let's get on
Dobby hurry up
oh no
come on
hold on tight everyone let's go
oh
yeah I'm sorry something's wrong with
the welding
but don't worry there's another way look
petals
[Music]
Adobe pedals
ah
[Music]
it was so scary
[Applause]
[Music]
Sheriff Labradors safety top
kids sharks are very dangerous sea
animals we shouldn't play in the water
when there are sharks around if you ever
see a shark get out of the water and go
to a safe place nearby also don't go
into the water when you have a wound the
smell of your blood might attract sharks
please remember these tips
[Music]
don't leave school by yourself
let's get inside
[Music]
we did it we can have some ice cream
look it's an ice cream truck
there you are thanks
let's go okay
[Music]
little rabbit
I saw them going outside together
what bye
[Music]
kill children coming out of school
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador
what we'll be right there
[Applause]
[Music]
oh sheriff Labrador they might be in
danger out there what should we do don't
worry we'll find them soon
kids can you tell us where they went
[Music]
let's go
look the ice cream truck stop let's go
[Music]
look at the traffic lights
sorry
we're finally here
[Music]
hey what's wrong did you even see the
lights
sir two ice cream cones please
that will be ten dollars
you need money to buy ice cream
two ice cream cones
[Music]
hey kids these are for you
wow thank you sir
come on now let's have some fun okay
[Music]
excuse me have you seen these children
no I haven't
sir have you seen these children
no I saw them going with fox
oh no they might be in danger hurry
let's go
[Music]
the police are following me I need to
find a place to hide the kids oh
right here oh
kids how about we play here
oh sir I don't want to play here I wanna
go back we go back
you won't go back
excuse me sir have you seen a fox with
two children around here uh two two
children they went this way
huh it's a dead end no no that way
it looks like he's hiding something we
should check out the trash cans
[Music]
[Applause]
he's running away
[Music]
nobody can run away from me
Sheriff Labradors safety talk
[Music]
kids leaving school by yourself is very
dangerous without any adult to protect
you you might get in a traffic accident
get lost or get fooled by bad people
so you should never leave school by
yourself
[Music]