Baby
[Music]
Bus happy happy Halloween I love
Halloween woo woo woo woo let's go trick
or traing baby panda baby panda where
are you Boogie boo Boogie Boo Here I Am
woo woo woo woo happy Halloween
woo woo woo woo happy
Halloween trick or tree trick or tree
give me something good to eat trick or
treat trick or treat give me something
good to
eat tiptoe tiptoe spooky
Halloween tiptoe tiptoe I love
Halloween sister panda
where are you Boogie boo Boogie boo here
I
Amo W woo wo happy
Halloween woo woo woo woo happy
Halloween trick or treat trick or treat
give me something good to eat trick or
treat trick or treat give me something
good to
eat tiptoe tiptoe spooky
Halloween tiptoe tiptoe I love
Halloween mommy Panda mommy Panda where
are you Boogie Boo boooo Here I Am woo
woo woo woo happy
Halloween woo woo woo woo happy
Halloween trick or treat trick or treat
give me something good to eat trick or
treat trick or treat give me something
good to
eat tiptoe tiptoe spooky
Halloween tiptoe tiptoe I love
[Music]
[Applause]
Halloween daddy Panda daddy Panda where
are you Boogie boo Boogie Boo Here I Am
woo woo woo woo happy
Halloween woo woo woo wo happy
hallow trick or treat trick or treat
give me something good to eat trick or
treat trick or treat give me something
good to
eat woo woo woo wo happy
Halloween wo wo wo W wo wo wo W wo wo wo
w
[Music]
h there is a
monster in the kitchen now I'll be
brave I'll take a look
at the scary
[Music]
monster there are two
monsters in the kitchen now I'll be
[Music]
brave I'll take a
look and the scary monsters
[Music]
there are three
monsters in the kitchen now I'll be
brave I'll take a
[Music]
look at the scary monster
there are four
monsters in the kitchen now just be
[Music]
[Applause]
brave a
look at the scary
monsters there's a
monster in the kitchen
[Music]
be Daddy I want to go home sweetie we'll
go home when you feel better
[Music]
I'm so scared there's a scary monster
here I hate hosts no no
no Daddy I want to go home don't be
scared it's not a monster it's a
[Music]
doctor little kid little kid don't be
nervous say don't be scared I will check
you it's okay open your mouth ah you are
such a brave
boy it was not a
[Music]
monster no no no I'm so scared I don't
like bitter
medicine I hate hospital no no
no Daddy I want to go oh you'll get
better if you take
[Music]
medicine Dear baby Dear baby don't be
nervous don't be scared baby you are
really brain
ah ging goling I did it medicine didn't
taste that
[Music]
bad oh I'm so bored I want to play with
my friends I hate hospitals no no
no Daddy I want to go
home
wow dear friend dear friend we brought a
present for you play thought it'll be so
fun
we hope you feel better
[Music]
soon today is no snacks
day give me all your
snacks my favorite
chocolate my donut
[Music]
no one's allowed to eat them okay
uhhuh
wow yay
[Music]
sweeties sweeties yes Grandpa eating
chocolate no grandpa telling lies no
grandpa open your mouth ha ha ha
[Music]
Grandpa Grandpa yes
sweeties eating Donuts no sweeties Telly
lies no
sweeties open your
[Music]
mouth you hold on to Grandpa's Donuts
okay and please keep the children's
chocolate too keep close watch over them
this time don't eat them while I'm not
looking okay
[Music]
sweeties sweeties yes
grandle eating chocolate lit no grandpa
telling lies no
grandpa open your mouth ha haa
[Music]
sweeties sweeties yes Grandpa eating
Donuts no grandpa telling lies no
grandpa open your mouths ha ha ha here
you are
[Music]
Grandpa
hey finally the monster packed up his
things and started a new
Journey maybe the monster is coming for
you really don't worry I'm here
[Music]
listen what is that
sound listen what is that sound bang
bang bang bang bang there's a monster
under the bed I'm so scared I'm so
scared don't be afraid I'm here it's
okay it's okay huh du d Da Da Da Da Da
Da Da Da Da Da Da Da Da Da Da Da a big
monster a big monster let's play a fun
game the monster has a big
[Music]
tumy and it has a big M do do do do do
the big monster so
funny let's play a game
[Music]
da da da da da a big monster a big
monster let's play a fun game come on do
as I
do come on you as I
[Music]
do a big monster a big
monster let's play a
[Music]
game now it's time to go to bed H ho ho
H ho good night big monster H ho H H
good night big monster H H ho H ho the
big and funny
monster see you in the morning
[Music]
big
[Applause]
[Music]
monster let's clean up the toys under
the
bed okay and don't leave your toys lying
around okay
[Music]
I just remembered it's Halloween oh no I
have no candy they will play tricks on
me ha Halloween ha playing tricks knock
knock knock knock on the door knock
knock knock knock who is
it a pointy pointy pyramid wrapped with
long bandages boo I'm on mommy trick or
treat your
[Music]
choice trick me time to
trick
Mischief trick or treat
[Music]
always ha Halloween ha playing tricks
knock knock knock knock on the door
knock knock knock knock who is
it Twinkle Twinkle Little Wings swinging
a magic wand boo I'm a fairy trick or
treat your
[Music]
choice trick me time to
trick
Mischief trick or treat oh it's
Hallen
wait what should I
do time to
trick
misch
trick knock knock
knock ha ha ha
knock knock
knock
it's doctor help
me here you
are huh time to harvest
pumpkins pum pumpkin jump jump
jump pumpkin jump jump jump huh oh
naughty
pumpkin my pumpkin jumping on the ground
one falls down and bumps his head the
farmer calls the witch and the witch
says to him give me that I'll make a
Jacko
Lantern ha wooo four pumpkins jumping on
the Hy stack one falls down and bumps
his head the farmer calls the witch and
the witch says to him give me that I'll
make a Jacko
Lantern
pum hey pumpkin stop
jumping oh naughty
pumpkins three pumpkins jumping in the
car jump one falls down and bumps his
head the fer calls the witch and the
witch says to him give me that I'll make
a Jacko
lantern two pumpkins jumping on the
boxes one falls down and bus his head
the farm calls the witch and the witch
says to him give me B I'll make a Jacko
Lantern pumpkin pumpkin jum jum stop
there pumpkin pumpkin jump jump run away
pumpkin pumpkin jump jump jump
yeah oh naughty
pumpkins one pumpkin jumping in the sky
he falls down and bumps his head the
farmer calls the witch and the witch
says to him give me back I'll make a
jackter
no pumpkin jumping in the cart now no
pumpkins bump their heads now oh naughty
pumpkins oh naughty pumpkin pumpkin jum
jump jump pumpin pumpkin
chump pumpkin
pumpkin naughty pumpkin
[Music]
spooky Boogie Woogie
boo spooky Boogie
[Music]
Halloween six monsters go out to trick
or treat pirate vampire ballerina they
go knocking on the door say trip tree
goody goody gum drops happy Halloween
trick or tree trick or tree goody goody
G happy Halloween spooky Boogie Woogie
boo spooky Boogie
Halloween six monsters go out to trick
or treat pumpkin Cowboy skeleton they go
knocking on the door saying tree goody
goody gum drops happy Halloween trick or
treat trick or
treaty gum drops happy Halloween spooky
Boogie Woogie
boo spooky Boogie
[Music]
H six monsters go out to trick or treat
pirate vampire ballerina they go
knocking on the door say trick or tree
goody goody gum drops happy Halloween
trick or tree trick or
treey gums happy Halloween spooky booie
Bell spooky boogy
Halloween six monsters go out to trick
or treat pumpkin Cowboy skeleton they go
knocking on the door say Trick or tree
goody goody gum drops happy Halloween
trick or tree boo trick or treat booy G
drops happy Halloween spooky booy
boo spooky boogy Halloween
[Applause]
[Music]
trick or
treat happy
[Music]
Halloween meum Mew what's wrong oh the
Halloween party is starting soon but
where our police car fire truck and
ambulance don't worry maybe they are
still on duty and we'll come soon let's
go get
[Music]
ready the Halloween party starts right
now starts right now starts right now
police car is on his way changes now
into a scary B
car the wheels on police car go round
and round round and round round and
round the wheels on police car go round
and round hurry to the Halloween ball
the Halloween party starts right now
starts right now starts right now fire
truck is on his way changes now into a
pumpkin
truck the wheel fire truck go round and
round round and round round and round
the wheels on fire truck go round and
round hurry to the Halloween ball the
Halloween party starts right now starts
right now starts right now ambulance is
on her way changes now into a scary
ghost
car the wheels on ambulance go round and
round round and round round and round
the wheels on ambulance go round and
round hurry to the Halloween ball the
Halloween party starts right now starts
right now starts right now it's so much
fun to dance together oh Halloween
[Music]
Mew
Mew where are we
going I think this is the way to the
Witch's
House we are almost there today we will
learn some magic tricks from
her learning some magic
tricks meum me wait a minute
[Music]
and itsy bitsy witch boiling Witches
Brew there are slimy worms smelly socks
and germs a bubbly bubbly stew a sloppy
sloppy goo yuck it is Hall
[Music]
witch an itsy bitsy witch flying on a
broom this is my cat and this is my bat
room room to the Moon zoom zoom to the
moon it's Halloween witch I'll
[Music]
try and itsy bitsy witch boiling Witches
Brew there are slimy worms smelly socks
and germs bubbly bubbly stew a sloppy
sloppy goo yuck it is Halloween witch
[Music]
itsy bitsy witch flying on a broom this
is my cat and this is my bat room vroom
to the Moon zoom zoom to the
Moon it is Halloween which
Mom I don't want to go to the
hospital baby you need to see the doctor
to get
better here is a dark spooky Hospital a
monster doctor and a witch nurse wearing
a black mask waving a magic wand oh it's
a really spooky
place here here is a dark spooky
Hospital a monster doctor and the witch
nurse holding a green potion waving a
magic one oh all the germs are running
away from me mom why did my body turned
all
green Mom I don't like this Hospital
baby you should see a doctor to get
better here is a doctor
spooky Hospital a monster doctor and a
witch nurse wearing a black mask waving
a magic
wand it's a really spooky
place here in a dark spooky Hospital a
monster doctor and the witch nurse
holding a green potion waving a magic
wand oh all the germs are running away
from
me Mom my body turned all green too