go go go go let's go sh
it false
advertising and
drink you can't stop drinking it the
more you drink the healthier you'll be
wow it looks so yummy let's buy some
okay
1 2
[Music]
3 wow it's so
yummy it's empty I want some
more let's buy more this
time
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
watch
out Danger let's go
[Music]
ha that was really close what happened
to you we just had this
drink we couldn't stop drinking him and
this is what happened to
[Music]
us I need I stop
drinking something's wrong let's go have
a
look I'll go
I'll go buy one excuse
me I lost my
shoe police thank you for your
[Music]
cooperation papion check the drink
okay
[Music]
yes oh it smells
great I'm going to take a sip stop
something's wrong with the
drink look it contains a lot of
unhealthy stuff they might make your
hair fall out or make you
[Music]
[Applause]
floated everyone stop drinking it who
made this drink it's horrible don't
worry there's no case that I can't
[Music]
solve with my special ingredients people
won't stop drinking
it as long as I can make money I don't
care if you lose your hair or become
bloated
[Music]
the police is coming I need to
hide it says the factory that makes the
drink is here it's in such a remote
place let's go in
now huh H nobody's here let's search
around okay
[Music]
okay that's strange where are they
hiding huh what are these strange
things ouch that
hurts you
an stop right
[Music]
there
keep playing guys I'm going to leave
you'll never catch Dr
antel
huh you can't run
away I don't want to
drink
help my hair you're coming with us to
the police
station Sheriff labor safety
[Music]
talk kids some advertisements might
trick us into buying their products
don't believe everything they say and be
careful not to be fooled please remember
[Music]
that
dangerous
[Music]
friends we got stop right
there hey follow
me oh
no bye-bye you bad thieves
go oh huh Mr bear what's going on
Sheriff lavador some kids have been
stealing candy from my shop help me
please
[Music]
huh don't worry leave it to
us how much did you
get seriously is this all you
got
shall we go back for more Mr bear knows
who we are now we can't then what should
we
do we need to find someone to help us
that's my
toy
minutes I think I found
one hey give it back to Little
Koala okay
toy wow
thanks little why don't we be friends
friends yes if we are when someone takes
away your toy we can protect you sounds
great I'll be safe
then from now on friend
come on friend let's go have some fun
[Music]
uhhuh by the way can you pretend to have
a stomach ache a stomach ache like
[Music]
this wow you did it so
well when you see Mr bear in the shop
keep acting like you have a stomach ache
why to fool him of course no no no we're
going to play a game huh we're friends
we won't lie to you come on go
inside
[Music]
wow Doby watch out someone's coming
in leave it to
me hi kid feel free to look around
didn't choose what you
want ow
ow it
hurts are you all
[Music]
right they fell for
it hurry
hurry
hurt my
tummy I'll take you to the hospital oh
no I don't want to go don't worry it's
okay no I will
go what's that
sound hey what are you doing
here something
wrong I don't want to go huh is that a
new game
what they stole the
candy let's
go Yay good job Little Koala you helped
us steal a lot of candy what you stole
candy stop right
[Applause]
there
[Music]
hey stealing things is against the law
you can't run away
stole the candy we have nothing to do
with it it's not me watch
out is
me stop right
there you're coming with us we will
never steal
again and I'll never make best friends
[Music]
again Sheriff labrador's safety
talk kids be careful when you make
friends you should never make friends
with bad people bad friends might teach
you bad habits use bad words or do bad
things if your friend asks you to do
something bad please say no and tell
adults such as your teacher parents or a
police officer please remember
[Music]
that the ghost
motorbike green
light stop at Red go at
Green
[Music]
huh what's that there's no one driving
it ah
[Music]
ow W hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
Labrador I got hit by a ghost motorbike
when I crossed the street just now what
a ghost motorbike we'll be right
[Music]
[Applause]
there
huh where is
[Music]
he I'm
here that was
close we're lucky to have hard
scales Mr
Pangolin you called the police right oh
yes I got hit by a motorbike running a
red light and you know what there was no
driver it's must have been a ghost
motorbike I'm so
scared a ghost motorbike I'm sure
something's wrong here don't worry
there's no case that I can't
solve now let's find the motorbike first
got
it every vehicle leaves a mark when it
passes
[Music]
[Applause]
by
it's a
puddle
H these are cars tire
tracks and these are motorbikes tire
tracks I found the clue it must have
gone this
way
woof let's
[Music]
go
look over
there it can't be is it a real ghost
there's no such thing as a
[Music]
[Applause]
ghost there into the alley hurry up
oh huh oh no it won't go
[Music]
far
police Mr Turtle can you help us follow
the motor like over
there
[Music]
Sure hold
on Mr Turtle are you sure you can catch
it of
[Music]
course
go let's
[Music]
go my bottom really hurts huh where are
we
huh the ghost motorbike
[Music]
huh
stop
[Music]
huh it's a
com watch
out
[Music]
no I was really scared
chameleon you broke the traffic rules
you're under
[Music]
arrest Sheriff labrador's safety
talk kids TR traffic lights are the
signals to control traffic the red light
means
stop the green light means
go and the yellow light means be careful
whether you're a driver or a pedestrian
you should always follow the traffic
lights if you don't you might get in a
traffic accident please keep that in
[Music]
mind missing little
chicky I can't hold it anymore
wow brother I want some ice
cream just wait a few
minutes all
right ice cream ice cream I'll eat some
ice
cream hey little friend
I know a really nice ice cream shop H I
can take you
there um but I don't know who you are
I'm not going with
you come on I'm a friend of your parents
don't you remember that I cuddled you
when you were a baby
a come on hurry up or the ice cream will
be all sold
out now let's go buy some ice
cream my
brother where is
he hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
Labrador my little brother is
missing what should I do don't worry
little kid we'll be right
[Music]
there
Sheriff Labrador just now I went to the
restroom but when I came out my little
brother was gone please find my little
brother don't worry kid there's no case
that I can't
solve little
[Music]
CH that's my my little brother's toy
then he must be around here let's keep
[Music]
searching that man looks suspicious he
keeps looking around he must be hiding
little chicky
somewhere stop right
there
what it's not little
Chicky what are you talking about look
it's my
[Music]
hump you could have just said it nicely
why did you rip my clothes I'm sorry I'm
so
sorry Mr Camel have you seen a little
chick who has a chubby face and is
wearing a plaid cap
H well
ah yes I have he was with a red fox and
he went into the forest that's not good
the red fox might be a kidnapper we need
to find
[Music]
him huh there are three roads which way
do you think it is
[Music]
it's all muddy here so they must have
left some Footprints let's look for
their
[Music]
footprints found them these are red box
and little chick Footprints they went
this way let's
go we're going too far to the shop I
don't want to eat ice cream anymore I
want to go home
home home no you can't go
home somebody help
me
please Sheriff
Labrador
nobody can run away from
me take him to the police
station Sheriff labrador's safety
talk kids when you go out don't wander
off alone or take things from
strangers if they say they'll take you
home you must say
no and if they threaten you never
hesitate to shout and ask other people
around you for
help remember these
tips no littering no
[Music]
mosquitoes
sh go
away so many
mosquitoes help stop following
me oh no so many mosquitoes
run what's going
on my head my lips my neck that's so
itchy what happened to you Sheriff
labador mosquitoes are everywhere in
town it's so scary look at what they did
to us please help
us they're
coming Doby let's go take a
look got
[Music]
it now they can't fight me Doby hurry up
okay
more and more mosquitoes are coming
looks like their breeding ground is over
there oh let me check it
out you can't fight
me my bottom ow my face help there are
too many of them let's
go they're
coming hide in the
Box oh that's so scary there are too
many of them what should we do papion
we're surrounded by mosquitoes we need
your help mosquitoes leave it to
me Poppy always pass
[Music]
away happy
H wow papon why aren't they coming after
you because I'm wearing mosquito patches
and
bracelets here you
[Music]
go now they can't get close to me
hey look over there the mosquitoes are
coming from
there ew it
[Music]
stinks mosquitoes are still breeding
they are most likely to breed in dirty
and wet places like
this no wonder there are so many
mosquitoes in this
town who on earth made this
[Music]
[Applause]
mess
[Music]
hey I'm not scared of
you bounce
[Music]
what's going on let's
go
[Music]
huh ouch
ouch
help let's
go
[Music]
oh
Pap watch
[Music]
me I'm so
sorry hurry
up
[Music]
hey Mr bison make sure to keep your
surroundings clean from now on I will
and I'll never litter
again Sheriff labrador's safety talk
kids mosquitoes in summer are annoying
not only do they fight but they can also
spread
diseases mosquitoes usually breed in
dirty and wet places so we need to keep
our houses
clean also we need to keep our town
clean and don't Litter please remember
that don't play with
sockets
Go
Dino welcome to robot snack house how
can I help
you I want to get some
[Music]
too here's your ice
cream
yay it's so
yummy wow one chocolate cake
please okay
[Music]
please what's going on huh chocolate
chocolate
[Music]
huh chocolate cake is ready oh no the
robot turned me into a cake Blueberry
Blueberry
[Music]
help let me go blueberry ice cream is
ready oh that's so
terrible
[Music]
ouch the juice cup needs to be filled
with juice yummy juice is ready
please help H what's going
on a super
[Music]
donut
help Miss king rat snake what made you
become a donut Sheriff Labrador
something's wrong with the robot in the
snack house huh let's go have a look
help us
please oh no they all became food hot
dog hot
dog ah stop chasing me Doby draw the
robot's attention help you let's save
others hey robot look here
come on turn me into a hot dog hot dog
hot
dog it's coming come on uh-oh
[Music]
run we're safe
now oh no it's so fast Sheriff
Labrador I can't go on I have an idea
let's run circles around the
robot strawberry mango avocado proag
proag
uh finally it
stopped what's wrong with the food robot
papion give it a
check it circuits are broken no wonder
it went out of control
[Music]
let's go check the
shop huh the robot's charging socket is
burnt oh no something's wrong over
there the sm's coming out of my house
stay here we'll go have a
look huh get
down
oh my what's going
on look the dino robot's hand got stuck
in the socket that's what made the food
robot and other sockets broken we need
to turn off the
power over
[Music]
there leave it to me
hey huh trash detected trash detected go
away I'm not
trash
huh watch your
back hey power
[Music]
off oh that was so scary Little Bear you
should stay away from sockets
okay I got
[Music]
it Sheriff labrador's safety
talk kids sockets are very dangerous and
you should never touch them if you do
you could get seriously hurt by electric
shock so if you need to use electricity
ask an adult for help please remember
that little Rhino was taken by a monster
an
orange a
banana a half rotten
[Music]
apple wow Sheriff Labrador that was
awesome it was a piece of cake I even
know that you haven't showered for 3
[Music]
[Laughter]
days
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff Labrador
little Rhino was taken by a monster
please help him a monster don't worry
kid we'll be right
[Music]
[Applause]
there the sh labador what do you mean
that little Rhino was taken by a
monster well we were playing hide and
seek and we looked for him everywhere
but couldn't find
him my grandma told me there is a
monster that only takes children who
don't take a
shower little Rhino's feet smell really
bad so it must be the monster who took
him well
kids there's no
monster wait little Rhino's feet smell
bad that's an important clue if we
follow the smell of his feet we'll be
able to find him
[Music]
smell
I got
it it smells
terrible who didn't flush the
[Music]
toilet I think I smell the
evidence
[Music]
oh come on it's just a smelly
shoe little Rhino must be hiding in
here hey little Rhino don't worry I'll
get you out
[Music]
there he
is little Rhino little
[Music]
Rhino what
happened we got you were Tak by
[Music]
monster when we started playing hide and
seek I thought that if I hit in the
closet you wouldn't find
[Applause]
me what it was so dark and
stuffy I tried to get out but the door
wouldn't
open I was so
scared little Rhino it's really
dangerous to hide in the closet never do
that again
okay I'll never do that
again Sheriff labrador's safety talk
kids please be careful when you play
hide and seek never hide in a closet or
a chest you could run out of
air and don't hide in narrow places
under the sofa you could be stuck stairs
and balconies are dangerous too you
could fall and get hurt remember never
hide in dangerous
places don't play with
soap hey
it's so much fun oh my look at these
little buddy
kids all
[Music]
right wash off all the mud okay
body
so help help us what what's
[Music]
wrong what's going
on wo hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
Labrador it's Mr elephant my house
floating with bubbles we'll be right
[Music]
there oh my what's with all these
bubbles let's get
[Music]
inside oh where's the door
oh the door knobs
here that's strange the door knobs
running away H gotcha ouch my
[Music]
nose I'm
sorry come here I found the
[Music]
door
bubbles Len to
[Music]
me I'm going to blow them all
away Mr elephant where are
youby
[Music]
finally Mr
elephant I've got bubbles in my eyes it
hurts so much bubbles can harm your eyes
let's wash them up right
now what's that sound
my kids are still upstairs please save
them little brother where are
you
brother let's go
upstairs
aw the floor is all slippery with
bubbles papion we need some slip proof
tools got it slip proof tool slip proof
tool this will do
taada huh a
[Music]
plunger they were
great
help it's brother elepant
[Music]
hey that was so scary
help oh no watch
[Applause]
out
Daddy Daddy was so
worried oh no the whole bottle is empty
no wonder there were so many bubbles
kids playing with body soap is very
dangerous we'll never do that
again Sheriff labrador's safety
[Music]
talk kids don't play with body soap hand
soap or shampoo which all make many
bubbles if they drip on the floor you
can slip on them and get hurt and if the
bubbles get in your eyes they can make
your eyes sting or even worse please
remember
that don't go with others
pets Mommy will go get some ice cream
stay here and wait until mommy's back
okay ha this is my chance it's my pet
Lulu's
[Music]
Showtime let's get
started wow you look so
cute there you
are sir is this Lulu your pet it's so
cute isn't it
cute oh I need to go to the bathroom now
can you watch my Lulu for me for a
second
[Music]
okay stop don't
go
[Music]
wow smells
great oh sty these are pet
cookies but it tastes good though of
course because I made them
myself hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
Labrador help me my child little sheep
is missing please come right now what
we'll be right
[Music]
there Sheriff Labrador my daughter was
playing right here but she disappeared
in a Flash what should I
do don't worry there's no case that I
can't
[Music]
solve Doby let's investigate the
scene not here not here
[Music]
either these are little sheep's
Footprints what's
this I think it's a red Lulu's hair
according to the footprints little sheep
and the Lulu went that way if we find
the Lulu we will find Little Sheep
aha woof this is papion papion we need
your pet cookies the more the better no
[Music]
problem little mon
time take these cookies to
them we'll be able to find the red Lulu
with these cookies do you you think it
will
work this is way too good there isn't
any red Lulu
here let's
go stay away for
me don't run I can't keep up with
you where am
I hm
good
job oh where are you come out please
huh I got you
[Music]
hi these are all the cookies we
got another
Lulu red
hair the same Footprints that's it
follow
it where's my
Lulu there you
are hey
police Labrador you're safe now stop you
can't get
away
really
I'll go first see you
later watch
me nobody can run away from
[Applause]
me Sheriff labrador's safety
talk kids pets may look cute but you
need to be careful because bad people
people might use them to trick you if a
stranger asks you to take care of a pet
or to come home with them to see other
pets they have don't listen to them
please remember
that falling
firecrackers oh no I've got to
[Music]
go
R Sheriff Labrador someone Just Dropped
a Bomb into the restroom what a bomb yes
and I got burned please find doubt who
did this don't
worry there's no case that I can't
[Music]
solve I can't see any traces of the bomb
what's
that
huh it's just a
firecracker the firecracker must have
come through the vent over there but the
vent is so high up on the
[Music]
wall who could have done
it over
there let's
[Music]
go my sand castle is ruined
my ice
[Music]
cream oh man why can't we even see the
suspect firecrackers
again sure Labrador we were taking
pictures here and suddenly a firecracker
flew towards us it's
[Music]
terrible taking pictures can I see the
pictures please
[Music]
mhm
look here's the
[Music]
suspect it can fly that's why we
couldn't find it
ouch oh I'm sorry I didn't see you
coming what are you looking at
there I'm not looking at anything I'm
keeping my head up because my neck is
hurt Mr giraffe did you see anyone
flying
around let's see Two Sparrows a pigeon
and a flying
squirrel a fly fing
squirrel the suspect is probably the
Flying Squirrel which way did he fly huh
that
way wow firecrackers are so much
fun 1 2 1 2 1 2 1
2 here's a big one for
[Music]
you 1 2 2 1 2 1 2 1
2 what's going
on I'm on
[Music]
fire
help oh there
[Music]
hurry
that was so
scary little flying squirrel you should
never play tricks on others with
firecrackers you could hurt other people
and yourself
too I'm so sorry sheriff
Labrador Sheriff labrador's safety
[Music]
talk kids firecrackers are
dangerous you should never light them
without
permission if your parents say it's okay
make sure to have them by your side and
be careful please remember to do
that baby swan got
lost oh Mommy
Mommy
ouch
[Music]
hey little kid are you all
right I lost my
[Music]
mommy don't cry kid we'll help you find
your mommy don't worry there's no case
that I can't
solve kid what's your name
my name is gray and your mommy's name
mommy um I mean what's your mommy's
name it's just
[Music]
mommy well do you know your mommy's
phone number oh maybe
7773 and
three
hello
hello are you Gray's
mommy
what gray gr
what
gr as my gray skirt
arrived it's nothing
sorry hey gray are you sure it's
77733 uh I don't remember then do you
know your address um no I just know
there's a big pond by my house a pond
the wild goose family live by the pond
great let's go to their
[Music]
house how is it
Sheriff Labrador can I help you Mr wild
goose are all of your children home
right now of course they're all at home
with me everyone gather
up 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 a I have only six
children
why are there seven
Now where's
gray which one is
gray
aha everyone line
[Music]
upow wait
aha I got you
gray we haven't found any
clue huh Mumu ice cream I love mumo ice
cream gray do you and your mommy often
come here to buy Mumu ice cream
uh-huh then let's go and
[Music]
ask hi may I help you is C do you know
gray here gray what are you doing here
your mommy was looking for
you where did she go that
way huh
Mommy a swine so gray is a little
swine mommy
mommy mommy is
missing she's over
there where's my
child coming through sorry excuse
me we can't catch up with her what do we
do I have an
[Music]
idea yeah Miss Swan Miss Sheriff
laborator finally look over there
[Music]
Mommy
Mommy Mommy Mommy oh
sweetie oh where did you go my child oh
I've been so worried about
you Sheriff labrador's safety
talk kids when you go out with your
parents you should always stay close to
them and if you lose them stay where you
are and wait for them or ask a police
officer for help also make sure to
memorize your parents' phone numbers and
your home address it will help police
officers find your parents please keep
these in
mind