the San Antonio Spurs are now just one
step away from the prize that has been
their goal all season long the NBA
Championship tonight it's game five of
the NBA Finals go SPS
[Applause]
go it ends today get it done get it done
tonight last year we're 30 seconds away
way we have it in the bag and and it
slips out of our fingers it's not over
till it's over our goal right now is
just to win one more game standing in
the way is the two-time defending
Champion heat a team that has used a
two-day break between games to regroup
and refocus I'm very confident I believe
in our our guys I believe in our group
and we look forward to trying to get
this win
tonight head back to Miami R for game
six take care of business offensive
defensively fly around Follow My
Lead
away he'll take it the other way leans
in on a runner missed it and from the
weak side to collect the rebound is
LeBron James James on the follow and an
80 run to begin the game it's the
largest lead of the finals for the Miami
Heat LeBron James tracks him on radar
and flies in to rebuke the shot spiking
it out of bounds when he says follow me
it's not just putting up huge numbers
it's showing huge effort two on the shot
clock James real long three got it oh my
that one from some 30 ft away on the big
stage you got to deliver he's delivered
and they're going to ask for an encore
here just remember we have to do this
together the great part is we got all
night long to take care of a bad start
but we do it by doing what we normally
do the beauty of the Spurs offense never
letting the ball
stick left wing Boris di lobs to the rim
s to slam dunk on the alleo great way to
start the second
quarter how good is this Spurs team and
the way that they battle compete and
never get W Duncan low left turns into
the lane sweeping right-hander up and in
Tim Duncan going to work on Haslam well
the Spurs weathered that early storm
we're starting to look like we're moving
the ball a little bit more on offense
it's all it has to be done at that end
James drives can't finish Leonard the
rebound Leonard for three
dang first lead of the game for the
Spurs you're hearing MVP chance from the
crowd Manu into the front Court he'll
drive it inside Manu all the way in left
hand
slam wow Manu that is why you do the
voodoo that you do so well and the Spurs
on a 140 run after trailing by 16 the
Spurs lead by seven at intermission we
got to bring more energy to our offense
we got to help each other get a shot
right now help each other for the Miami
Heat what do they have left can they
come back in the course of game six wa
blocked by
splitter and remember last year when
James blocked splitter here splitter
gets his
revenge now he finds di cutting aside
Boris to the right wing Mills for three
good day Mike py Mills with a
three-pointer back to back frees for the
5-year vet from CRA Australia this man
can shoot he has electrified the crowd
Spurs running away a 17-point
lead we're playing the backto back NBA
champion right keep pounding now keep
pounding now don't let him back
in Parker oh beautiful hesitation and
floats it in Parker was cold early but
right now he's hot and he wants to
finish off Miami San Antonio did it as a
with some of the most beautiful team
basketball we've seen in a long long
time spurs by 18 everybody on their feet
at the AT&T Center chumper good 7even
for seven in the fourth quarter for Tony
parer it's
9676 it's time to celebrate San
Antonio San Antonio Spurs are the world
champion the Spurs have captured their
fifth NBA championship
thanks for pissing me oh my God oh my
God crazy feeling that's what it's about
baby
right the fans of San Antonio know how
great you are and now the whole world
does you are the
2014 Bill Russell
MVP and they will celebrate this title
in Europe South America Australia the or
Islands Canada and especially here in
San
Antonio it wasn't about Tim dunan or
Tony Barker it was about Kawai was Danny
Green Boris de this is a team and that's
what makes it so so
[Applause]
nice they dominated us they took two
games on our home
court uh by 20 points a piece they beat
us by 20 tonight you know you have to
tip your hats off to those guys they
they play best basketball I've ever seen
it's all for the team and it's never
about the individual and that's how team
basketball should be
played you know it's
selfless I asked them
first um I didn't explain it to them
they explained it to me I was like um
you know what do you think about you
know Daddy going back home to play he
was like home you talking about
Cleveland
I'm like yeah it was like okay you get
to play with Kyrie Irving I was like I
was like yeah they was like we get to go
back home to our to our house and I get
to go back home to my old school and my
old friends like yeah I like okay you
can do
it and that's how it
[Laughter]
went
it's game one of the NBA finals and for
the first time ever an NBA Finals game
will be played in
Oakland our goal is a win a championship
and it's one that's realistic for us
we're ready and Poise for that uh opport
Unity a lot of work to do to get there
though it's exciting and just can't wait
to hoop in about an hour and a half a
lot of nerves so it's be a lot of
fun we've earned this trip every second
of this should be enjoyable and the best
way to enjoy it is to just let that
thing fly and play like you know how to
play I'm looking forward to being part
of it once again the
magnitude the talent the
quality the lights even get brighter
we went through every task we went
through everything everything odds
against us but we here let's get through
it all right by any means necessary you
pick your brother up if he
down same game fell same
Mission be the best version of ourselves
every single possession let's get this
done just US 1 2's
go which man will lead his team to the
promised land well the answer lies
straight
ahead conrat man I'm so happy for you
it's crazy is it a fabulous thank you
you too good luck with
everything you already know what time is
dominate this game from beginning in the
back green pass for Livingston stolen by
Irving Irving on the attack drives it
green BL it up with the left handed in
and the Cavs lead 1911 and what a start
for the Cavaliers JR Smith guarded by
Livingston step back free oh he knocks
it down J.R Smith in a phone booth cans
it from the left side and the Cavaliers
have taken a 2915
lead it's exactly how I thought this
game would start lot of energy franic
Pace everybody's a little little jumpy a
little nervous that's that's supposed to
happen it's the final Andre sizes of
James shakes the dribble moves left now
right H pass James to the basket with a
twoand
jab we
go and the quarter comes to an
end
everybody the first quarter just trying
to do it on their own and it's not going
to work against this team but if we move
it we cut and we set screens we're going
to get opening here's curry in traffic
Works to the basket at nothing there he
circles the world gets it to green back
Curry a three it's good game tied at 36
and Cleveland will take timeout don't
lose concentration even for a minute you
know that team right that's it keep
pushing the ball Curry guarded by James
putting out a dribbling swimming Curry
gets away scoots inside again left hand
and Bs it
in both these teams have such good
halfcourt defenses you need some of
those easier easier
buckets James gets H to the paint back
shot is good as the Caps go back up by
four I want him to see one go in we
going to keep playing I'm going to keep
playing James has his 76th third plus
Point playoff game that passes Kareem
Abdul Jabar third All
Time come on now put it together for one
quarter for one quarter all right fellas
in May a little run that's good keep
your composure come right back at him
screen set by mozgov TA of the key three
for the blind good and he ties the game
at 96 he's got 42 here we go win a
basketball
game well with thought this had the
potential to be a dream matchup so far
so good curry right side Curry has a
lane to the basket driv puts it up
harving blocked it from behind Kyrie
Irving blocked it from behind and we'll
go to
overtime five minutes win the game let's
go soon as we can get to our game plan
offensively we'll be in great shape
Steve Curry saying push Curry trying to
draw the foul almost goes in and he got
hit as Curry wants the crowd to get
fired
up now you see Irving and Kyrie Irving
is hurt now that he's off the court
showing how much pain he's in and what a
terrible sight to see right
now 207 to go OT Curry hook pass up toy
gal chest pass over to Mar's open Hill
fire free ball left corner pocket
Harrison bar the Warriors who are down
14 in the first half they went 108 to
100 and take a 1- n
lead in The Best of seven NBA
Finals that's one game fellas that's one
game we had a chances to win that game
too execute a little bit better on
offense we're going to beat these guys
one game down that's it come back to
game two get ready well I mean we had a
lot of miscues tonight and uh it's up to
us uh now you know to make some
adjustments you know and be ready for
Sunday
three more three more and we got a ring
baby let's
go huge win uh you know to start the
series off up 1 especially with home
court advantage that was important
didn't play our best but we gut it out
and got a win now game two is even more
[Music]
important
on Thursday night Cleveland lost more
than just a game all-star point guard
Kyrie Irving is out for the series with
a fractured kneecap and now the
Cavaliers have to fill a major void guys
we've been in this situation before and
to all of your credit that's what
brought us to where we are right now I'm
motivated to get our guys ready to go
tomorrow good work good job way to be
sharp you know with Kyrie being out
people are writing us off so um
next man up and um guys be ready for the
challenge we're coming out the window
Mall let's go let's go come on let's go
together
Warriors
Warriors for the Warriors they look to
take another step closer to an NBA title
something fans in the Bay Area haven't
seen in 40 years right now it's crazy
being a warrior fan because it's been so
long it's been a generation I was here
for the
1975 championship and it's just awesome
that my daughter can come with me
now it's been a lot of dark days here
but now it's a new day and you'll see
grown men crying if they went in
[Music]
here got to get it done they without
Kyrie they going to come out playing
hard we just got to do what we do hey
next man up mentality what are you going
to do tonight how you going to make a
difference how you going to make the
play to get over to H fogus has the ball
he's at the right elbow puts it on the
for fogus bounce pass to Curry wild shot
off the glass it goes in curry threw it
up in the air and somehow chopped
through four steps golden state has
scored the last five out come the
Cavaliers in their blue uniforms
attacking the basket down to our right
LeBron spins to the paint takes a fade
away jumper and scores tough shot by
LeBron James who's now five of nine from
the field for 10
points possession by possession
just get a stop get a score get a stop
rebound move the ball come on down and
play our game they find Klay Thomson
guarded by delova he likes the match up
step back jumper off the dribble
Thompson and the Warriors lead by three
move it move it move it 14 points in 8
minutes for Klay
Thompson he's seven of nine from the
field he has seven of their 11 field
goals
all right Fells get through these Miss
we're all right come on now right there
come right there let's
go 520 to go in the second quarter Jones
right corner James Jones snaps a three
Jones Off the Bench with eight points
this the Cavs are in the midst of a 102
Run come on M energy now James is
isolated now mozgov cuts across the lane
mozgov left-handed pretty play from
moscov a terrific first half for
Cleveland without Kyrie
Irving these guys are a for take we got
to stay focused we got to stay locked be
[Music]
disciplined Harry catch and shoot short
the shooting Wes continue for Steph
Curry this game for Cleveland it's been
all about their defense delova part of
that defense starting in place of Kyrie
Irving 10 is on the shock block LeBron
James has the ball in the near Wing
where he's guarded by Draymond Green
accelerat goes Baseline lays it up and
lays it in time out Golden State as the
Cavaliers take an 11-point lead a triple
double for LeBron
James we got it right what we do we got
a lot of heart we got a lot of fight in
us let's finish the deal like we did the
other night 250 to go Curry off a screen
left hand guarded by LeBron takes a
three off the dribble knocked it down
Curry to the right side get up get up
get up come on now 25 left Curry takes a
three off the rim no good igod Alo the
rebound inside a dunk for Barnes a foul
by JR Smith Golden State fighting back
down the
stretch eye drama here in
Oakland both teams just fighting tooth
and
nail 15 seconds left the Warriors are
down by two Curry off the screen splits
traffic down the lane to the rim layup
good we're
tied for the first time in NBA history
the first two games of the NBA finals
are going to
overtime let keep our energy up now okay
come on let's keep our energy up we
dropped energy wise last game not this
game keep our energy
up James find sheer sheer gets a good
look goes to sheer for three got
it James attacks down one at igod
pitched in the corner James Jones for
three off the rim no Del overa rebound
and he got fouled those are the plays
that you show tomorrow you want to win
don't talk about it be about
it and the Cavaliers with 10.1 seconds
remaining in overtime lead the Warriors
9493 and now golden state with a chance
to take the lead and Win
It Curry on the drive step back puts it
up step back jumpers an airball it's gra
by LeBron this one is over the Cavaliers
claim game two in overtime and we are
going back to Cleveland tied at one an
inspiring bounce back win for the
Cavaliers and this crowd stuned that's a
big win for the Cleveland
Cavaliers proud of awful lot of winning
plays out there a lot of winning
play we got right back where we want now
that was even serious we're going home
together 1 2
three and from here on out we got to get
better right we you're in the same
position against
Memphis we figure it out and we go 1:1
slide to Cleveland tomorrow let's keep
rolling it means everything for this
franchise for our city for all the Cavs
fans all over the
world I'm looking forward to seeing our
fans and I can't
wait it's all about grit it's all about
grp gave everything that we had and uh
we live with the results I see y'all in
[Music]
Cleveland
when LeBron came back to Cleveland last
summer fans had dreams of the finals
those dreams have come true let's go
this how we do it in Cleveland baby this
how we do it let's go I know our fans
are going to be unbelievable tonight and
this probably be the loudest I've ever
heard them I think our guys are very
excited about you know playing in front
of them everybody in Cleveland and the
organization has been all in all year
we're ready to go the most valuable
player Stephan Curry is coming off a
nightmarish game too will the Warriors
bounce back from a loss and raise their
level of
play energy and passion and intensity B
48 minutes let's go let's man
up we play the same way we played on the
west coast the same way same lock in
mentality don't let the guard
down
your
C LeBron Jam takes him right
Baseline
toaw and they off to an excellent
start this Cleveland defense just
tenacious ball deflected by Miller
Miller Dives and keeps it alive how
about Mike Miller giving it up for the
team multiple efforts smart play those
good boys all right take good shots
every time down LeBron has the
basketball he finds James Jones for a
rhythm three he KN it down and the first
half is in the books Cavaliers 44
Warriors
37 so right there guys we got to keep
Our poise but we got to bring our brains
to this half bring our brains and our
hearts and compete compete compete
compete drives on mozgov gets to the rim
and throws it down oh impressive dunk
from Klay Thompson at that end we must
continue to move don't stop now's not
the time to get
static this time is on the right side
works on bars heals back to delova who
unloads a three hey knocks it down
delova has 15 points and the Cavaliers
have a 15-point
lead we're too good to play like this
too good to hang our heads right let's
go Barbosa dribbles around delova the
floater no good lead jammed it down two
hand
slam well if any team has the ability to
come back from a huge deficit it's Goen
State Curry on the right side it goes
revers and scores going right to left
Golden State right back in it after
traing by
20 sorry I did made a run run it right
back at him come on now come on
Fells LeBron he's got a two-on one with
Dela
Dela back to LeBron he throws it down
this place is going
nuts back to delova T to shoot behind
Curry now down the lane off balance
shoot a par he B it in delova was
falling down to his left we are seeing
the emergence of one of the more
improbable playoff heroes in recent
postseason history run run run 9488 here
come the Warriors it's curry curry left
sideline gets an open daylight fires a
three got another one for the far side
it's a one possession game what an
unpredictable roller coaster we have
seen so far they cannot beat you if they
do not score we have got to play this
end the way we played the the first
three quarters Golden State are playing
with a ton of confidence right
now
Cur lson it's stolen by James that's fou
by Thompson another extraordinary
performance from LeBron
James 40 points 12 rebounds eight
assists and he now has the most points
ever scored in the first three games of
the
[Music]
finals golly that's tremendous they made
some tough shots we may Ben but we do
not
break
it's good win for us fellas stay humble
and hungry all we got to do is win one
game here every single person who steps
on the floor we have to fight the whole
[Applause]
game
baby
923 the fan getting you ready for game
number four of the NBA Finals when you
look at the global perspective on what
LeBron James means to the game of
basketball winning this series with a
depleted Team without Kevin Love Without
Anderson veral without Kyrie Irving with
a M Shumpert playing with one arm and
Matthew delova coming out of the
hospital I just think for LeBron this is
the greatest challenge that he has ever
seen it's been a difficult challenge but
I accept it all we're underman we
undermatched and we're
fighting the Golden State Warriors walk
in the quick and load's
Arena not in a must-win situation but
they are as close as you could be to
just
that spacing activity gu what that is
it's us anyway it's who we've been all
year long that's what tonight is
about stay desperate as we've been stay
desperate every game for us is a game T
and we have zero room for
error anybody want to go over anything
at all anything Kenny
Jason Rock
and the Cavaliers lead two nothing a
minute 40 gone by James behind the Head
Pass mava DP it was a head high pass and
James just tapped it over his head how
about the vision mozgov on the other
side finishes timeout coming let's into
the crowd in
Cleveland storm they got a lot of energy
right now with the crowd in over 48
minutes they're playing seven people
they're going to wear down Steve CT
changing things up they're going small
Draymond Green's going to play center
and Andre Iguodala will start for the
first time this season Outlet aoda
Breakaway slam with a right
hand roll reversal tonight it was the
Cavs that were taking the fight to the
Warriors but tonight the Warriors really
putting up a good fight here on the
first
down don't lose your way now fight
through this period we'll get through it
we will
regroup now you really got to focus
Fells having a tough time keep your Bo
stay in it elova finds LeBron James
spins Baseline and as sty as he goes
inside it's been a more physical game as
James Goes Down apparently cut his head
a bit but he's going to stay in the
game Curry bent over the way to the
dribble gets it back to the right hand
comes back left hand right hand gets
bump stumbles goes all the way in for a
layup and he scores with 3.5 to go in
the
[Music]
half one thing that should never happen
and cannot happen second half is for
them to play a part of the
wheel that's what we got
guys that's what we
got if we play harder and tougher than
them we got to lay it out there till
you're
done
CS in transition delova middle of the
floor lock to LeBron for the D crowd
back into it with this
run here's the double team mozgov wisely
coming across perfect execution there
that's seven assists for James 21 points
for
mozgov to me right now the momentum
seems to be going to Cav's way keep
playing game's not over keep playing no
momentum what a pivotal moment right now
in this series one more great quarter
from Golden State and they tie the
series with two of the final three on
their whole floor flips it up shot short
Curry gets a running start P it push
it he's got one man ahead of him goes
past Jones nice feed to Thompson and the
lead back up to 10 quick timeout called
by David
[Music]
black let's pick up our defense fs and
we're not getting back make the miss
Sprint back we don't need to do anything
special everybody
rebound good shots to great shot let's
get great
shot rotation to igawa Triple is down
for Andre head coach Steve Kerr made
another brilliant move in this
postseason he starts Andre igawa and the
Warriors came out wanting it got them
going and it's allowed them to tie up
the NBA Finals at two games a piece
final score Golden State One 3 and
Cleveland
82 just got to work harder than they do
every night be a to get some wins that's
the recipe for success and we finally
figured it out
tonight now we go back to the bay on
Port Advantage best two out of three and
uh we got a tough task ahead of us
but'll be ready for the
[Music]
challenge
[Applause]
this is mosswood Park Oakland California
and we out here talking about the
Warriors well we all know they going to
win the finals so a too much talk about
that the energy level got to be there
they have to play their game and don't
play nobody else's game what they have
to do is just keep putting Steph Curry
through the isolation he got to get high
he has had one of those games where he's
just been on fire so I think he's due
for that game pivotal game fire
especially know with it being tied two
to two so this game right here the
biggest of the series we got to get this
one we gave up one on our home floor
it's going to be crazy it's going to be
great for the fans it's right in front
of us fellas One Step Closer to our goal
we control our destiny let's go just US
1 2 3 sir we get started right away all
right don't wait around together on
three 1 2 3 together Klay Thompson puts
on the brakes now the timeline gets a
screen from Draymond Thompson finds
green perfectly executed pick and roll
1611 Golden State 325 to go beautiful
drive from LeBron James LeBron James
zigzags over the pass from the left wing
side gets F puts it up puts it in LeBron
James has been superb with a near triple
double in the first
half JR Smith front Court turn and toss
a three is good again that's in j
hey get in here we've lost our
competitive Fire come on let's go
compete T to shoot back door shovel the
igod behind the back of David Lee a
beautiful pass and Lee with a twoand rim
record well it's been a wild first half
Curry steps back
bang 12 lead changes here are the first
two quarters of game
five guys we got to play harder
continually
we have come this far and come through a
lot cuz we never have given in make sure
we're matching their energy it's our
half it's our kind of game man I love IT
Crowd still
standing in a large part of the Arena
Livingston up top he to Barn right side
Barnes in the lane over mus throws it
down and a foul Harrison Barnes took off
from the side of the lane and threw it
down over the seven footer poys an
execution and just run at every
three-point shooter all right here we go
let's fight play the game keep playing
the game everybody box everybody got a
rebound now let's go to work come on who
will be up three games to two and LeBron
James going to win on the road five to
shoot back out LeBron James puts up a
three gets it to go and now another
triple double for LeBron James hey this
is your kind of game your kind of game
you can get anywhere you want against
these guys come on now dig in get a stop
right here dig in
Curry at the right Point works on delova
takes a step back three here with game
five the two MVPs going back and
forth Stephen Curry with some
magic another eruption from the Oracle
crowd their team on the verge of taking
a 3-2 lead in the NBA Finals Warriors
will take a little time here Curry gets
a screen tribes on delova both behind
the back left crossover Fades and
[Applause]
fires oh my goodness curry with another
three the Warriors have a 10-point lead
game five to the home
team game six Tuesday in Cleveland the
Warriors can win the title the Cavaliers
will try to force game seven back
here pay attention to detail keep
defending like crazy and keep competing
we can get this done in Cleveland that's
the goal get the next one that's
it one more game one more game wining
six first time 4 the
[Music]
in now we got our backs to the wall
let's see how we respond I know we can
Tuesday let's go come
[Music]
on got a huge win at home one step away
from our goal just got home at 1:00
all this is about uh winning one more
game no matter how we get it done
hopefully we get it done on
Tuesdays what a story this has been
underdogs all the way the Warriors have
done it the Golden State Warriors have
just won the NBA
Championship it's been 40 years since
the Warriors last celebrated an NBA
title today they're one win away from
making history again we're not done
let's go Cavs get it done tonight
go but standing in their way a HomeTown
hero drawing on his championship
experience I feel confident cuz I'm the
best player in the
world that's
simple you've earned the right to be
here you've earned the right to play in
this game but we have to earn one more
thing and that's the game tonight
nobody's giving us
anything people that think they can and
people that think they cannot and
honestly probably both of them are right
but what's important is what you
believe number 23
Li
[Music]
je Ain't No Tomorrow ain't no tomorrow
right now don't worry about tomorrow
what tomorrow bring it's all about right
now and a big difference in the last
couple of games for Golden State they
get off to good start bigod after the
inbounds with the CH clock at eight
right side Draymond Green the Action
cutting is a beautiful back door with
curry who lays it up and in all right
good job guys Good Start Boys poys take
care of the ball keep defending back
door curry curry triple team out to get
doesn't want to shoot it gets to the
curry he'll
fire and hit a three right in front of
the Golden State bench talk about a gift
to shoot the basketball that was locked
and load come on guys they made a run
let's run right back at him one play at
a time FS One play at a time we're all
right FS back to LeBron in the corner
with the clock at three guarded by
Livingston step back corner three it's
good what a shot by James six in a row
to start the quarter for the Cavs well
that was an impossible shot he got to
keep working at that end keep playing
defense Fells gets inside blocked by
mozgov what a defensive presence for Tim
mozgov here in the second quarter
Warriors struggling offensively these
cab fans do not want their season to end
tonight GES drives off balance Thompson
on the follow now on the half the
Cavaliers are back within two in this
must-win game
six doing some good things the first
quarter we moved the ball a lot better
than we did in the second we started
settling now it's just a matter of
executing and doing our
jobs Curry somehow comes out of the pack
with the ball dribbles down the lane
passing two hand slam beautiful feed by
Curry get up get get up three on two
Curry puts up the
[Applause]
three Ail on the follow and the foul
that's is ail with the slam and it's a
13-point
lead guys there's a lot of game left
don't put your head down play a lot of
game left come on green outside the arc
on the right P left side taken away by
James here's LeBron to the
basket Ducks him with the right hand
all of a sudden it's a seven-point game
come on BS come on come on guys and the
energy is back in quicking Loans
Arena but if you're the Cavs right now
you got to find a way to get stops on
the defensive end Curry gets an opening
fires
away got it again Stephen Curry from
downtown it's back to
11 back to Draymond Up and Under throws
the corner there's igod he'll
launch healo wide open shot that'ss the
three-pointer go look State could start
their celebration LeBron James with the
congratulations to the MVP and it's over
the championship is back in the bay for
the first time in 40
[Applause]
years and the dream season is now
complete the Golden State Warriors are
the 2015 NBA champions
clay we did
it just
beginning and one of the great regular
seasons in the history of the league 67
wins is going to end with the
title it could have been a lot of these
guys but there can only be one MVP
incredible incredible work this year's
Bill Russell MVP is a player who didn't
start in a single game until these
finals Andre IG
[Music]
[Applause]
DOA people don't understand how hard the
journey is to get
here 12 years 11 years people play their
whole careers never get a championship
we got one we earned it too first
championship how's it feel the words my
[Music]
[Applause]
man I'm just going to sit here for a
second the hours in the hard work the
practice fight through
injuries this it looks so much better in
person
too oh
man I'm tired my mind's still racing
it's history you know we really all
blessed and we just happy right
[Music]
[Applause]
now
it starts with one thing I don't know
why it doesn't even matter how hard you
tried keep that in mind I design is Ry
to explain in due time all I know time
is a valuable thing watch it Fly by as
the pendulum swings watch you countown
to the end of the day the clock takes
light away so unreal didn't look outow
watch the time go right out the window
trying to hold on to didn't even know or
wasted it all watch you I kept
everything inside and even though I
tried it all fell apart what it meant to
be will eventually be a memory of a time
I tried so hard and got so
far but in the end it doesn't even
matter I had to far to lose it
all but in the end it doesn't even
matter one thing I don't know know why
it doesn't even matter how hard you try
keep that in mind I designed this rhyme
to remind myself how I tried so hard in
spite of the way you were mocking me
acting like I was part of your property
remember ring all the times you fought
with me I'm surprised it got so things
aren't the way they were before you
wouldn't even recognize me anymore not
that you knew me back then but it all
comes back to me in the you kept
everything inside and even though I
tried it all fell heart what it meant to
me will eventually be a memory of a time
when I tried so hard and got so
far but in the end it doesn't even
matter I had to fall to lose it
all but in the end it doesn't even
matter I put my
trust in
you st far as I can go for all this
there's only one thing you should
know I've put my
trust in you pushed as far as I can go
for all this there's only one thing you
should
know
I tried so hard and got so
far but in the end it doesn't even
matter I had to fall to lose it
all but in the air it doesn't even
[Applause]
[Music]
matter
[Applause]
[Music]
you know you up right byebye wish
you luck with life but I'll be damned if
I let you manage to bless that blade and
keep taking advantage look man yeah you
shook my hand but that was back then
we're not good fam I'm the fool cuz I
started to be cool with them but I got
schooled in the art of opportunism I
ain't the only one that walked away look
around everybody gone today you all
alone with your empty chest so bury the
bones with any regrets and keep those
skeletons piled in Stacks just drink
your medicine don't bite your glass I
tried to make a difference but the only
thing that