baby bus
hi i'm kiki
choose a tool and let's go fishing
swordfish
octopus
wow look at that
[Music]
puffer fish
kiki is wearing a wetsuit
[Music]
swordfish
it sounds amazing
[Music]
you did an amazing job
let's go fishing
[Music]
cart
lobster
it's jumping
[Music]
lobster
kissing gourami
it's so much fun
[Music]
the aquarium is frozen
help touch the screen
harp
you are so fast
[Music]
it is a tortoise shell
goldfish
it's super cute
[Music]
i'm so happy
kissing gourami it's so much fun
million fish
[Music]
harps
you are so fast
that was really awesome
[Music]
hi
i'm yumil
[Music]
japanese sea bream
fish
jellyfish
[Music]
look at those fishes
no a shark
[Music]
cuttlefish
[Applause]
[Music]
be careful with that bomb
flying fish
uh
[Applause]
[Music]
you are an awesome fisherman
hi i'm kiki
baby panda supermarket
[Music]
good morning
i have to do the grocery shopping today
kiki could you help me okay
give it to me
[Music]
we need to buy these things
chocolate
find the snacks you want to buy
you are so smart
chocolate
[Music]
corn
find all the fruits and vegetables that
you need
corn
wrong one
[Music]
you are so smart
backpack find all the dairy products
that you need to buy
wrong one
great
[Music]
you are so smart
cake
design your own cake
[Music]
you are so smart
fish
find the one you want
[Music]
great
cosmetics
eyeshadow
[Music]
it's not this one try again
you are so smart
done
let's pay
[Music]
oh
let's see what you have bought
backpack
cake
eye shadow
jelly
fish
fruit and vegetables
chocolate
napkins
[Music]
thank you very much
[Applause]
thank you
you did a great job
this is your prize
[Music]
good morning
i have to do the grocery shopping today
mew mew could you help me sure i want to
help
[Music]
we need to buy these things
pineapple
find all the fruits and vegetables that
you need
wrong one
[Music]
you are so smart
yay
jelly
find the snacks you want to buy
awesome
yay
[Music]
drinks
coffee
[Music]
great
yay
[Music]
find all the dairy products that you
need to buy
great
cake
design your own cake
[Music]
[Laughter]
you are so smart
yay
shoes
choose the right one
[Music]
too big
keep trying
hi beautiful lady
yay
fish
find the one you want
[Music]
you are so smart
yay
blush
[Music]
what do you need
it's not this one try again
[Music]
awesome
let's pay
[Music]
let's see what you have bought
coffee
shoes
jelly
fish
fruit and vegetables
cake
blush
[Music]
thank you very much
[Applause]
thank you
you did a great job
this is your prize
[Music]
baby panda supermarket
six seven eight nine ten wow
there are 10 goldfish
our show is about to start come and
watch the show everybody
[Music]
little five little six little goldfish
seven little eight little nine little
gold fish ten little fish
[Music]
one little two little three little
goldfish four little five little six
little fish seven little eight little
nine little goldfish
[Music]
one little two little three little fish
four little five little six little
goldfish seven little eight little nine
little gold fish ten little goldfish
weighing bare tails
[Music]
one little two little three little
goldfish four little five little six
little goldfish seven little eight
little nine little goldfish
[Music]
[Applause]
welcome to baby panda carnival
welcome to the carnival
welcome
thank you
welcome to the carnival we have fun
games and snacks
i want to play this
insert coins to play
[Music]
knock them down
awesome 10 more seconds to play
[Music]
keep going
you've earned so many coins
[Music]
cotton candy
i want a cotton candy
which flavor to pick
mango
what shape do i want
[Music]
i like this one
can't wait
[Music]
[Applause]
i want to play this
move the fish rod to fish
[Music]
keep going
awesome ten more seconds to play
[Music]
nice job
you've earned so many points
duck chase
[Music]
move the water hose and chase the ducks
into the cone
[Music]
awesome 10 more seconds to play
so
[Music]
oh what a pity
yeah this is your prize
last chance
[Music]
lucky you
we're here for more coins
[Music]
let's play the claw machine you can earn
more coins if you catch the right dog
[Music]
[Applause]
one
[Music]
[Applause]
you've earned so many coins
[Music]
i love popcorn
a popcorn costs 20 coins
what flavor should i pick
[Music]
smells so yummy
i like this one
can't wait
[Music]
i want it
dig in
[Music]
so yummy
welcome to baby panda carnival
you