today's how to build is on a dinosaur
cyborg
so this model is my entry in the rebrick
be the special contest
in this contest you have to take the
pieces from an existing lego set and use
them to build something else that's cool
and creative so there's a link in the
description where you can go log into
rebrick and then like my bookmark to
help me advance to the semi-finals of
this competition now let's get down to
building
first thing we're going to build is the
legs awesome dinosaur cyborg legs so
this is built using pieces from the set
5884 raptor chase but if you don't have
that set here's a look at the pieces i'm
using so you can go find them in your
own collection
so the colors i'm using here are
determined all by what's in the set but
if you want to use other colors based on
what you like go ahead
so i'm starting with a dark red two by
four
uh putting next to it a one by one
dark red plate a one by one tooth plate
and in front here a 1 by 2 transparent
dark orange
layering on top of that we're going to
take one of these 1 by 6 curvy slopes in
yellow
bring that together
a 1 by 3 downward regular slope
another 1 by 3 downward slope
2 by 2 plate
and then this dinosaur leg
right on top
and now you'll need the same pieces but
with a dinosaur leg going the other
direction
so this side is gonna be just the mirror
of the other side so start again with a
two by four plate
put a one by one plate next to that
one by one plate with a tooth next to
that
1 by 2 plate in the front here
connect it all with a 1 by 6 downward
curvy slope
do a 1 by 3 regular downward slope this
way
a 1 by 3 slope that way
2 by 2 plate here
and then a big dinosaur leg on top
these are the pieces you'll need for the
waste
take a 2 by 2 brick in light gray
and some 1 by 2 technic bricks put those
on the side
connect these with some 1 by 2
tiles in yellow
or you could use a 1 by 4 here
if you're not going just by the pieces
in the set
then we're going to use a 2x4 tile in
yellow
flipping it around to look up we're
going to use a 1x4 brick here this one
happens to be one of the bumpy ones
do another one of those and then i'm
going to use this uh 2x2 upward slope in
dark gray so that's what was in the set
and then connect another 2x4 yellow tile
on that so that's the waste piece
so to bring that all together we're
going to take the waist piece like so
and then connect each leg
and
put this to the side while we go build
the torso
these are the pieces you'll need for the
first part of the torso
this is a 1 by 6 plate in dark red 2 by
6 plate and dark gray another 1 by 6 and
dark red push those together
top them off with
two two by sixes and dark gray
on this end i'm going to take one of
these 1 by 2 with a 2 by 4
studs on the sides
put that here
do another one on this side
the middle here we're going to put a 4x4
round plate in yellow
and then put this
4x4 round brick in dark gray on top
these are the pieces you'll need for the
front of the torso
so starting with the thing we just
finished building let's take a 1 by 1
brick with a stud on one side in yellow
put it facing that way
and let's not break this while we're at
that
do another one on the other side flip it
around and do two more
right next to those
so we're looking like that then let's
put a 1x1 red
dark red plate
on each of those studs
okay one by one red plate on each of
those studs
then let's take one of these um
big plates that goes over the wheel of a
car
and stick it over here
just take another one and do it on the
other side you want the lip to be facing
forward
across the front we're going to do um
1 by 2
tiles in yellow here
grill plates and dark gray there
we're going to take two
1 by 1 round plates in transparent
orange stick them together
put one of these radar dishes that's 3x3
on top of that
then take a
transparent red one by one round tile
stick it on there and then stick that
right in the middle
these are pieces for one side of the
back of the dinobot
start with a 1 by 3 upward slope put a 1
by 2 plate on top of that
1 by 1 plate on top of that get another
1 by 3 upward slope
stick it up here
do a 1 by 2 with the grill plate hanging
down
connect all that with a 1 by 3 plate
and connect all that to your upward
slope over there with a 1 by 4 plate
get that same batch of pieces but with
some additional 1 by 4 plates
start again with that 1 by 3 upward
slope
put a 1 by 2 plate on it
1 by 1 plate on top of that
upward slope
this time do your grill plate and 1 by 2
off the opposite side
then do a 1 by 3 plate
and a 1 by 4 plate to connect it all
take your other side
and then connect them with some 1 by 4
plates
you're going to take that whole kit and
caboodle and stick it onto the back of
the torso you already built
these are the pieces you'll need for the
tail
i'm going to start with this raptor body
piece here
stick some technic pins in the side make
sure they're the black kind that stick
really well
put some 1 by 2 technic bricks on the
ends
then uh we're gonna put some one by one
bricks with studs in them facing that
way
do that on both sides
i'm gonna take some transparent orange 1
by 1 round plates
stick them in these empty holes
on the top here
dark gray grill plate
1 by 2 cheese graters
cheese grater slopes in yellow two of
those
now we're going to take the body we
built before
see these spots here that's where these
yellow bricks are going to connect
dark blue
the blue pieces will not connect to
anything
yet
uh and that is a
tail for our dinosaur
cyborg thingamajig
um
this
antenna piece you're just going to stick
on one side here
and then this big old black piece do the
same thing with
since we're feeling ambitious we're
going to go ahead and connect the legs
to the torso
so the best way to line this up is these
blues pieces in the back are going to
connect to the very back of that light
gray which means the very front of this
light gray is going to overhang onto
that yellow
your half-built uh cyborg dinosaur is
going to be a little unstable at this
point going to be
falling backwards a lot so if you want
you can rotate it forward and rotate the
tail all the way up and then it'll at
least stand on its own without falling
over
these are the pieces you'll need to
start building the top
for the sake of uh stability while
building i've moved my uh dinosaur body
here into a seated position so we're
going to take a 2 by 4 plate in dark red
connect that
like so
we're going to take a 2 by 2 computer
downward slope
one of these two by two by two downward
slopes
connect them together like so
and then stick them on the bottom of
that 2x4 red plate
now
you can see that the tail has a nice uh
top on how high it can go and it sort of
connects in a line down the back
with some computer stuff and uh
looks pretty cool so that's the back
flipping around to look at the front
we're going to take this 1 by 2 plate
with a handle on the side and red put it
next to that dark red plate
the same over here
connect these puppies together with some
1 by 4 plates in yellow
put in the center this 2 by two round
plate
dark gray
then we're going to take our raptor head
put a one by one stud in the bottom of
it
and stick it on
so now we just need some arms and some
cool shoulders
these are the pieces you'll need for the
shoulder pads now we're going to build
some shoulder pads that would make an
80s businesswoman proud
start with a 2x3 plate there and use
this weird two by two
sort of curvy
slopey thing
there then one of these two by two half
circle bricks
uh and then on the very tip here you're
gonna put a
dark gray cheese slope
and here you're going to put a little
1x1 tile with a gauge on it and a little
transparent red
and for the other shoulder plate you're
just going to do the same but reversed
and the only thing that's really
reversed here is going to be the
position of the gauge
and the
1 by one red tile thing
shoulder pants
the shoulder pads obviously go in the
shoulder area
shoulder pads
these are the pieces you'll need for the
left arm i'm going to start with another
one of these over the wheel thingies
uh you can tell i don't know things
about cars all right 1 by 2 plate with a
clip on the end over there
this is just going to go on there and
it's going to be you know able to freely
rotate back and forth
and then
more 1 by 2 plates with clippies over
here
and do two like so
then we're going to take one of these
tiny ladder pieces
stick it onto the clippies this is going
to force them apart a little bit
but they'll stay pretty much in place so
this is a
less stable connection because you can
see they're
straining up a little bit
uh then on here we're gonna put a bunch
of 1x2 clippie plates
to appear
and flip it upside down and put two up
here
i don't know why i just got a different
voice there
um
then take your 1 by 3 upward slopes
and put them on the end of all those
clippies
yeah look at this cool little arm so
yeah it's got sort of grabbing pincer
parts over here
uh
sort of big grabby claw
then you're gonna take your
cyborg dinosaur body
clip this to the red uh thing there
uh now to twist the arm you've gotta
sort of hold the
1 by 2 gray plate in place here to twist
the yellow thing
uh but it can get forward like that
so you can now uh
put this claw forward
since he's got something and now he'll
be able to stand up a little bit better
since he's got some weight forward
less back heavy
these are the pieces you'll need for the
right arm
so again let's start with one of these
over the wheel platy things
put it on top of a 1x2 plate with a clip
do another one on the other side and
another one over there
connect those to a
small ladder
um then take some of these robot arms
and want four of them
attach them to the top thing
flip it over
attach them to what's now the top
and then you're going to want to put
some of these uh big gray spikes in them
make some nice claws
that are scary and stuff
scary claws
scary claws scary claws why are you
now for the final touch we're going to
attach this over here
red handle sticking down
we're going to tilt the arm forward
here are the pieces you'll need to build
a little couch why are we building couch
just hold on and you'll find out
start with this big old six by six plate
because it was there
take this uh
i don't know even what you call this
this thing
put it there
then take a
1 by 4 brick with studs on the side
put it on top of some 1 by 4 plates
stick some
clear little
round 1 by 1 plates in the bottom
stick that over here
stick some 2 by four tiles on this
i'll stick this whole thing
in the back here
got a little couch
take uh one of the minifigs from the set
say this guy
give him a chicken wing
and then pose him on the couch like he's
enjoying a delicious chicken wing
delicious chicken wings
oh
what's that i'm too busy enjoying a
delicious chicken wing to pay attention
to that
thanks again for tuning in to this how
to build video please go vote at the
rebrick contest for my model and let me
know in the comments what models you
want to see me build in the future
thanks and keep on building
you can hear my dog playing with her
squeaky toy in the background
uh 1x2 plate up front here
hi sophie you need to play with your
squeaky toy
yeah squeaky toy
shoulder pads
now open the mouth or tear off the head
rather dinobot attacks