this Patriot system costs a whopping
$1.1 billion each so let's take a look
at how it's set up to fire the Patriot
system is actually a full battery
containing four separate units each
missile is self-contained in its own
transportable canister this heab crane
is attached to an m985 cargo truck which
carries these canisters around the crane
Maneuvers the canisters between the
cargo truck and the Patriot launcher
don't drop it now that costs more than
your mortgage once set up the masks on
this the AMG mobile antenni system are
raised this creates a network of
communication between different Patriot
batteries which is necessary to Shared
data from this the aent tpq 53 radar
which can not only detect incoming
attacks but also can scan the position
of enemy launchers out to 60 km the
systems are all connected together with
cables once set up the battery can be
operated from inside the anms q132
engagement control station which
controls the whole battery