[Music]
what's up everyone and welcome to the
club in today's video i'll be showing
you step by step on how to draw kobe
bryant now you get started in the center
of our page with the lower eyelid so on
the left side draw a curve going up
and then down on the inside let's leave
a gap in center and draw the same thing
over on the right so i'm going to line
up the bottom edge
curve up
and then out
now i tuck the eyes in behind the lower
eyelid so starting on the left side step
in draw a circle coming around to the
top
down
and then back in do the same thing on
the right
all the way up to the top of the eye
[Music]
around and then back in
we're gonna add a small highlight circle
on top left of each eye so up against
the edge just gonna draw a circle going
around and then back out
line this up on the right and do the
same thing
let's fill the eyes in black
[Music]
i'm going to move up and draw on the
eyebrows on top of the left eye i'm
going to curve up
and then in
line this up on the right and do the
same thing going out
and then down
now on the inside we've got a short line
going up
and we'll taper this out and then down
towards the outside
of the eyebrow
let's fill the eyebrows in black
[Music]
now move to the center and draw the tip
of the nose starting over on the left
we're going to curve down
and then back up on the right and step
up and draw a short curve in the
opposite direction of the bridge of the
nose
now we're gonna move down and draw the
top edge of the mouth starting over on
the left
curve down
and back up on the right now go back to
the left side and draw the bottom of the
mouth coming down
and then back up on the right side
[Music]
i'm going to add the teeth over the left
side we'll draw a short curve coming
down and then in
do the same thing on the right side now
we want to cross this like a t with a
straight line coming down
and then we'll fill the outside corners
in black
[Music]
we're going to move down again and draw
a short curve from left to right for the
lower lip
let's move out and draw the lower half
of the head in line with the bottom edge
of the eyelid we're going to step out
draw a half circle going down towards
the bottom underneath the mouth
and we'll pull that back up
on the right side
and then we'll draw the top of the head
starting back on the left side and bump
out the side of the head
go up and then in
around at the top
and down towards the right side
and pull that in
now let's add the ears from the top of
the cheek we're going to step up
curve up
round off the ear and then pull that in
towards the side of the head let's line
this up on the right and do the same
thing
and then back to the top of the cheek
i'm just going to draw a short curve
going up and then out
now let's add in the beard the top of
the nose on the left which step down
out around the corner of the mouth and
then down
do the same thing on the right side
now we're going to curve up and out
towards the top of the cheek
[Music]
that's why i have a small fold above
each eye starting up on the left just up
above the eye when you crimp up
and then down
do the same thing on the right
[Music]
now let's move down and draw the sides
of the body on the left side underneath
the head and curve out
and then down towards the hip
go to the right
and we'll do the same thing
i'm going to connect the hips with a
curve coming down
and then back up
let's add in the color in the center and
start with a point
we'll angle up and out towards the left
and then the right
let's add the number 24 to the inside of
the jersey so we'll start on the left
side on the outside of the tube and
crimp up
come down
and then across in an angle
let's go back to the top draw a short
line coming in
round up the top
and down and out towards the side
and come straight down towards the
bottom
straight across towards the inside
and go up
then we'll close out the top with a
straight line
let's move over and draw on the four i'm
gonna line this up along the top
and go down
come down inside with a straight line
and go back out
come all the way down towards the bottom
close off the bottom and go back up
let's go back to the top and come
straight out
i'm going to come down the side
and go out with a short line on top and
bottom
and close off the end let's move to the
inside so the short line going out
up
and then back down
let's go back to the center step down
and draw a curve going up and then down
from the lower torso you want to leave a
gap in the center go over towards the
left draw a straight line coming down
towards the bottom of the shorts
go to the right and do the same thing
now let's round out the bottom of the
shorts starting on the inside go down
and then up
and do the same thing on the right now
let's go back up to the hip and round
out the side of the leg coming out
and then down
and then we'll step in and just trace
that same curve
to the trim of the shorts
let's go back to the inside corner of
the shorts and step out and draw a
straight line coming down towards the
heel
on both sides
and then we'll round out the bottom of
the feet starting from the heel and
curve down and up towards the toe
and do the exact same thing on the right
let's go back to the left side and round
up the top of the foot so we're going to
curve up
and bend this down aiming towards the
heel
and we'll bend this back up towards the
inside of the leg
do the same thing on the right coming up
towards the top bending that down
curving that back up towards the inside
and then we're going to thicken up the
sole taking this curve and step up
and then just trace that across
from the outside corner of the shorts
we're going to step in you just draw a
curve going out and down from the top of
the foot
then we're going to add the tongue of
the shoe stepping back out
up
and then down almost like a half circle
on both sides
and then from the inside from down and
up for the edge of the socks
[Music]
let's add the toe cap from the top of
the foot we're going to curve in
and then down towards the sole
[Music]
let's move back up and draw on the arms
let's start with the arm on the left
let's start halfway down the side of the
body
and then down towards the wrist
and then from the wrist we're going to
draw the thumb draw a small half circle
coming in and back out
at the end of the thumb we draw a
bracket
let's go to the bottom of the thumb
curve down
and up around the bracket we're going to
add two more fingers
stepping down
down and up the second finger
now on the side when you curve the third
finger going out
round up the arm and pull that up
underneath the head
and then we're going to give them an
armband start from the inside of the
wrist
up
and then out
go all the way up to the top of the arm
on the inside curve up
and out
now we're going to draw him holding the
ball over on the right side so let's
start here we'll start with a circle
from the very top
work our way around to the bottom
and back up
towards the top
let's add the lines of the basketball
starting from the center at the very top
draw a straight line coming down
go the inside draw a straight line going
out
and then from the sides going to curve
in and then back out let's start with
the inside
and out
and do the opposite on the outside
now let's draw the top of the arm going
in behind the ball so we land at the top
angle down and out
go out with a straight line in behind
the ball
and then we draw the tip of the thumb
and the fingers to start the very top
draw a small half circle going up and
down
and move to the side
and draw three small half circles
[Music]
and we'll draw the bottom of the arm
starting from the inside of the
basketball curve down
and then up in behind the body and
that's pretty much it there's our
cartoon illustration of kobe bryant i
hope you enjoyed today's lesson make
sure you subscribe and send me your
requests in the comments below thanks
for watching and we'll see you again
soon