what's up everyone and welcome to the
club in today's video i'll show you step
by step on how to sketch a dragonfly
let's begin by building up the structure
of our drawing we move to a side grip
using the flat edge of our pencil let's
start from the very top and sketch out
an oval starting right in the middle
it's going to work out towards the left
down towards the bottom
and then back up along the right side
let's draw a smaller oval overlapping
the top starting right in the middle
going around
through the top
and then back up towards the center
and then from the bottom of our oval
we'll sketch a straight line coming all
the way down towards the bottom of our
page
from the bottom of the head we're going
to move out towards the side draw two
short lines coming out and down and then
going back over towards the left side
it's going to round out the body going
out
and then bending that in towards that
center line
let's add some thickness to the tail
from the bottom step over towards the
left sketch a straight line coming down
and do the same thing on the right side
i'm just going to curve this down and in
towards the bottom of that center line
and i'm going to place the wings on top
of the body and start from that center
line sketch a line going all the way out
toward the left to right about there
and then extend this out towards the
right
[Music]
let's sketch a small circle on the end
of the wing going all the way around
and then back up
[Music]
let's go to the bottom of our circle
curl the wing coming down
and then bending that up toward the
center line
and we'll go around and down towards the
right
[Music]
now i'm going to block out the second
set of wings starting from the center of
the wing draw a straight angle line
coming down and then out to right about
there
do the same thing on the right
coming down towards the same height
and then again we're going to draw the
same size circles on the end
let's go to the bottom of the circle
draw a straight line coming in
about halfway towards the body
it'll bend the wing coming in
and then up towards the bottom of that
body
let's go back to the base of the head
and drawn the first set of arms we're
going to angle this down and out for the
left and right side
angle this up and out
[Music]
let's go to the side of the head angle
up and out
[Music]
angle this up and in towards the top
now add a little hook on the ends of the
arm and go up
and bend that in
now let's add the last set of legs from
the top of the wing or step down on the
left side angle is down and out
[Music]
and then we'll curve this leg going out
and then down towards the end
now that we have our basic layout let's
go back and add a second level of detail
and refine the shape let's start with
the eyes start from the bottom of the
head we'll step up curve this down and
then up towards the left
and right side
and it'll add some shape to the top of
the wing starting from the center curve
this up
and then bend that down about halfway
and we'll add some sections across the
tail starting from the top start with a
straight line going across
leave a gap
just continue all the way down towards
the bottom
now we move to the tip of our pencil and
start adding some detail let's start
from the very top and trace out the top
of that oval going out towards the left
and then we do the same thing on the
right side
[Music]
just curve this down in towards the
center point
on top of the head
and it'll just thicken up that bottom
edge
[Music]
i'm going to go back and add a little
bit of detail on the inside
[Music]
and go in with the side edge of our
pencil and lightly shade that in
we'll also darken up the bottom edge i'm
just fading that out
[Music]
now we're just going to work our way
around the eyes
just flatten off the bottom with a
slight curve
and then we'll shade in the eyes
and we'll add a shadow across the bottom
so just darkening this up and then just
fading that up
[Music]
i'm also going to bring that shadow up
across the middle
and adding a light shadow across the top
and then two shaded spots in the center
of the eye
now from here we're just going to work
our way out towards the legs
adding some thickness
and then we'll darken those up
[Music]
and bend the top of the legs
and add that hook on the end
[Music]
um
adding a little bend
to the second set of legs across the
bottom
and draw on the top
darken up the legs starting from the
outside
and then just gradually fading that out
as you come in
[Music]
so
adding a little claw on the ends
[Music]
and some spikes along the inside of the
arm
[Music]
let's move back to the center of the
body and start adding some details
and working our way across the top of
the left wing
just round up the end
and we'll bend the wing down across the
side
[Music]
do
and add a thick ridge along the top of
the wing
and then just taper that out on the side
[Music]
and we'll continue to add that detail in
the middle
[Music]
foreign
and go back and add a light fur edge on
the side of the body going in behind the
wing
drawing these short lines going across
that seam
[Music]
and then adding a light shade across the
body
[Music]
and then using the tip or pencil to add
some texture
and draw the top edge of the bottom wing
starting with the outside
[Music]
do
again just adding a thick ridge along
the top
and just tapering that out
foreign
and continue to add that fur across the
side of the body
going across the wings
[Music]
and we'll lightly shave that in
um
[Music]
so
and we're going to work our way along
the side of the tail down towards the
bottom
again just adding a little bit more
shape
[Music]
and then we'll continue to add that
pattern inside the tail
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
um
so
[Music]
and go back and layer those bottom legs
in behind the edge of the wings
adding some thickness
and then darkening this up
tucking that in behind the body
and then we'll lightly trace out the
bottom of the length
and adding a light shade on the inside
now i'm going to add some patterns
inside the wing
start by separating out the wing with a
curve
[Music]
on the bottom
so
[Music]
and i'll continue to add these veins
inside the wing
just adding the layers as we go
[Music]
we'll go back and add a light shade
inside the wings
[Music]
my
so
now go back and just tighten up the
contrast in our drawing
then adding a shadow on the side of the
tail
[Music]
so
and finally we're just going to add a
drop shadow just underneath the body
starting with the legs
[Music]
now come down the left side of the tail
and down towards the bottom
adding that light shadow underneath the
wings
[Music]
um
so
[Music]
and as we get closer to the end of our
drawing we'll tighten up our shadows and
add a little bit more detail and that's
pretty much it there's a sketch
illustration of a dragonfly i hope you
enjoyed today's lesson if you did please
make sure you subscribe because i'm
posting new lessons every single day you
can also drop your request in the
comments below i want to thank you for
watching and i'll see you again soon