today's how to build is on a Lego
flower if you like this video here are
some other how to build videos you might
enjoy so this flower is from my
animation
metamorphosis which I created in
2010 but only uploaded to this channel
in the past week the color scheme I'm
using in that animation is very limited
it's just four colors black yellow red
and white so that's why this flower is
black red and yellow but as you can see
I've also built it in this other color
for this video green yellow and blue so
you can build this flower in whatever
colors suit you for your Lego flower
needs let's get building these are the
pieces you'll need to build the stem of
the flower so start off with two 2x4
bricks push those together connect them
with a 2X two brick and then do two more
2x2 bricks on top of
that then we're going to go with a 2x3
brick go offset one then do a stack of
three 2x two
bricks stick that on the other side then
go back to the center with another 2x3
brick another stack of three 2x2
bricks and then we're going to top the
whole thing off with a 2x4
brick these are the pieces you'll need
for the center of the top of the flower
to start off with you'll want a 2x6
brick if you have one of those or you
can substitute it with some 2x3 bricks
like I've done here then you're going to
put some 2x2 bricks around
that now to give some stability to this
we're going to connect it with a 2x8
brick going this
way and another one of those going that
way uh and then on each side here we're
going to do a 2x4 brick
that's going to be the center of our
flower
blossom uh now we're going to do in
yellow a 2X two 2 a 2x4 going the other
direction another 2x two then we're
going to take some 1X tws to fill this
out so one by tw's there and there and 1
by tw's Under This 2x4
here that's going to be the center of
our flower if you're feeling ambitious
you can go ahead and connect that to the
stem I'd suggest having the 2x4 brick go
across that 2x6 or 2x
3s these are the pieces you need for one
petal of the flower so for the flower
petal take two 2x6 bricks or this could
be four 2x3 bricks if you don't have 2X
sixes connect them with a 2x3 brick like
so then put a 2x4 brick on each side
going
down then down here we're going to do a
2X two brick and a 1x two brick now
we're going to build three more of those
and then at the top of our flower we're
going to take the petals and attach them
to the
edges
here so around the edge oh that petal
broke petals are a little fragile so be
careful just like a real
flower so this is what your flower
should look like now as a finished
flower and again you can use whatever
colors you'd like to build your flowers
to build a nice bouquet of Lego flowers
that are just to your liking thanks for
watching the video don't forget to like
this video subscribe to my channel and
leave comments telling me what you want
to see me build in the future if you
like this video here are some other how
to build videos you might
enjoy
[Music]
[Applause]
n