I'm going to surprise my siblings with
Magic by making a coin disappear I was
given a magic set filled with magic
tricks so I'm going to pick one that I
think will actually trick them I look
through each magic trick and they all
look really cool but I have to pick one
that I know I can do well or else I
won't be able to trick my siblings so I
decided to try the mysterious coin case
trick I practiced the magic trick until
I got the hang of it and then I added
extra Pizazz to my performance by adding
a magician's Top Hat wand and some
confidence but you're not really a
magician without an audience so I'm
going to see if I can perform magic and
trick my siblings you want me to make
the coin disappear
yeah Abra
boom what's the coin it's not in here
it's not in here you want me to make it
reappear yeah
yeah Abra cadabra
boom wo wo