what's going on guys and today I'm going
to be teaching you an incredibly amazing
and extremely easy card trick let's get
into it now check this out first I'll
have the deck shuffled by a spectator
there we go
and then I'll give the cards a quick cut
now next thing I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
have a prediction card selecting and of
course I'm gonna select the prediction
card myself so just going through I'm
gonna come over here and pick the six of
Hearts okay and we'll come back to the
six of Hearts in a second but the next
thing I need is for the spectator to
touch five cards as I go through the
deck so we're going through going
through we have one card selected two
card selected three card selected four
and five now of course I thought like I
said I'm a spectator here but I just
selected five cards at random okay now
let's just take these cards and I'll
leave them right on top now let me
explain the significance of my
prediction card now of course you can't
pick the six of hearts because it's here
and there's only one six of parts in the
deck but you can pick the soulmate of
the six of Hearts which is the six of
diamonds and similarly if you picked you
know if I pick the nine of Spades so me
for nine is paid to be in nine of clubs
so the card that I'm looking for you to
pick is a six of diamonds
okay now that being said let's get back
to the trick so we have five cards here
right five cards that you selected now
I'm just gonna give them a nice shuffle
like that nothing too crazy and now
generally at this point I've give the
cards to the spectator so let's just
pretend this hand is a spectator
I'm gonna have the spectator deal one
card and then put one card on the bottom
and keep on doing this until there's
only one card remaining in this hand so
deal one put one on the bottom deal one
put one on the bottom deal one put one
on the bottom and deal one now if this
trick work correctly
my prediction should match the same card
that you picked the six of diamonds now
this trick was originally performed by
Harry Lorayne and let's just get into
how it's done now of course I have the
card shuffle my spectator it really
doesn't matter how they shuffle the deck
or how they cut it whatever they want to
do as long as there are cards in the
deck worth it so now first thing I do
that you saw is I spread the cards out
and the reason I do this is two reasons
want to pick out my prediction card and
two to get a peek at the top the second
card from the top so I take a peek of a
second card from the top first in this
case we see that it's the five of Hearts
so now your prediction card is going to
be the five of diamonds so we go to the
deck we find the five of diamonds and I
place it to the side face-up and the
reason I don't explain the importance of
this yet is because I want to talk about
it while covering another move that I do
so for now I'll just put it over to the
side okay and at this point I like to
give the deck a false shuffle to retain
the second card from the top but have
the spectator think that the card was
shuffled you know the deck was shuffled
nicely there we go and of course
retaining that second card
now the next thing we need is that for
the spectator to pick five cards and it
really doesn't matter what cards they
pick we're just gonna go through the
deck and have them touch five cards so
let's say this one okay we're just gonna
have it protrude about half way but half
the card here and then next one also
have now the third card that we get - we
want to stick it out about two-thirds so
as you can see this card for trude's out
more than these two cars okay and I'll
get to why in a second so that's three
cards that's four and that's five now
the reason we have the third card here
protruding the most is because we're
gonna push the last two cards back into
the deck we're gonna push the last two
cards back into the deck okay and we're
gonna do it under the cover of the third
card so now as I square them up we have
these two cards here right
my finger my index finger is gonna come
here at the tip of these these two cards
right this is the third card right here
and these are the last two cards
so these cartridge cards are all lined
up it's gonna come here and now while
I'm talk while I start talking about
this five of diamonds I'm gonna push
these two cards in just like that and
under cover you would just seem you know
pretty normal and now I'm going to swear
up these cards out so the karcher like
this I'm gonna swerve them out they're
gonna pivot about my middle finger of
the hand that's holding the deck I'm
gonna pivot out like this you're just
gonna grab them and I'm gonna place them
on top so now I'm only placing three
cards on top but the spectator is gonna
think I'm placing five cards now to take
the attention off of you know doing this
move I talk about what prediction card I
chose and why I chose it
so you know if you want to know exactly
what I said you can of course we watch
the original performance
but you know talk about soulmates of the
cards and whatnot just so thanks so the
spectator knows that they're looking to
pick the final hearts okay so now once
that's covered you'll take the top five
card remember they only picked three of
these cards and you remembered this card
the second from the top so you're gonna
be also taking you know these two cards
so now the card that you wanted to pick
the five of hearts is on the bottom now
we're going to split this packet into
three and two okay and we're pretty much
gonna inter leave the cards like this so
the top card of the two packet is gonna
go in the middle of the first two cards
and the bottom card which is the five of
Hearts is gonna go between the bottom
two parts just like that and then we're
going to repeat this process one more
time so split it up into three and two
top card goes between the top to bottom
card goes between the bottom two and now
you can literally hand the spectator
these cards so I just you don't give it
to them
and they're gonna deal one card and put
one card underneath which isn't gonna
duck so deal duck deal duck deal and
tell them to repeat the process until
there's one card left in their hand and
now however however you want to build it
up build up to the reveal and just
slowly reveal the five of Hearts which
is the same as a card that you predicted
now I think this is an incredible car
trick and it has become you know one of
my go-to card tricks to perform and the
crazy part about it is I learned it two
days ago so like literally two days ago
and I performed it for you know a
handful of people and they were just
left puzzled about you know how I did it
what happened you know is the world
ending so things like that so they were
really surprised you know and you know
doing card tricks for the same people
for such a long time people don't get
surprised as much but they really like
the trick
and I highly encourage you to go out and
perform you know for your friends family
strangers at the mall if you know
whatever you want to do just one tip
that I want to add is you know when
you're you know pushing the carts in
just make sure to practice that in front
of a mirror maybe four or five times
because if the cars are not aligned
properly the person is gonna see you're
pushing in the card with your index
finger and you know after looking for it
if they're not looking for it and you
know you have them engaged in the
conversation that it's gonna be
completely fine but I still highly
encourage you to practice it maybe four
or five times and you'll definitely get
it down and thank you guys so much for
watching make sure to hit that like
button leave a comment down below of
your performances or reactions that you
got or you know things that you liked
about this trick and make sure to
subscribe if you haven't already and
I'll see you in the next video