Hey guys, this is Evan from EZ Origami! And today I'll be teaching you how to
fold one of my original origami designs
named Stella.
It's a very simple modular model and it
looks great when it's completed. This
model requires 8 square sheets of paper. Each unit is folded from one square and
I recommend using 3 inch squares to
fold the units. Using 3 inch squares
will result in a star about 4.25 inches wide. And I'm going to be
using larger paper with color on one
side and white on the other just to make
it a bit easier to follow along. And once
you've prepared your paper, then we're
going to start with our first square
with the white side up. And then we're
going to fold in half diagonally. So take
this bottom right corner and fold it up
to the top left corner. Align the corners
and the edges, then make your crease, and
then unfold. Then we're going to slightly
rotate the paper so that the crease you
just made is now held vertically. And now
we're going to fold over this top left
edge and align it with the crease that
we just made. So we're going to do that by
pulling this left corner over to the
right. Then we want to start at the top
of the model and work our way down until
the entire colored edge is aligned with
that crease just like this. Then you can
make your crease all the way across and
then you can turn the model over. And now we're going to fold up this bottom
corner by making a horizontal crease
that extends from this bottom right
corner here. So we're going to do that by
pulling up this bottom corner, and we
just want to continue pulling it up
until you notice this white horizontal
edge underneath. And we want our new
crease to align with that edge. But
before you make your crease, you also
want to make sure that the vertical
creases in the center of the model
align as well. Then you can make your
crease. And again we're going to fold
over this top left edge and align it
with this vertical crease. So we're going
to do that by pulling this left corner
over to the right. Then once again we
want to start at the top of the model
and work our way down until the entire
white edge is aligned with that crease.
And once everything is aligned, then you
can make your crease. And now we're going
to fold over this top layer along the
left edge of this white triangle
underneath. So we're going to do that by
starting in the bottom left corner and
we're just going to fold over the
colored flap like this. Then we want to
work our way up until the colored edge
is completely aligned with the white
edge of that triangle, and once both
edges are aligned then we're just going
to make our crease right along the
triangle's edge here. And then you can
unfold. And now we're going to make an
angle bisector.
And we're going to do that by taking the
bottom edge of this top flap here and
aligning it with the diagonal crease
that we just made. So we want to lift up
this top flap then we want to start at
the bottom left corner and work our way
up and over to the right
aligning the colored edge with that
crease. And once it's completely aligned,
then you can make your crease. And then
we want to fold up this colored flap
one more time along the crease
underneath. So we're just going to fold
this entire flap over to the left, just
like that along an existing crease and
once you have that then I want you to
remember this point here where this
colored corner intersects with this left
edge. Then we're going to turn the model
over. And now we're going to make a
diagonal crease that extends from the
reference point that I mentioned before.
So I've marked that point on the right
side of the model, and essentially it's
where this colored flap underneath ends
and aligns with the right edge of the
model. So what we want to do from here is make our crease pivot from that point. So
we're going to lift up the bottom right
corner of the model and we're going to
pull it over to the left. And as you're
doing this, I suggest making a small
pinch mark at that reference crease just
to make it easier to pivot this flap
along that point. Then the next step is
to align the corner that we're folding
over with this left edge here. So we're
going to do that by simply folding it
down like this, and you might have to
slightly adjust the paper to get it in
the correct position. And before you make
your crease, you also want to make sure
that this white edge is parallel with
the colored edge on the top of the model.
And the last step to make sure this flap
is in the correct position is to make
sure you have a 90 degree angle at the
bottom of the model here. The closer you
get to 90 degrees, the easier it'll be to
assemble the units. So once that flap is
completely aligned then you can make
your crease through all layers and your
model should look like this. If you turn
it over it should look like this on the
backside, and if you flip it over one
last time then this is one completed
unit. Now you must fold seven more. Once you've
folded all 8 units, you're going to
need 2 to start the assembly. Then look
at one and you'll notice that has a
large colored flap on the left side and
it also has a pocket underneath this
colored triangle here. Then again we're
going to take our second unit, and we
want to slightly rotate our first unit
like this. Then from here we want to
insert the right side of the second unit
inside of this colored pocket on the
first unit. Then we want to lift up both
units and we want to carefully bring
them together like this,
again making sure that the right side of
the second unit goes inside of the
colored pocket on the first unit. And
you'll want to slightly adjust the units
so that their colored flaps come to a
common point at the center of the model
here. You'll see that the white and
colored edges on both units will align
as well, and once you have this then you
can put both units back down. And from
here I want you to notice this colored
flap from the first unit that extends
past the left edge of the second unit. And all we want to do is lift up that
colored flap and we want to fold it over
to the right as far as it'll go. And your
crease should align with the left edge
of the second unit here. So just make
your crease through all layers, and now
you've connected the first two units. The
back side of the model should look like
this, then we're just going to flip it
back over, and now we're going to add a
third unit the same way. So once again
we're going to slightly rotate the two
units that we already connected. And from
here we want to insert the right side of
the third unit inside the colored pocket
here on the second unit. So we're going
to do that by lifting up all three units
and we want to slide the second and
third units together like this, again
inserting the right side of the third
unit inside of the second unit's pocket.
And you may need to slightly adjust the
units until their colored flaps come
to a common point at the center of the
model and until their white and
colored edges align as well. And once you
have that then you can put all three
units back down. Then again you'll notice
this colored flap from the second unit
that extends past the left edge of the
third unit, and all we want to do is lift
up that flap and fold it over to the
right as far as it'll go. So we're just going
to fold it over like this, and again your
crease should align with the left edge
of the second unit here. So just make
your crease through all layers, and now
you've connected the first three units. And now we're going to add a fourth unit
the same way. So again, slightly rotate
the three units that we already
connected, and we want to carefully slide
the fourth and third units together just
like we did before by inserting the
right side of the fourth unit inside of
the colored pocket on the third unit. Again, you may have to slightly adjust
them so that their colored flaps align
at the center of the model and until the
colored and white edges align on top as
well. Then you can put all four units
back down, and again you'll notice the
colored flap from the third unit
extending past the right edge of the
fourth unit. So what we want to do is
lift up that flap and fold it over to
the right as far as it'll go. And crease
sharply through all layers. And once you
have this, then you've connected four
units. And now we're going to add the
remaining four units the same way.
And as you continue adding more units
you'll start to see that they'll overlap
with the first one. And you just want to
continue adding units on top of the
other layers because it makes it a
little bit easier to lock them together.
And once you've added the last unit, then we're going to slightly rotate the model.
And then to connect the first and last
units together, we need to pull the first
unit out on top. And we're going to do
that by lifting up the model and then we
carefully want to rearrange the layers
so that this large flap from the last
unit is now held on the bottom of the
model. So we're carefully going to grab
those layers and at the same time we
want to pull the first unit out on top.
So we're just going to carefully
rearrange the layers like this, and once
the first unit is on top, it should look
something like this. Then just like we
did with all the other units, we want to
insert the right side of the first unit
inside of the colored pocket on the last
unit. So you'll see that the colored
pocket is slightly hidden underneath, so
we're just going to have to bring the
first unit behind like this. So just
slide the right side of the first unit
inside of that colored pocket just like
we did on the other units, so now the
front side of the model is symmetrical. Then we're going to turn the model over,
and just like we did with all the other
units, we need to lock the first and last
units together. So we're simply going to
mountain fold this flap along the
colored edge of the first unit here. So
you just want to take that flap and wrap
it around the colored edge of the first
unit just like we did on all the other
units. And your new crease should aligned with this colored edge on the first unit.
You'll now see that the backside of the
model is symmetrical, and if you turn it
over one last time, then your origami
Stella is complete. I hope you've enjoyed
this video tutorial on how to fold my
origami Stella. Feel free to upload
photos of your completed star to the
YouTube Gallery on my website to be
featured here in my next video, or simply
upload your photos to Instagram with the
hashtag #ezorigami to be featured here
as well. Diagrams for this model along
with a couple neat variations can be
found on my website. Also, be sure to
check out my Etsy shop for EZ Origami t-shirts and some of my most recent
works. I'll link to that in the video
description as well. And if you liked this
video, please give it a thumbs up or
leave a comment below. I'd love to hear
what you think. And of course, subscribe
to my channel and hit the notification
bell for more videos like this. Thank you
for watching and I'll see you in the
next video!