all right guys we're at Shot Show 2025
we're here at the BNT Booth I am with
Nate he's going to tell us a little bit
about what's coming out in
2025 pleasure to have you guys thanks
for coming we have a smorgus board of
things obviously and it's crazy busy
here on day one pleasure to make time
for you guys though thanks for coming so
we are releasing almost a dozen new
things this year this is a big step for
us and there's a lot going on so we're
just going to touch the tip of the
iceberg if you're interested more
definitely come back to the channel
we'll be happy to do more with you guys
first off we have promised this gun for
almost 3 years and we're finally coming
through on it that's awesome this is the
SPC 223 so it is a 12.1 in cold Hammer
Forge Barrel adjustable gas system
you've got qds built into the handguard
this is our new assaulter muzzle device
it is a neutral timing on the top so
whether you're righty or Lefty you're
still going to be able to get a little
bit of muzzle compensation out of that
it comes with our lower which is
interchangeable across all of our 223
platforms this is our new pistol grip I
saw it for the first time on Sunday I
didn't even know existed till then you
look at it and it looks kind of Blocky
it is remarkably comfortable to hold in
your hand do you mind if I hold it yeah
absolutely how's that feel it's
different I like it though more vertical
alignment not quite as angled so back so
far but even for hands it's not bad it
looks funky but it's really comfortable
and then the last piece is now on this
gun we have a six P or excuse me a six
position receiver extension and you'll
be able to use your normal AR butt stops
it still retains our hydraulic buffer
system though so from a recoil stand
standpoint it feels like a dream we had
these arranged day yesterday and put
thousands of rounds through them and
consistently what people told me is it
feels like shooting a DI AR instead of a
piston gun which is a very high
compliment yeah tea charging handle over
the US commercial Market normally our
apcs have charging handles up front like
a European design this will feel a
little more comfortable for the US
market yeah for sure next up oh this
baby so we've been promising this for a
little bit and I am so happy it's
finally here this is our spr 86 so we go
from something that you could absolutely
use in competition General usage to a
highly specialized fire oh yeah so this
gun is not very heavy oh yeah I was
expecting that to be way heavier so that
is a modular titanium suppressor on the
end of it chambered an 86 blackout it
has a timy single stage trigger in it so
it's very comfortable very light also a
fantastic trigger the whole thing folds
and and the suppressor reflexes all the
way over the barrel so this entire gun
including the suppressor comes as a kit
the optic separate go figure right we'll
get that off here in a second that's the
gun wow so you can literally put that in
the bag that it comes with pull it out
of the bag screw the suppressor on even
comes with a bipod toss in a MAG of 86
blackout subs and you have a very quiet
beautiful package yeah the last thing
though and I'm going to be very careful
putting this back down is is our new
print xh suppressors so I am not a huge
fan of using the term revolutionary but
this is about as close as I've seen the
suppressor Market to date so one of the
problems with titanium suppressors and
obviously the automotive industry you
get this as well titanium heats up
quickly cools quickly but it's not very
durable under heat and specifically in
suppressors titanium suppressors tend to
spark so if you shoot them in low light
no light you get this Roman Candle
effect out of the front of them some of
them burnish over time like ours do some
don't we really wanted to solve that
problem though so the blast baffle
inside of this is 718 Inc canel as well
as stainless steel so now the sparking
issue that people run into is gone the
heat erosion issue that you find with
titanium is also gone SpaceX uses 718
Incan L on their uh cones forcing cones
for Rockets because of its durability
we're using the same material for the
same reason but the whole thing still
titanium as far as the body and it's
reduced back pressure so you get about a
1.9 increase or 1.9% increased Bolt
speed when using this suppressor so
normally when you suppress a firearm you
have to change the gun to suppress it
whether it's changing the gas system a
different buffer different bolt carrier
this one
uh-uh hold
that wow that's our Surefire Rotex
device in the end of it it is Hub
compatible so you can buy that
suppressor and no matter what other
mounting systems you have rearin plan B
hux Works whomever that can will work
we're also now doing hubs for rearin
Plan B and hux works from us directly
then there's also the SC variant so this
was Full Auto rated no barrel length
restrictions this one I recommend using
it on 11.5 in or longer it's best than
like a 139 145 but it's shorter
right also Ultra lightweight yeah we've
also got a new direct thread adapter
that comes with it to give you an idea
from a weight perspective how much do
you think this weighs without that
adapter oh I'm so bad at guessing the
that's the fun part I don't know it's
about 10 o oh really without the adapter
just the bear can so these are
incredibly lightweight incredibly
durable and with that new Inc canel
blast baffle this is the next generation
of suppressors if I am putting a
suppressor on a comp rifle something
like this yeah this you it's actually
becoming viable to do so you don't need
a muzzle break anymore yeah so maybe who
knows these might show up in TCT IAL
games we'll see I know it guy and before
we go we got one more thing he's going
to pull out when you say it like that
yeah absolutely so this is a Walther PPK
in 32 ACP the James Bond gun with our
new 3D printed 32 Caliber suppressor so
if you really want to get your James
Bond gun on we absolutely have the gun
to do it as well as the brand new
suppressor it is remarkably quiet for
its size it might even be best in class
so as far as a unique firearm and a
unique suppressor there's not much else
you're going to see at the show that's
quite like that hey guys we're at Shot
Show 2025 we are here at the aimo booth
I'm here with John he's going to talk a
little bit about what's coming out in
2025 all well this year we're bringing
out a collaboration we've done with
Glock this is the new Kaa site and Kaa
is a system that it's incorporated into
a new cut and a new site the cut we're
referring to is the a cut and what
you're going to see with the a cut is
the site's going to cam into from the
front and get bolted in by these two
screws in the rear that also contain the
rear sight what that does it cuts down
on any sort of up flip from The Recoil
of the pistol cuz we're locked into the
frame instead of being locked in by
threading and screws right another
really great thing about the a cut is
how low it gets and what that does it
allows us to actually co-witness the
iron sights through the optic while
using Factory height iron sights and not
having to go to super tall suppressor
height sights
2032 battery in a tray in the side here
with a 5year battery
life just a phenomenal sight picture uh
this year glock's going to release it in
the 43x the 48 the 19 the 45 and the 47
variants yeah I haven't even if I could
hold that I haven't even held that oh it
fits beautifully on the single stack
guns and it fits great on the double
column guns too
one of the things that we did is if you
look at earlier Generations the acro M5
all the series
sites there's an inner tube inside of
the body that actually moves to adjust
for the zero it's connected to the front
lens going all the way back to the
LED so this does have what you see
inside there is a tube inside of a tube
well with the COA instead of moving the
tube in the lens we're just moving the
LED so there's a lot less material
inside the body of the site now which
increases the overall viewing window and
the size of the port to for the site
picture guys so we are here at Shot Show
2025 at The hux Works Booth I'm here
with Porter he's going to talk a little
bit about what he's excited for for 2025
awesome thank you so we launched two new
cans today we have our flow 9k tie and
then our flow range 36 so this is going
to be a super good can for any of the
pcc's pistol anything like that it's 4.8
o and then for our flow range 36 it's
actually one of the best entrylevel cans
on the market you're going to be
anything from 22 to 338 lauck this can
can do so rifle pistol anything in
between this is going to be your go-to
can and that one's coming in at 8.4 o
awesome y so what's the price about the
price range for these this is on the map
on this is $6.79 and the map on on this
is $979 okay so a sub th000 can uh that
will work on
everything and are these available now
these are these started shipping earlier
this week these ones will be available
they ship in about two weeks uh so
dealers and Distributors will have them
here shortly aesome so we're known as
the innovators of flow through
technology a lot of companies have tried
to chase us in that and they're a little
late to the game um but yeah so we just
the flowr is our main thing get all that
toxic gas out of your face and it also
helps heal the hurt not hurt the weapon
system cuz normally on a suppressed
rifle you're seeing about 20 to 30%
increase in Bolt velocity with ours it's
anywhere from 0 to 2% so it's longer uh
use of the weapon system all that tosic
gas out of your face and there's just a
lot of good
benefits hey guys we are here at Shot
Show 2025 I'm at the lgo booth with Ian
he's going be talking about what they
have and what they're coming out with in
2025 hi guys Ian from L arms USA here
what I have in my hands is the alien
Remis uh if you guys aren't familiar
with the alien give you a real quick
rundown on who we are what the gun is so
go a and lock that slide back for you
guys as you can tell very very low Bora
axis perfectly in line with my index
finger what that means is when I'm
ridling off shots down range the gun is
not trying to flip out over the top my
hand it's just coming straight
back secondarily also very very uh great
feature of the alien stationary optic
comes standard on the uh on the gun when
you're running the pistol the optic
itself stays stationary
outside of that the pistol itself is a
gas delayed blowback handgun and what
that means for you the shooter is just
slightly softer recoil and much much
quicker cycling times so that's the gun
itself what's new for 2025 like I said
is the Remis here this as you guys can
tell is a compact variant of our aliens
is a 4-in barrel model as opposed to our
standard 5-in Barrel model outside of
just that shorter Barrel what we do have
working on this guy is a nice thumb
safety four carry safety and my personal
favorite like I said brand new for 25 is
this push to Rack system so if you guys
are familiar with our retro lineup or
our reciprocating optic guns you'll know
that it's very nice to be able to rack
off of that optic that being said you
lose the follow-up shot time of the
stationary optic we thought why don't we
combine the two into one that gives us
our push TOA system so you depress that
gold lever right there pull back let fly
you're hot now when you're firing it's
going to stay stationary and then when
you're back to normal say you're doing a
slide loock reload no worries push back
just like that guys that's us that's
what we have new for 2025 come check us
out if you're here 7143 but other than
that it's great talking to you hey guys
I'm here at Shot Show 2025 I'm at the
primary arms Booth with Alex he's going
to talk about what's new for 2025 so
we're super excited thank you for coming
to our booth uh we're super excited for
2025 to launch our brand new htx one
that's the new hotness we have here that
is our first iteration of an enclosed
made in USA reflex optic so super cool
we'll probably do a deep dive a little
bit later on the product if you guys
want um but it's the first product that
out of the box can fit up to 90% of all
Optics cut Footprints uh right out of
the box so it's super cool uh we have a
couple other objects uh we've got our
long range plx Scopes uh we've got some
new illumination technology in our one8
Scopes uh and we have a new line that
we're releasing our CLX line it is
probably one of the most
affordable um Optics line uh in the
industry today and we've got microprisms
in that line we've got red dots in that
line so super cool uh We've also got
some new uh lpvo some new prescriptions
a new 2 to2 which is super cool um so
we're super excited to have that out for
2025 so what do we have here so this is
brand new for 2025 this is a new
iteration of our plx line we're
introducing some new long range Scopes
so this one's really cool this is
actually my personal favorite uh coming
out for 2025 it's our plx 2 1/2 to 20x
48 and what's really cool about this it
is a medium to long range scope uh this
thing can go 1,000 yards all day long
and further which is super cool uh it's
all made in Japan part of our plx line
Japanese glass we've got this huge 48 mm
front bezel lets all the light in super
bright illumination Steel on steel
turrets with easy stop and for those of
you that don't know what that is you can
take the turret off uh you can set where
your zero is you can lock it in put the
turret back on and now you have a fully
functioning zero stop turret which is
super cool um aside from it it is super
durable so everything every component is
steel um and awesome for 2025 so that is
the plx 2 1/2 to 20 uh by 48 also we
have the big brother of this scope and
which is this guy right here so same
thing as I just described just in a
bigger prescription this is our 4 1/2 uh
to 36 and they each come with three new
reticle variants we've got our mbased
reticles our Deca G2 our acss Athena uh
and our uh ACS up Neptune so come check
us out hey guys so we're at Shot Show
2025 I'm here at the HK Booth I'm with
Angela she's going to talk a little bit
about what's coming out in
2025 hey guys I wanted to show you what
we have new um this is the cc9 which
this is the first americanmade HK and
it's also the smallest HK um handgun
that's ever been made and there's a lot
of really cool features about this gun
um it's taken us a little time to come
and Market but you'll understand why so
right now here is you're going to have
your small and medium uh I'm sorry small
and large back straps so what this is
going to do it's going to help the shoot
shooter have a um a really good length
of a trigger pull right here and if you
actually measure the trigger pull on
this it is the same distance as the
vp9 uh full size so a lot of people with
um familiar with the VPS will really
appreciate that um we do have
ambidextrous uh magazine release and
slide release here and then the magazine
it comes with a 12 plus one and a 10
plus one that actually fits really good
that feels nice interesting and that's
the small um back strap on that one yeah
I don't typically like like small guns
but this is this feels nice comfortable
and it shoots like a full size too so
that's the one nice thing about the cc9
and we're also offering it with um an
Optics equipped so um you can buy it in
a package with the Optics and it'll come
with a hollison um optic on it looks
like the MSRP is $6.99 mhm yep $66.99
and this is already out you said yes
okay yeah so right now um we're we're
shipping it out um a little hard to find
right now but I'm just telling everyone
be patient you know just the Demand
right now is pretty high for them
everybody's wanting to get their hands
on one so down here we're showing our
vp9 a ones so it's going to come in a
full size which is the F and then um the
K which is our Compact and the gentleman
there has that in his hands um there's
there's a lot of new features on this
one of my favorite features is the um
the back straps it now comes with small
medium a extended medium and extended
large and like we talked about with the
cc9 what that's going to do here is
going to help with the length of the
trigger pull so you're going to be able
to shoot this um way better than any of
the other Sher fires that you're going
to see on the market and another feature
with this is you're going to have um a
flared magazine roll well um the F comes
with a 17 round and a 20 round magazine
so you're going to have a lot of options
there you're going to have deeper
cations there on the slid so you're
going to be able to get a better
grip and again you're going to have
ambidextrous um releases on that as well
so all the upgrades on the vp9 A1 I'm
here at the HK Booth I'm with John he's
going to be talking about the mr556 A4
and John let first let's tell us a a
little bit about your background yeah
sure so hello everyone my name is John
rasmason I'm one of the factory team
shooters for HK uh my background in this
uh I've been involved in competitive
shooting for close to 30 years now
started off in USPSA uh currently a law
enforcement officer I've been a cop for
about 25 going on 25 years now um I'm a
competitive shooter I'm also an
instructor with my agency most of the
agency armor so I'm just kind of a gun
guy uh in nature so I've been around the
sport a long time and and just been
involved with guns for a long time been
part of HK now for about 10 years on
their shooting Team all right and now
magically we have an mr556 A4 in my
hands the magic of the internet uh so
talking about the mr556 A4 um kind of
our Focus here is speaking with Alyssa
because she's been involved in tactical
games and I've been involved in
competitive shooting uh looking at the
mr556 A4 with regards to competitive
shooting so what makes this thing a good
rifle what are we looking for in a
competitive shooting rifle uh so Alysa
what do you look for in a competitive
rifle well for I have to say really for
tactical games I need to be have
something that's good for longer
distance and shorter distance not
necessarily a long range gun not
necessarily short range so kind of
something that's kind of all around good
yeah so mr556 A4 perfect for that you
know most people in competitive shooting
16-inch carbing is about you know the
the general thing that's you run gives
you enough barrel length to get you out
to 5 or 600 yards if you need a long
shot like that but it's short enough
that you can run it in like a CQB kind
of a stage without any kind of an issue
so the Mr 556 16 and 1 12 in Barrel
works perfectly for that um you know we
need the accuracy to get out to a
roughly 2 or 3 minute of angle Target
out there at 500 y uh and this thing is
an is a minute of angle capable rifle
from the factory these all leave the
factory as a minute of angle capable
rifle so super accurate um easily
capable of the kind of accuracy that
we're looking for uh in a competitive
shooting match what else what else do
you need in a competitive rifle another
thing it's weight I don't want it too
heavy cuz I'll be carrying that around
yeah absolutely so all the matches that
we shoot you shoot tactical games I do a
lot of uh like running gun matches where
you know you be right in for you know 7
8 9 miles sometimes in some of those
matches so weight really matters uh the
M 556 A4 uses like a medium profile
Barrel so it's it's a heavy enough
profile to give you the accuracy that
you need but it's not so heavy that's
going to bog you down so the overall
rifle still a really lightweight package
uh and the handguard designed by HK USA
nice and slim so you can get a good grip
on the gun uh so super important yeah
weight weight is absolutely eff
especially in a tactical game situation
or the running of matches that I do uh
the Ambi features is always nice being
able to charge from either side uh
dropping the bolt Magazine from both
sides all that stuff very important so
um mr556 uses full Ambi features both
sides amb features yeah yeah great you
know there's a lot of times you know a
lot of the matches I'm sure tactically
in the same way um match directors for
the running gun Style Match is a real
big on making you shoot from the weak
side so so having Ambi features on the
gun is very important when you
transition to that weak side and you
still have to manipulate safety you
still got to drop a magazine uh lock the
bolt to the rear all those things so you
got to make sure you train with it yeah
AB absolutely 100% yeah same thing super
reliable tunable gas system that's super
that that's critical on a competition
gun is it's got to work uh and this is
the most reliable rifle I've ever shot
so yeah mr556 fits all of that bill so
yeah perfect for what I do probably
perfect for what you do too so you shoot
this guun I do so I shoot this gun in
competition uh I configure it
differently based on the match that I'm
doing based on the distances that I'm
using really some of the matches like
out west if I'm shoot a match in Texas
where there's a lot of 5 600 yard shots
it'll have a little bit larger magnified
optic on it if it's an East Coast match
where you know the distances we use not
quite as far CU most of the ranges don't
have that kind of distance I put like a
low power variable out there like a one
to six a razor something like that on it
uh just cuz I don't need that much
magnification and then you know maybe
it's a CQB match where nothing that you
shoots over 50 yards and it gets a red
dot put on it but it's super easy to
reconfigure the rifle in any way that I
want throw light on it if I need it so
yeah all that says very important M
loocks on all the rails to make sure
that you can put whatever accessory you
want on it so yeah yeah awesome so
what's your next match what are you
shoot next oh it's probably going to be
tactical games oh here in Nevada
actually is it really what is it April I
think it is okay I think I'll have to
check on that but yeah so it's coming up
in a few months fantastic well best of
luck thank you what's up guys we're here
at Shot Show 2025 I'm at the Sig boo
with Chris he's going to
explain okay so I guess we'll start off
with the suppressor since we're over
here already um for those that are
unfamiliar Sig sour is uh pretty well
known in the industry um specifically
we've had a lot of military successes a
lot of contracts that we won um the way
the big one being um really replacing
all the m4s and 249 saws with the xm7
and the XM 250 program uh the NG program
and the big thing uh was that that
contract included suppressors um so this
is the first time that the Army
widescale adopted suppressors um lot of
lot of reasons for that allows you to
commun communicate better um less issues
with hearing damage longterm um and this
is something that we actually kind of
pioneered um we had developed other
previous uh suppressors for Socom um and
we kind of developed a high flow
suppressor which is starting to become
more popular in the industry um we we
were one of the first to really get uh
the military to adopt it um we kind of
worked jointly with a lot of those units
um to kind of develop some very Cutting
Edge Products um so we sell all of these
products um to the military but as with
six hour we want to make sure that we're
providing that ex excellent products to
the commercial Market as well so um we
do have variety of different calibers
5.56 300 Blackout 762 and then also the
68 high pressure round um that is being
used by the US Army we use uh kind of
like we were some of the first to
Pioneer the the dmls process which is
essentially like a fancy way to 3D print
but it's printing uh with metal so
titanium and in canel are the two
materials that we use
um and really what that printing allows
us to do is have kind of crazy
geometries on the inside so uh in the
past um most suppressors for the last
like 100 years have been very uh kind of
like v-shaped uh baffles that's what's
on the inside um but with the the 3D
printing um and with Advanced Computer
Software we're able to model all sorts
of stuff we're able to rapidly prototype
so we're able to like very quickly kind
of hone in on like what the optimal
suppressor is for different calibers
um and we kind of have like three things
that we're looking at we're looking at
flash suppression we're looking at sound
suppression and then the toxic fume is
kind of uh and the low back pressure
thing is something that is the
relatively new uh thing that the the
industry is all kind of moving towards
um but this is something that we were
kind of some of the first to develop
with the US military um and with their
input uh to kind of really develop these
products yeah so the gun itself is is
obviously like really cool um we had
like an entire Council of of of women at
our company um because I think there was
a lot of feedback that we had from the
industry like there are a lot of
companies in the past that were trying
to like sell pink J frames and all that
stuff and I think you know internally a
lot of a lot of us saw that like that's
not exactly what women want so like we
had a whole lot of input trying to
develop it based on what what you know
those customers were looking for um so
we wanted to make sure that like you
know it was aesthetic it wasn't tacky so
uh we obviously have just touches of
color um but there's also functional
things that we wanted to put in to make
it more pleasant to shoot but also still
uh very concealable so some things
you'll notice um is that grip so that's
a rose pattern grip but that actually is
laser etched in that gives you good
traction while not being so aggressive
that it's like if you're carrying inside
the waistband that it's going to
completely chew up your skin definitely
seen But if you grip on there it's it
gives plenty of traction another thing
that we kind of developed in the last
couple of years if you flip this side
we have a slide integrated compensator
so this is something that we patented um
it's kind of cool so compensators have
been around for a while but there's been
a lot of downsides to compensators um
some of them you have to basically take
off the compensator completely off if
you want to clean it this one
disassembles just like an ordinary
pistol um another side benefit is that
this isn't as ammo sensitive so some
other bar mounted compensators you have
to fiddle with the Springs you have to
fiddle with the ammo and even then it's
still kind of borderline reliability
this is just as reliable as any other
Striker Fired you know non-compensated
pistol so this is something that we kind
of custom tuned this is the 9 mil
variant we also have a 380 variant
that's a little bit smaller with the
smaller caliber recoils less so it kind
of gives people the option is like hey
if I want something Ultra small it's
still in a manageable caliber or if I
want something that's a little bit you
know 9 mil kind of the standard I would
say now with modern pistols you still
have some feature sets that give you um
you know plenty of control in such a
small concealable package so this one's
12 round flush fit we do have other
magazines that go all the way up to 21
um for the 365 and then for the 380 it's
10 mil uh sorry 10 Rounds
flush we also have uh an optic so we
have variety of uh accessories that are
uh Rose accented to kind of match it um
but really the biggest thing for the
rose it's an entire program so Lena
melik I think plenty of people have have
heard of her fantastic shooter um and
really this was a a program that she
wanted to spearhead to to try and get
more women more knowledgeable and
comfortable with concealed carrying and
and learning how to shoot and making it
fun so when you buy the gun it actually
comes with a variety of different
accessories that is bundled with a gun
so you get the pistol it comes with a a
matching VTech case so you have a safe
way to store the firearm if it's your
first gun you know a lot of people don't
have a giant you know gun safe or
whatever so you have a way to you know
safely carried in your nightstand or
whatever um it also comes with a QR code
um that allows you to essentially have
Lena kind of give you some of the
initial steps in you know firearms
training so weapon safety you know
handling all this stuff so it kind of
gets them a nice easy way to kind of
Step Into You know having firearms for
the first time yes exactly and that's
really what we wanted to design is that
kind of take away a lot of the you know
uncertainty of like diving into a new
unknown kind of hobby um so that's what
we Tred to do is make it really uh easy
for people to get into it for the first
time and what's the price so uh it it'll
uh depend on the the N uh 9 mil versus
380 and then red dots so it kind of
varies um but the non uh Red Dot
equipped ones will be
around uh $950 is doll free price um the
380 will be a little bit cheaper if you
put it with a red dot it'll be a little
bit more expensive so it kind of varies
depending on what packages you decide to
go with so we have a variety of options
so if people want to do a Red Dot from
the factory non install we we have a
variety of those different options so
non compensated options as the the 380
is non-compensated but the 9 mil is
compensated mainly like we tried to we
wanted to kind of tame that recoil for
you know small guns tend to be very
Snappy so we wanted to kind of keep it
so that it was controllable okay so what
do we have here uh we have a variety of
uh different Sig pistols um a couple
different families we've got some 1911s
some 320s some uh 365's as well as some
226s um so I guess on the competition
side it kind of depends like there's we
have a lot of guns that are you know
very very uh you know specifically
designed for certain types of
competition um we have some that for for
USPSA uh some for IDPA pssl there's so
many uh Firearms disciplines out there
um the 226 x5s are are probably my
favorite trigger um they've got
three-way adjustable triggers they're
I've been handing them to people all day
and they're like
very surprised when they pull the
trigger it's definitely something that's
very cool um which one sorry which one
was that so there's actually two
variants that we have we have the X5
Legion and then we have the X5 Reserve
um so this one's a little bit more of a
little more blingy um that one's kind of
a limited edition uh uh pistol but some
similarities some differences um but
those are two uh compensated kind of
similar to what we saw earli on the 365
but now on a a much larger firearm um
and it's got a lot of kind of cool cool
nice features like gas pedals and and uh
you know uh single action only triggers
that just make make it very easy to
shoot very fast um another one that's
that's really purpose built for for
shooting competitions is our 3 320 X5
sxg the sxg stands for steel x grip so
this is uh if you want to hold on to
this it's a very heavy pistol yeah it's
also got um some very aggressive G10
grips makes you get have really really
great action know if you got sweaty
hands if it's ring it doesn't really
matter that gun's going to stick in your
hand and you're going to help help you
mitigate that recoil yeah this one's got
some really nice fiber optic sights but
it also still allows you to be able to
mount a red dot so good for production
or carry Optics um all sorts of kind of
different shooting disciplines this
one's got a 5-in full Barrel as well as
the ability to swap out Springs so if
you're running uh you know some ball
ammo versus your match ammo you can kind
of tune that so that it's uh you know
it's really sprung perfectly for
whatever ammo uh that you're just
sending to shoot but got a whole variety
of different stuff depending on like
what you're looking to you know shoot
competitions with um I've shot this gun
um in the tackle games um where you know
some competitions uh will bump you up
into a different division with a
compensator so it all kind of depends on
on what competition you're deciding to
shoot so you'll obviously have to look
in kind of the rule book of what the
divisions are but so for something like
tactical games do you think that would
be the best option um this is this is
something that I liked um I kind of took
this slide off and actually put on a
polymer grip um but that's kind of
personal preference um but honestly I
think if you were just to have one gun I
think this is probably the best option
for the tassel games Okay um but I think
that's uh yeah there's a lot of
competition so it's kind of like yeah
there's there's there's so many answers
and there's no really right or wrong
answer it's just kind of depends on what
you want to do for sure uh because of
all those feature sets like they help me
toate recoil some really good G10 grips
um it's a good competition gun as long
as it's allowed in that
competition you feel a trigger on it oh
not not this one
yeah so that's our Legion trigger which
is going to be lighter um than the
standard 320 triggers
the cool thing about the G10 grips is
that if it's too aggressive or not
aggressive enough it's super easy to
swap out grips so it's the same pattern
you can put these grips on that or vice
versa um there's all sorts of different
companies that make grass grips and
aluminum grips and all sorts of
different patterns and colors so you can
kind of customize them super
easily all right so we're going to be
talking about rifles now so uh we were
kind of just talking about the tassel
game so kind of wanted to show off a
very similar rifle to what I was using
this past year at Tel games um so this
is our M M400 X Series so this is kind
of our more featur Rich AR-15 um this
one's 16 in um this particular uh
flashhider is kind of like a hybrid
flashhider with a little bit of
compensation what kind of makes this gun
special is that it does have an Ambi
bull Catch and Release so we like that
for tle games it makes it really easy to
almost show clear you know typically
with an AR you kind of have to break it
down do this weird motion whereas with
this you're literally you can literally
be in here and do that so it makes it
super easy to to make that gun clear um
so very safe uh the one thing I wanted
you to check out was this optic that
we're actually just showing off here at
shot so this is called the at
AMR if you want to take a peek out there
look at that put the magnifier
in wow so I'll kind of describe what
she's seeing so with just the Red Dot I
have this set there's four different
retical settings that you can choose the
way I have it set up right now is a
circle dot so I think what a lot of
people have heard of like the Donut of
death um that allows you to have
something super bright super fast at one
power and then when I flipped it over I
have it so that there's BDC dots and I
also had it actually at a lower
brightness so you have the ability to
adjust both the reticle and the
brightness of both of these it basically
saves what your setting is with just a
red dot or magnified so having that
lower brightness also means that you
have a more precise shooting uh uh
aiming Point uh when you want to shoot
something at a little bit further
distance or you want a little bit finer
uh point of Aim so this is something
that's that's really cool I normally
kind of lean toward lvpo um but I will I
think this might be winning me back to
red dots what's up guys we are here at
Shot Show 2025 I'm with Nick at the Cato
Booth he's going to tell us what is new
for staccato in 2025 Hey Alissa thanks
for having me by the way uh okay so now
we have the hdp4 so if you guys uh are
familiar with the brand obviously we had
the P the C2 uh the Cs we went into V3
kind of stuff and this is all of our new
things right so staccato HD is the new
new we have two different models that
came out a P4 and a p 4.5 uh this one
currently is a p
4.5 difference between this and the uh
4.0 is the front side block here and the
frame is a little bit uh longer there um
one of the big things obviously that the
market is aware we're using Glock style
mags now um so any anybody that uh has a
Glock or uses Glock mags knows how
affordable those magazines are and now
we're able to run them in a staccato uh
we're keeping the same grip angle as the
2011 of you guys currently love we took
away the grip safety here in the back so
now it's a little bit easier oh I didn't
even notice that yeah it's a little bit
a little bit easier
and so with that part um here's a fun
fact is we lowered the AIS of the barrel
so that now you can get your hand better
purchase on the gun so you can control
the gun a little bit more easy right uh
the gun now is fully ambidextrous so any
left-handed right-handed people can now
uh switch the Mad catch over to the left
or right hand side um another another
thing is the uh amid extra slide stop
lever so we now we're completely left
and right-handed uh able to do that
another cool thing that we kind of did
was we moved the rear sight to the front
of the optic the optic plate now is more
of like a a washer so this one has a
Trion HD RMR HD on there so this this
will bolt actually through the plate all
the way to the slide itself so a lot of
other guns have it where you're going to
bolt the the slide um to the actual
optic um piece and then optic to that so
we don't have to worry about that um
another couple cool things I'm just
going to go over all the things we we
currently offer uh in three different
pieces right you have the stainless
Barrel option um you have uh the Amero
front sights come with a stainless
Barrel option and then you have Trion uh
sights with anything that's going to be
a DLC Barrel so that's kind of a cool
thing right now we only offer the the
curve trigger but in the future we'll do
threaded barrels and flat triggers like
we currently offer uh this gun doesn't
have the X Series serration but we do
offer the X Series serration in another
option as well the slide on on the 4.5
is the same as the 4in gun so it's a
basically a 4in slide with a/ in sight
block on it so the reciprocating mass of
the slide is still going to cycle rather
quickly but now there's a little bit
extra weight up here in the front for
you guys to manage recoil a little bit
easier so a lot of people enjoy shooting
this gun a little bit more again overall
length is still 4 and 1/2 in so you're
like still a fulls siiz gun using
fullsize mags the gun also comes with a
MAG well on the top tier as well so
we're just really excited it's a beefier
gun it's it's essentially built off of
all the information that we got using
the version two version one version
three guns that we made and then we kind
of incorporated into everything as
always with staccato it's American made
from the seal that we have that we start
with all the way to the end um no men
Parts everything's high quality and uh
there's a lot more details like twist
Barrel has or the the barrel uh twist
rate has changed now it's one in 10
right hand um a lot of the like I would
call nerd stuff that we love as gun gun
guys and gun girls is all on the website
so if you go to staccato 2011.com and
you guys can look up all the the real
details the widths the Heights and all
that stuff if you're really interested
in learning all that stuff so I
encourage you guys to go there don't
forget we have the heroes program so law
enforcement military anything like that
go to the website we have those links
for that as well so and then what's the
price so 20 $24.99 for the 4 in and then
this will come out with
$26.99 um sometime the 4 and a half will
come out sometime in Spring okay I think
we're looking for a spring launch for
that and then yeah when's the four
available four is available to 28th so
what are we looking at 6 days okay
dealers it's so it's already shipping to
dealers dealers just got to like Bogard
them until the 28th but then if you show
up at the dealer uh on the 20th so if
you don't know where your dealer is go
to the website again and then uh look up
the deal the dealer locator you'll find
the nearest dealer to where you live and
then go there on the 28th and pick an HD
up they'll sell out yeah hopefully yeah
that's the and again we love hearing
feedback from the market so please if
you guys get any feedback for these love
it hate it whatever let us know so that
we can continue to innovate and push
this Market forward as much as we can uh
one of the biggest things obviously that
we didn't really bring up is this is now
a series 80 so it's completely drop safe
it has a firing pin block there's
nothing this that this thing you could
drop it on its face all day long um and
it won't go off that is I will say that
is one comment I get on some of my
videos the internet is a great thing and
and usually the first thing I tell
people is like don't drop your gun like
that's original right but um past that
if they're really that concerned this
this won't happen with this gun so but I
mean if somebody wants to come try come
by the booth check it out and we'll talk
so we're at the b& booth I'm here with
Nick with BSD he's going to tell us what
he has right here hey guys my name is
Nick uh so we have been working here on
bringing the uh vsss Ventures AS Val to
the US domestic market now one of the
big challenges in bringing this is the
fact that ammo can be pretty scarce so
we decided to chamber this in 300
Blackout make it a little bit more user
friendly here now we have had the
absolute privilege of teaming up with
BNT here and they've made us a beautiful
can it is a solid one piece uh can
produce out of inkel through 3D printing
technology um super excited to see this
project come to life we actually started
this project about a year and a half ago
uh we first started building blank
firing kit guns and that evolved as we
started showing off some of our projects
on social media uh more important people
would reach out and say hey we really
want one of those guns you know the big
issue being is that you know the parts
just don't exist so we ended up taking
it upon ourselves to slowly scan and
design and and mock up a gun that would
eventually become a working prototype um
we started modeling back in October uh
at this point we were about a year and a
half in development year year and a half
in development um I reached out to BNT
because we really just wanted to focus
on the gun and partner with another
company that would have uh the
manufacturing ability but also the
vision to create something new and bring
something different to the market
uh B&T was was awesome to work with they
printed us this beautiful can here it is
a true to design QD one piece
design so it has the same lockup system
as
normal now our final variations are
going to be ported
barrels reindex
here so what is what's you unique about
this gun well this gun is integrally
suppressed uh what's not necessarily new
is the fact that it's integrally
suppressed but you just don't see
integrally suppressed vsss Venturas or
ASL rifles around um due to some of you
know uh our import laws these aren't
necessarily easy to get in the country
even the even the kits so it's very
scarce a lot of the guns you do see
produce are manufactured from blank
firing kits or some other type of model
gun so to be able to take you know a
bunch of files create parts and try to
develop an inventory to you know end up
producing and Manufacturing it's just
something that a lot of people have
thought about doing or or tried to do
and just haven't been able to quite
figure it out um we still haven't quite
figured it out 100% you know but we're
slowly getting there you know one step
at a time um super happy with all the
progress we've made so far excited to
see where we're at you know 9 months
down the road from now yeah so is that
when like when do you anticipate it
coming out like you said maybe like 9
months yeah fingers crossed yeah we'll
see we'll see but fingers crossed Q3 Q4
of this year we're going to start
pushing out models um you know in in
working with B&T they made an offer for
us to be in this booth probably
around end in November beginning in
December so we we had a very short
timeline to get some guns together
roughly 78 weeks we put together you
know two no time at all two different
prototypes two different op systems so
uh it's been an absolute blast it's been
chaotic I'm exhausted I'm sure I'm super
happy but um you know I'm excited to see
where this continues to develop and what
kind of refinement we get out of uh this
particular platform have you shot this
yet this particular model no okay it's
funny this this paint the paint was
still drying on this 24 hours or 48
hours prior to coming out here really um
so it was an absolute race to get this
gun our final fire control group uh
Parts here were all um all ended up
coming into the shop Friday for fitting
and final assembly so it was a it was It
was kind of it was kind of a race and a
rush here at the end so weren't able to
play though that's awesome I'm excited
for you to start you know refining it
over the next year now our prototype
model over here uh that one does fire we
fired that several times this one just
needs a little bit of tweaks and a
little bit of you know tuning and we'll
be right there awesome and then do you
know how much it's going to cost yeah
MSRP out the door is going to be around
6500 uh per rifle we're planning on
doing it as like full deployment package
you're going to end up with a nice solid
case the gun breaks down so it'll be
very compact you're going to get a sling
you'll have your choice of stocks uh as
well as a Optics rail as well what's up
guys we're here at Shot Show 2025 I'm
here with Sterling at the sholo booth
we're going to be talking about what
they have new for 2025 it sounds like
correct me if I'm wrong sounds like we
have some update to the Blackjack and
and then a new product is that correct
correct so when we first launched the
Blackjack we used to run a detent delay
blowback we punted that system um and
now go to a roll pin delay system we
found it much better it's actually more
fluid it reduces all the friction that
we were problem problem we having with
detents after seven th several thousand
rounds they were wearing funny they were
causing binding and then breaking the
ears off of the detents so we took that
design and threw it out basically
redesigned and now we have our roll pin
system which is more fluid like I said
it has a pin that actually rolls in
there and it locks into our recoil
spring Rod so when it's in battery it
fully locks and snaps in so that's what
it's overcoming so initially I I think
you talked about in your video a little
bit the initial lock up it's like a
little tough at first and as it wears in
that spring wears in it gets a little
smoother helps so cycling so what other
changes to the black deck are there so
the other thing we're doing this year
with the new system in it it also has a
fixed ejector which the original one
never had a fixed ejector and it was
part of the bolt stop on it so when the
bolt stop would move the last round a
lot of times it would it would actually
Jam in the gun so we it wasn't holding
open like it was supposed to so we
redesigned that um we also are coming
out with the Ambi safety now that was a
big request last year at SHOT show a lot
of people are like oh I love it i' would
love the see Ambi safety and with that
we have the Ambi side charger so you can
put it on either side
now we also added a Tak down pin so it's
toolless so when you remove the and up
open the gun you can actually pop that
out and separate your up and lower
without any
tools cuz a lot of people they like to
maybe even run a separate upper um with
a 4-in barrel or rifle once so they can
change their configuration really fast
right in the
field um couple other things we're
working on this year we're working on a
a 10 mil so that was a huge request last
year at SHOT show was to come out with
the 10 mil so we decided all right
that's that's the next caliber we're
going to work on so we running the HK
mags and we grab one real fast
so this is going to be called the odds
maker the
om10 um so like I said the HK mags we
wanted to stick with a double feed
double stack mag 30 round capacity and
these are becoming more available too HK
parts and other places they're starting
to carry them they're about a $50 mag so
it's not terrible we like to stay with
the like the Scorpion mags were $20 but
we've gone up so price of this gun will
go up a little bit the other things
we're work on right now is a hydraulic
buffer system for along with a roll pin
delay
so what's the what's the price of this
new one we don't have a price fully
dialed in because like I said we're
still developing some of the parts for
it so the price is may change um it's
going to be a little bit more than the
standard price the blackjack right now
probably the $18 to $1,900 range got
it I'm here with Mark at the Desert Tech
Booth he's going to be talking about
what they've got here and what's new for
2025 hey guys yeah so new products for
Desert Tech is going to be really
talking about the Quattro 15s and then
we have our Wolverine line kind of
flushed out uh this is our standard
product offering this is a multic
caliber bullpup rifle uh very similar to
what you saw in the earlier generations
of the MVR and the mvrx this just kind
of kind of be the next evolution of that
platform we've done a 40% Parts
reduction we've machined everything
internal to the chassis uh We've offered
a better gas system in here we went to a
side eject on all calibers just to add
that much more reliability out of this
system uh this one chassis is going to
do everything from 6 5 308 300 Blackout
and know 556 which you see configured
here uh my favorite configuration of it
is the Micron which is our 115 shorty
option so this is just really really
snazzy you have a non-reciprocating
charging handle a rear seated bolt
release you have AR style mag controls
up here but you also have that pinch and
strip so just kind of a really neat
modular system there talk about
applications for law enforcement and
Military having a really small package
or your you know your consumer and
civilian models which are going to give
you a lot of ballistic Advantage without
any compromises on that super long right
you get that short compact package so
that's just something kind of cool it's
our Flagship product there something
that we're known for but our new product
for this year we have the lowers but now
we're going to rock with a full Quattro
15 rifle these are going to come in 11
and 1 12 in pistol versions and then
you'll see the 16-in Bro rifle back here
on you'll have our furniture on there
but we will be shipping these with the
radians uh on these uh something cool
about
these it's going to come with a quad
stacked 53 round magazine this is going
to be a single spring and a single
follower so you can see that in there
the follower is up in there but it's
just going to be super super reliable
you're not going to have a bunch of jams
and a bunch of issues in there we're not
doing multiple Springs multiple
followers we wanted to design this with
the Army's ngsw program so when we
didn't get the track for the magfed
machine gun we just re you know
re-engineered that into an AR started
with the magazine and then built the
lower around it the lower features full
Ambi controls so you guys have your bolt
hold open levers your full Ambi mag
releases here Standard air controls on
this particular side uh so yeah really
cool something we are debuting we're
talking about an onboard computer system
that is going to do some round counters
it uses a series of
magnets and the mag magnets are going to
work by trying to it'll have a a magnet
in there that will sense 53 once it gets
all the way up uh it will start giving
you more accurate round count readings
you have a light here top that button
it's a light really short battery so we
wanted to conserve that we're looking at
you know increasing that or having
permanent on options there but this is
an early prototype going to be an
optional system for people to run on
their quatros if they want kind of give
you that Space Age vibe there but yeah
really slick system going to be offering
coming in at a price point of $8.99 MSRP
for your consumers and then obviously
dealers and distribution are coming in a
little bit less so yeah available now or
when will it be available right now we
are shipping basically February 1st so
right after shot show these will start
rolling out for consumers uh pistols and
rifles same same price sweet I'm here at
the CZ Booth with Cole and we're going
to talk about the CZ Bren yes so this is
the uh the Bren 3 um so a lot the Bren 2
came out a couple years ago and it's
been used extensively right now in some
overseas conflicts that uh I'm sure
everyone's quite aware of but the Bren 3
actually came out of those conflicts
from uh from feedback we've been getting
from end users so the Bren 2 is still an
excellent platform still very reliable
durable service rifle we've just added a
couple long-term durability uh upgrades
over here to the three models so uh I'll
start front to back so the first most
obvious thing you can see is an extended
handguard here that's mlock so uh
previously on the brand 2 you had kind
of a short truncated hand card due to
the fact that the receiver was uh
monolithic but this one goes out a
little bit further you've got some QD
slots on either side and also as you can
see here this Ingress here for you to
access the gas Port adjustment knob um
the gas Port adjustment has also changed
a little bit it's still three settings
the same way it is on the brand 2
however instead of the fully off setting
that we had on the Bren 2 this one has a
designated suppressed setting so little
bit nicer uh instead of using rifle
grenades more people using suppressors
so that makes a bit more sense uh moving
back from there uh We've got uh the bolt
and bolt carrier um have had some minor
tweaks done to them so the uh the bolt
carrier has a new uh bolt bounce uh
prevention system uh just to stop an out
of battery detonation the bolt face
itself now has dual ejectors instead of
uh of single ejectors um moving back
from there the
stock NOW links up on a metal retaining
uh portion right here rather than a
plastic one that's on the Bren 2 and
this is to prevent uh wobble and this
whole kind of wallering out on the
plastic another great thing about this
uh stock redesign is you can now drop
the trigger pack which by the way is
100% backwards compatible with the uh
Bren 2 but you can drop this polymer
trigger pack off and you can take all
the bolt guts out of the gun from the
rear without taking the stock off so
that's an upgrade we did uh very last
thing that I will say probably has some
limited uh usage on the civilian Market
but it's uh very exciting from a
military standpoint is these four screws
we've got here on the side of the
receiver so previously the uh the brand
has an extruded aluminum upper receiver
uh that a steel bolt and b or bolt cam
pin ride on so steel riding on aluminum
that does have some wear uh that happens
a little bit quicker so being able to
remove this rail and also have it be
made out of steel greatly improves the
uh the service life of the upper
assembly itself and lets you keep that
same serial number in service for longer
so like I said the the operating
principle of the uh Bren 2 or the brand
3 really hasn't changed over the too um
it's just a few little inline Creature
Comforts and uh and Service uh
durability standards have been uh have
been worked into design awesome and then
just in general for the brand what would
you say um is unique about it me
personally I think that the uh the
Piston driven system itself really lends
itself to uh cleaner shooting and uh and
a more reliable function we've actually
simplified the gas system from the brand
2 to a two-piece rather than a one piece
um and I would say really the other
thing that I mentioned earlier about the
uh the removable rail here just being
being able to service the weapon and
service that really integral part um of
the uh of how the bolt rides in the uh
system being able to change that out and
uh and make those improvements on the
Fly and keep your main receiver in
action is uh is something that really
unique to the market that I don't think
that uh I haven't seen anyone else do
I'm here with Ben at the Zev Tech booth
and he's going to talk a little bit
about their products hey guys so what we
have here is the fdp I know plenty of
you probably saw a lot of it last year
um we are super super close right now
we're planning the goal is to launch
this in uh the first quarter of 2025
late 20 late first quarter excuse me
yeah um this particular model here is
the spr or carbine version that we're
going to launch which will come out
first after that we we will release a
pistol variant um for those of you who
are not as familiar with the platform
this was something that um mag pulled
kind of teased a number of years ago Zev
came on board a couple years years ago
and started uh everyone realized that
the the frame that we use in our oz9
pistols was a great fit for this
particular system so we've taken that
modified it to suit the needs of the fdp
um to make it a dedicated uh platform as
opposed to just a chassis so uh as far
as operationally speaking goes
deployment you got your choice of left
or right these tabs here it's just a
straight push back on the button but
that also doubles as your charging
handle
you have slide release here also a
manual safety which kind of adds to the
to the safety of the firearm you can
carry this one in the chamber with the
manual safety on when it's all folded up
it's uh there's no chance of it going
off so uh when you're ready to kind of
get it folded back up start back here at
the grip just get it started and come to
the top of the stock
here n make sure the slides forward
first
then it will all fold back
up that's fun yeah that's really fun so
I'm curious that what kind of started
this idea so this was something that uh
like I said magpole and 08 they kind of
it was a proof of concept they just
wanted to see if they could do it yeah
it was originally going to be a chassis
for a Glock firearm um and since that
obviously has extensive history in
making aftermarket components for for
Glock it just kind of made sense once we
start started developing our own pistol
um and realized that uh it was going to
be perfect for turning this into not
just another chassis for handgun but
it's own its own weapon system yeah and
what like price do we know kind of what
that's going to be yeah so right now
it's going to be about $16.99 okay yeah
awesome yeah it's a pretty sweet little
thing the fold the folding part of it
all super cool but what really drives
the point home is when you get to shoot
it like we we did a launch event a
couple months ago we had a an lpvo on
here 1 by8 we were shooting this out to
200 yards no no problem so did you guys
have it at range day this week we didn't
no no not this year hopefully next year
though yeah yeah it's awesome yeah yeah
so pretty exciting like I said goal is
uh end of first quarter 20 25 hopefully
we meet that goal uh but we're pretty
darn
close yep either hand whichever you
decide just uh press straight oh you
have to go down yeah straight down
exactly I can even like hold it
oh that was easier you don't really have
to do anything it just it does it for
you yeah that's awesome exactly and
then there you go it's easy simp that
that's awesome that's really fun