what's going on guys card mechanic here
and today I'm going to be teaching you
the four kings card trick let's get into
it now check this out I have the one two
three and four kings now I'll take these
Kings and I'll leave them facedown on
top of the deck
now think about these Kings is is that
there's such good friends and they're
completely inseparable so us I'll take a
king I'll leave it on the bottom of the
deck I'll take another King and leave it
about 3/4 of the way in take another
King leave it about 1/4 of the way in
and I'll leave the last King on top now
check this out I'll push all these Kings
into the deck and because they're
inseparable if I just give the deck a
quick cut like this and look through the
deck we'll see that all four kings are
now right next to each other and that is
the four king card trick now in order to
do this trick of course we're gonna need
the four kings
so we're start off with the four kings
and we're also going to need two random
cards so I'll just take - unfortunately
deck now let's just say these are the
two random cards now I like to start off
by having the two lanham cards right in
the center of all the Kings so two Kings
two random cards on the two other kings
and now to shoulder cards to the
spectator saying I have four kings and
the way I do this is I peel off the top
cart slide it down I peel off the back
card so I chose three kings and I peel
off one more back card so now that show
is that I have four kings and this card
is holding three cards the one king and
two random cards okay so I just give
that a bit of a practice and you'll
definitely get it down so like you saw
in my performance I took the deck said I
have four kings and I counted off one
two three and four now of course this is
a lot easier if you don't have a deck in
your hand but for my purposes we'll just
keep the deck in my hand so you're sure
we have the four kings now what we're
gonna do is we're gonna grab this card
and discard just put them up like this
and put them right in the back and turn
this whole packet over and you're pretty
much gonna tell the spectator that I
want to take the four kings leave them
facedown on top of the deck and now if
you take a look at the order of the
cards we have three kings two random
cards and one last King so that's how
these cards are face down on top of the
deck
now for the first part we take one King
so two spectator you don't have to you
can if you want to just join them to
spectator makes it a bit more believable
show it to the spectator and put it
facedown you know pretty much on the
bottom of the deck and as you're doing
so just make up some story about how the
Kings are such good friends and then
completely inseparable just for you know
fun and performance purposes so now once
that card is on the bottom we take the
next card make sure to not show this
card to the spectator because it's the
random card put that somewhere
put that somewhere else in the deck take
the other random card put that somewhere
else in the deck above that and then of
course you just say and I'll take the
last king flash it really quick or if
you want it slowly but show I'll take
the last team and put it on top of the
deck and I'll slide all of these cards
right into the deck and at this point
the specter is going to think okay you
two split all the cards in the deck now
what's going to happen how are these
Kings gonna come back together since
they're so inseparable and now if we
take a look we have three kings on top
and we have one King on the bottom so
giving the deck a cut is gonna put this
one King on top of these three kings and
you're pretty much set that is pretty
much the trick all you have to do now is
reveal that the four kings are so
inseparable that they're found their way
right back to each other now this is a
nice beginner card trick because all
you're really doing is showing four
kings with two cards hidden and I think
that's probably the most difficult part
of the trick and now one thing is if you
don't want to show the four kings like I
did in the beginning
you could just have these cards pre set
up before I even show the trick you have
the cards lined up pretty much like this
and before you even bring it out to the
spectator just spread it in a way that
you're pretty much coming in with
showing I have these four kings and then
you just close them and put them on top
and at this point you're still pretty
much set up for the trick so if you want
to show it and fit in front of the
spectator
I mean spread it out in front of the
spectator you can do that or you could
arrange it in the beginning shortest
spectator then close it it pretty much
all up to you and whichever way you
think is easier but I hope you guys like
the trick and that is it for the four
kings card trick thank you guys so much
for watching make sure to check out my
social media links down in the
description below and I'll see you in my
next video
welcome to the N screen if you liked the
video make sure to hit that like button
leave a comment down below and subscribe
because subscribing is good thanks for
watching
[Music]