today I'm going to build five Lego
turbine engines to test which ones can
generate the most
power make sure you guys stick to the
end because the last one it's going to
blow you away also this video is
sponsored by Shopify but more on them
later essentially each one of these
engines we're trying to build is going
to take some sort of natural force like
water or air or heat and they're going
to turn that into electricity or
rotational energy starting with our
first build which is going to be a
vacuum turbo if we build together a
couple of these little cylinder pieces
with an exit on both sides and that
should let us control the direction of
the air fr
so now look this is what it's supposed
to do we're going to have the air which
is going to suck from this side and then
if we cap this off and create a little
spinny thing on the inside of this we
should be able to take an axle from that
and it should spin then we just need
something with wings to attach to that
I'm going use a few of these gears and
then just attach some lift arms to the
top of these and that should hopefully
create a little wings
propeller all right now we just got to
attach that to this axle inside this guy
now will that work probably not because
it's not taking up the entire thing we
might just need to make the blades a
little bigger
okay I've added a few more pieces to
seal this in a little bit better let's
see if this
works why is it turning that way
oh I get it now we need to put this box
shape up here because then no matter
which side we go from it'll be sucking
air across and this thing will keep
spinning quick
redesign so to actually test the energy
output of these turbines I have here
this Lego education set and on the
inside of it are a bunch of cool
Electronics like the solar panel and
some lights but the important part
inside of here is this thing this is a
type of Lego voltage meter and when we
hook it up to this little battery here
and the special motor that it comes with
we can actually utilize this motor as a
generator and then calculate how much
energy it's producing and then to test
the speed of our Motors we have this
little Lego Technic speed gauge and
that'll let us see the RPM the turbines
are generating the first thing we're
going to measure is speed we're going to
take our speed meter and snap it right
on top like that let's see here stick
our vacuum up to the side in three two
come
on there we
go 2,000 look at
that it's
spinning all right what do we got 2560
RPM that's rotations per minute which
isn't bad but we can conduct a quick
torque test with just a tire actually
that'll add a little bit of weight to it
too which should be nice
this thing has absolutely zero torque so
I'm going to give power a 1 out of 10
speed we got 2560 I'm going to give that
an 8 out of 10 cuz that's pretty good
and electricity generated zero because
it doesn't have enough torque to
actually spin our generator luckily the
next one should be a lot stronger the
next turbine I want to build is a water
turbine which is powered by water also
known as a water wheel so back in the
olden days they would have these giant
water wheels attached to houses and the
wheel would sit over a flowing stream of
water which would cause it to turn and
they can power stuff inside their house
create electricity I think I think the
best way to start this is to create a
shape using These Guys these are these
little angle bits when you snap together
eight of them you can create a nice
octagon shape with Stud connection which
is exactly what we need snap we grab
some plates and we snap this guy
together and to make this so that it can
actually be attached to an axle and
pivot we're just going use one of these
guys which really that doesn't fit
across Lego seriously I really thought
this thing would fit across uh ah I know
what to
do no shot that actually worked there's
the center and now we can spin this like
a water wheel all we have to do is just
create buckets or little flaps that will
actually be attached to this that way
when the stream is running it'll
actually push the flaps and cause this
thing to
spin then to create our Scoops we're
just going to build a few bricks down
from each of these and the water should
hit that and make this turn pro tip if
you ever missing one piece just lock
together three plates and boom you have
a brick cuz it's winter and I'm not
going to go find a stream somewhere so
I'm going to build up a Lego Stream
inside this tank using a water pump and
a bunch of bricks that way we should be
able to just take our turbine and set it
right in the middle to test if it works
and while I'm doing that I can tell you
about this video sponsor Shopify the
all-in-one Commerce platform that lets
you sell both online and in person
making it easy to start your new
business venture at any skill level I've
been using Shopify to manage my online
store where we sell these little
buildable figures I didn't really know
what I was doing when I first started
but Shopify makes it really easy to add
new products and customize things the
way I like all I have to do is just drag
and drop just so this thing doesn't
float up to the top I got some rocks
here I'm going to take those and just
stack them against this wall in the back
so say I want to build a store selling
these stylish Lego watches I can just
take a picture of the product with my
phone and then using their fancy AI tool
Shopify magic I can actually remove the
background and generate something a bit
more professional dang these are
actually pretty cool I can also use
Shopify magic to write my product's
description just give it a few keywords
check that out so easy and I literally
did all that from the mobile app on my
phone so we take our water pump here
we'll take our tubing and run that all
the way back behind this wall and
theoretically this should work to pump
water Shopify is making Commerce
accessible to entrepreneurs at any scale
and if you're selling in person they
also just expanded their tap to- pay
system to Android as well so you aren't
just limited to selling online I've also
built this guy which is based on an old
Lego set I used to have and I've built
in a special feature it's like a
blacksmith house and there we go so I
had this filled up all the way above the
pump and it's just not pumping enough
water to actually move the wheel so
we're going to pretend there's a
waterfall in a mountain right here with
Shopify making it as easy as ever to
start your new Venture there's no excuse
not to build your dream business so to
get a free trial you can go to
shopify.com Bricks science or click the
first link down in the description Let's
test this thing out turn on the pump the
water goes up the tube come on there we
go yeah we now have a water powerered
turbine check it out we can even
probably make this go a little bit
faster by adding some sort of buckets
instead of the paddles on the wheel I
think if we hold the thing oh yeah just
a little higher get a little bit of a
better waterfall it's also hitting the
hammer in the back which is not working
every time but it's still
working let's test the speed on it
though we go full power we are
[Music]
getting zero so for the RPM we're
getting nothing significant but we can
actually see if this will generate some
power with our motor I'm going to attach
this directly into this box we got to go
full power for
this uh okay 1.2 volts not terrible not
great either it definitely doesn't have
a lot of torque that's for sure the
thing is at this scale too water is not
as heavy as why is it flashing what I
don't know we did I think we broke it
what I was saying was there's a lot of
friction here for all three factors I'm
going to give this one like a 1 out of
10 it's not super fast it doesn't have a
lot of torque and in this case it
doesn't generate that much energy the
next build on the list is a Tesla
turbine actually invented by Nicola
Tesla himself according to my research
the Tesla turbine actually doesn't have
any rotors it's comprised of discs to
build this in Lego we're going to
actually use some CDs for the blade and
when we shoot compressed air into this
the discs are going to spin individually
and the air coupled with the smooth
surfaces of the discs are going to
create lamin or flow to spin them around
and the air needs to exit right about
here so first we need to figure out how
to attach these discs together my first
thought was let's take an axle and a 2x2
brick and now we can stick this guy
right in here except it's just too big
for the opening of the
discs well that Des is busted I did
discover a piece that fits inside this
which is a little Lego tire and if you
you put a gear inside of it it expands
just enough and also gives us an axle
attachment point and then we find
something to go around that piece as the
spacer a Lego rubber band put that guy
on here then we can put our next disc
that isn't broken right on top of there
and we can do that one more time for the
final disc here check out that spacing
that is like almost perfect now we just
lack the air exit so we're going to have
to drill holes in a few
discs hopefully the air should be able
to flow through there now we need to
build a housing for this out of Lego
with one entrance and then we need to
build the exit right over this
[Music]
area I'm using these Lego glass panels
on the front to actually build this up
because I don't want the air to have
anywhere else to go than around the
smooth discs and out through all those
holes we
drove here we have our Tesla turbine I
think it turned out pretty cool actually
we got our shiny discs on the inside and
hopefully those should give us some
pretty good RPM also since the discs are
so heavy I'm thinking it'll give us some
good torque too let's see how fast this
goes
wa what happened yeah we might have
broken it that's what you get when you
engineer things out of rubber and
plastic I think the rubber bands move
that's not good we're going to have to
basically glue these discs onto the axle
because right now the axle is just
spinning while the discs
aren't all right here we go see how much
power we can generate if
any oh dang look at
that dud dude this has got some good
torque to be able to spin that motor now
I'm kind of curious how much power we
can generate
here it's spinning really fast that's
for
sure wo just with that we've already
built up 8 volts we can take that power
we just generated with our Tesla turbine
and put it onto our motor and we can see
how much power that is let's
see okay so it wasn't that much power
but it ran the motor that that's cool
right I'm going to test the RPM one more
time here let's see how fast we can get
it it's still going we maxed out the RPM
that is insane let's try it with a tire
on the front too so let's check this
out did you see the tire expand dude
Tesla turbines all right oh God Tesla
turbines are dope I'm going to say 10
out of 10 RPM because we maxed it out
we'll give electricity 10 out of 10 as
well cuz that built up to 8 volts like
really fast and then for torque I'm
going to honestly just give this like
an8 out of 10 that's not bad I'd
arguably say the Tesla turbine is the
best one so far it's going to be hard to
outdo this one honestly the next turbine
I want to build is a steam powered
turbine and I want to clarify this is
not a steam engine so I've got a bunch
of Lego propellers here and each one of
them is a little bit different the
problem is most of the good ones don't
have an axle without an axle we can't
actually generate any power so I think
we're going to have to design our own to
actually generate our steam I bought
this steam cleaner which has this little
nozzle that'll shoot out steam super
duper fast thing about this though is
that the steam is really hot don't do
this at
[Music]
home interesting maybe kind of like the
vacuum powered one we actually need some
flaps instead of blades and then
hopefully what we can do is take these
and turn them into a propeller and we
kind of connect them at Angles all
around a little Central thing then we
should have those Scoops where the air
will fit I think we take one of these
little wheel pieces it has six holes in
it so what we can do is add some of
these pieces then we can add our little
bars and then add our blades to the
outside of that then just duplicate this
one more time with the flags upside down
we can sandwich them
together that is actually pretty cool
let's give that a
whirl I think that'll work so all these
guys actually folded over but we can use
a couple of these clips on the inside of
the pieces stop them from moving around
now these guys can't move over anymore I
think we can just build up a simple
housing with the Technic brick at the
back once we do that we should be ready
to test this thing
out so here we have our finished design
for the steam powered motor I just added
some fun details as well as this piece
which has a tiny little hole through it
so we can actually shoot the steam in
one direction we're going to start with
speed don't do this at
home all right let's see what she can do
put it right through here
good grief 3,300 3,540 3580 3,600
RPM dude I was definitely not expecting
that and that thing actually worked
really really well from what I can see
none of the blades broke off and nothing
melted because the water cooled just in
time now let's get rid of this thing and
test how much electricity this thing can
produce all right here it
goes I think we're going to need to
implement a gear ratio the purpose of
the gear ratio is to make it so that
this actually has the torque to spin our
motor and generate the power look at
that that's so much easier to spin now
okay currently says zero Jewels let's
see what we got
here it's working one
Jewel 4.4 volts wa 5 volts let's see how
much energy we can build up with this
nine Jews wow this is working really
well 10
[Music]
Jews wow 15 Jews dude that's insane
oh gosh it has a little thing on it that
says we put too much power into it I
think for being a tiny little steam
engine this one worked really really
well so I'd give it a 2 out of 10 on
power a 10 out of 10 on speed and then
maybe like a 5 out of 10 on electricity
cuz we were getting a solid 4.5 volts
generated which is pretty good and while
that was pretty cool the final build is
going to be even cooler cuz I'm going to
build an air powered turbine but instead
of building a big white three-prong fan
because that'd be super lame I'm going
to build mine into a jet engine turbo
fan so the first thing we need is the
actual fan that's going to go on the
front of the jet engine so I have these
little propellers here if we put a bunch
of these in the circle and then attach
them together giving each one a little
bit of an angle that should let enough
air into the engine to actually make it
work and since Lego is not fireproof
we're not actually going to be
combusting fuel inside this thing we're
just going to build it up to look like a
jet engine and then see if it can
generate power so I attached all these
to these little spider pieces because
they have eight connections and if we
sandwich two together that will give us
our shape but these things all being
attached to hinges so they're super
flimsy but we can connect a bunch of
these together and that gives us eight
connections and then we connect these to
that and then do another one underneath
it this might be
it here we have our finished propeller
design I'm going to put this little guy
on the top here to cap everything
together and finish off the front of it
for the housing for this we're going to
need a big circle and I'm going to build
that using hinges and plates so if we
connect a bunch of these guys end to end
we should have a big enough
Circle we just have to cover this in a
bunch of plates and tiles to complete it
and make it look like a jet engine then
we'll just have to find a way to attach
our turbine to the
inside so basically I just built this up
using some wedge plates and a bunch of
tiles on the outside to give it a smooth
finish and then to lock that together so
doesn't fall apart I have some Technic
running through the center of it here so
now we can install the propeller on the
inside of this so it just goes right
into there and Spins and then if we're
talking about like a turbo fan jet
engine there's several other propellers
inside it to compress the
air the last thing I'm going to add to
this is just a simple After Burner on
the back and then we'll actually test
this thing out and see how much power I
can generate all right our final turbine
I've actually built this one with a
special feature which is it not being
completely done so it has like a cutaway
so you can actually see the inside of
what's going on we have all of the
propellers which can spin freely also
added in these little igniters so in a
real jet engine the fuel would go
through these and be ignited and mixed
with the air that's a dumb down version
but essentially how it works and to
actually have enough air coming into
this so we can power it I'm going to use
a leaf blower first let's see how much
electricity this can generate our
voltage meter broke so to measure how
much power is coming out of this we're
going to start with the
lights there's 10%
power 20%
power it's spinning are the lights
lighting up not quite one more
[Applause]
oh we're getting light that's 80%
power so for power generation we have
absolutely 0% so that's 0 out of 10 for
torque it's not terrible it's actually
able to spin the motor which takes quite
a bit of torque so I'm going to give
that maybe a five out of 10 but the
final ultimate test is to see how fast
this jet turbine is actually spinning
I'm going to start 10%
power okay it working all right
here's
75% the 100%
power it's spinning it's going
fast uhoh some's rattling if it explodes
back
up oh we lost the propeller
blade it's still
going look at that that dude that's
crazy we're losing pieces left and right
oh
no oh
no oh man what are we at 680 it says 680
RPM not bad for a jet engine I think it
started catching on the walls and then
that's why they started falling off
there's really not much else we can test
with this
um guys huge thanks for watching check
out one of these two videos popping up
on your screen big thanks to Shopify for
sponsoring this video and I'll talk to
you in the next brick science see you