today I'm going to be building setting
up and testing over 10 Lego pranks I'm
even going to be flying to another
YouTuber's house to prank them make sure
to list it up so that you guys can use
these pranks on your
mom okay for the first prank I'm going
to build a mouse trap that can trap
someone's finger I used some rubber
bands and some functional pieces to
build a system where a shaft can
actually snap and grab someone's finger
okay here is the finished mouse trap now
I'm going to try and wind it up and
actually test it out hopefully I don't
lose my
fingers ow oh my God okay that hurt more
than stubbing your toe on a wall of Lego
so here's me testing it out on a bunch
of other Lego items and only use this at
home if the power is really low
otherwise you're going to give a
permanent red scar to your victim okay
but for these next few pranks I'm flying
to my friend TD Brick's house across the
country to prank him last time we met up
we had a giant Lego war but this time
he's not expecting anything and after
sitting next to a crying baby for 5
hours I landed all right guys we're here
we're in TD bricks territory could be
anywhere could be in there hi is this my
Uber what the heck been in the car sir
this guy kidnapped my Uber driver and he
picked me up half now that he scooted me
up it's time for the first
prank so for the first prank I'm going
to make him walk on Lego by putting it
in his shoes to do this I'm using some
specialized Lego tape that can tape out
to surfaces so attach that to the bottom
part of his shoes and next I gathered
the most painful Lego pieces in his
collection all right guys I secured the
mother load and attached them onto the
studs of the tape now we just got to put
them both in the shoes now I'm slipping
them back into his shoes this is about
to give him a permanent t tattoo and
putting the shoes back where they were
and now it's time to hopefully get his
reaction yo Tyler can you come down just
got to wait till he comes I kind of want
to get Chipotle do you want to get some
just don't get beans you're going to be
farting all night but just like get
ready okay
sure ow what's in this Oh shoot what the
what the heck why is there Lego pieces
in here they called them Lego shoes for
a reason here let me try these on here
these are so uncomfortable
jump okay that prank was a straight
bucket but this next one will hopefully
be even better for this prank I'm going
to make him lift a bit of Lego that's
completely bottomless so that the Lego
falls on his feet so I'm going to Target
all right I'm at the aisle I'm thinking
we're just going to go the big ones
right here we got to get two of these so
I bought the two bins with Tyler's
credit card so now we have something to
store the LEGO
in and now I'm going to add a hole into
one of them for the Lego to fall out of
I think I'm going to just punch it and
we should get a hole 3 2 1 there we go
we now have a hole inside the box now
that we have the bottomless bin that
he's going to hold and the normal bin
that I'm going to hold I'm taking them
right outside his room and filling them
up with
Lego but while I do that he started to
get suspicious wait Tyler what did you
say I know what you did what what am I
doing you're evil bro he took two bends
and you mix them together buto I already
know it luckily guys he didn't realize
what the actual prank was and now it's
time to run the prank this is going to
be hilarious Yo Tyler I need some help
moving some stuff oh my goodness where
think that room I'm trying to move these
two tubs downstairs
hey good job bro what the lift it wait
what is this like dude just lift it bro
what the heck is this what
what the prank was genius because not
only did the Lego fall out of the bottom
but it went directly for the feet and
got some Critical Hits ow
ow okay next another prank you could do
is breaking your friend's Lego creation
definitely don't do this one at home
Tyler was building a massive Tower in
the backyard and he planned on
destroying it later tonight but we're
going to rub that yo Tyler what are you
building this is huge I'm building this
giant Lego tower to make my neighbors
feel jealous awesome awesome little didy
note that I was about to smash it and
then I went in with the genius plan yo
can I get like a selfie with the tower
yeah yeah go for it I'm just going to do
it like from this side this thing's like
doubled his height wait wait what are
you doing wait what are you doing it's
falling I spent like 5 hours building
that definitely don't do this one at
home because you might accidentally turn
your mom into a
pancake next I'm going to prank him by
building a self-destructing Lego house
it's going to look completely normal but
as soon as he touches it it's going to
break apart so using some super weak
building connections I built up a Lego
house that's really fragile he's going
to feel so
guilty no all right let's go we got it
on might just fall apart by me talking
so I'm going to go quickly get him and
ask him to help me lift the house yo
Tyler can I get help with something yeah
what's up I'm trying to like move some
stuff downstairs so there's like a Lego
house in there what this one yeah right
oh shoot what is this what are you doing
dude I spent 4 hours building that why
are you breaking my house what kind of
illegal building technique did bro
use okay so sac's been pranking me late
hey what I meant to say was I'm going to
get him back here's a mini fig and I'm
going to super glue the head together
then ask sacred to help me remove it um
I can't take this head off can you help
me take it off the heck wait you can't
get it I think maybe I just pushed it
down I got an idea I got an
[Music]
idea so it turns out Tyler started
getting revenge for my pranks so it's
time to turn it up a notch next I'm
going to prank him with a super rare
Lego minifigure Lego used to sell a
series of minifigure Blind Bags called
series 10 Minifigures where for every
1.2 million packs there was one pack
that had an extremely rare minifigure
called Mr Gold that every Lego fan would
do anything for if my friend had one I
would probably rob their house so I
found a fake one on the internet that
I'm going to buy then I snuck it inside
a real series 10 minifigure pack and I'm
going to open it with him to get his
reaction to make a believable bought
five packs and told him that I'm filming
a second Channel video all right I'm
here with my favorite Roblox YouTuber TD
bricks and we're going to be unboxing
some mini fig packs so first we have to
open some normal packs bro I love this
figure and here comes Mr Gold oh my gosh
holy crap this is Mr Gold bro wait what
n no you got Mr Gold what are you are
you actually joking you're oh my go
you're joking it's a real Mr Gold you're
joking the cheapest one I could find is
$3,000 but event I had to reveal it to
him I mean usually like on mini figs
like there's a Lego logo there but let
me check this one oh shoot I think he
got scammed I don't know if I got
scammed or you got scammed and this is a
prank dang wait did you actually prank
me I put it
[Music]
in okay so for this next prank I have to
be quiet because sacred is sleeping
right now basically I have these giant
Lego bricks those ones right there I'm
going to build a giant wall outside of
his room so he won't be able to get out
of
bed a few moments later yo what the heck
what is this
prank okay guys I have an idea so he
moved it I thought he was going to knock
it down like now he's in the bathroom
which is the next door over so I'm going
to move the wall in front of the
bathroom now a few moments later bro
what is this what the heck you like that
you like that wall I went to drop a
Johnson and then you just put some wall
outside this is what you get for
pranking
me okay this is pretty much turned into
a prank war so next I'm going to get him
by replacing all his Minifigures with
plain yellow men so I moved all his
favorite figures to a separate bid and
bought over 100 heads torsos and legs
and plain yellow so that I can replace
them with an army of yellow men bro
instead of all these cool figures
there's going to be a bunch of shirtless
people it looks like I literally dropped
a bucket of paint on all the Minifigures
now that the stand was done I moved it
back to where it originally was and it
looks so much better now I don't even
know how this is a prank and now I'm
going to call it into the room to see
his reaction all right Guys Tyler is
about to come upstairs it's time to get
his reaction good yo what's up bro bro
why are you recording me I don't know I
just like I was filming like wait what
is this what is this wait did you
replace these wait what I I just spilled
a little paint there I didn't know it
did that why are they all
naked for this next prank I'm going to
put Lego on the toilet seat so let's see
how he reacts when he goes to use the
bathroom a few moments later he's going
[Music]
okay next we went out for some food in
the middle of the prank war and it gave
me the idea for another prank of
replacing food with Lego food I decided
to replace the lemonade his drink with
Lego so that he would only know after
taking a sip so I moved the lemonade to
a separate bottle for later sh don't
tell him that it's in there and now I'm
grabbing some Lego pieces that I'm
dumping inside of the cup but once I
dumped in a bunch of Lego I finished it
off with some trans yellow pieces to
match the color of the lemonade and now
I'm going to return it to the fridge and
see his reaction you got lemonade I want
some lemonade it's just in the fridge oh
nice yo thank you bro I appreciate
it wait oh shoot this is this Lego what
is this bro oh my gosh it's this this is
Lego dude this actually looks real
though not going to
lie I need to prank sacred back so I
built this Lego iPhone with apps like
YouTube Tik Tok Spotify then I'm going
to put it in an actual box and pretend
to give him a new iPhone I actually
really like the way this turned out a
few moments later I got you a brand new
iPhone
jeez oh my God it's even better than the
other phone we got the new iOS we got
all the app Spotify it has all the app
it has Discord let's
go okay now everyone is scared of
spiders so I'm going to build a giant
one out of Lego and prank him with it yo
bro I have a surprise put your hand
out
okay open
it wow there's a dead spider on my floor
now look at
that okay the preor has gone on long
enough so now I'm going to end it once
and for all Tyler was taking a nap on
the couch but earlier he was building
with a bunch of jumbo Lego bricks so I'm
using the bricks to build a fort around
him so that when he wakes up he's inside
of a Lego prison he's still sleeping
somehow surprisingly he didn't wake up I
finished up the fort and added on a roof
okay guys to wake him up I'm going to
play an alarm 3 2
1 oh what the heck he did you build this
what is this bro I made you a prison you
can't leave why am I in a coffin right
now what is this yo it's actually kind
of comfy in here not going to lie a few
moments later okay guys I'm going to
break him even more I'm going to go save
on wait no guys Tyler's gone I didn't
mean to do that oh how did you survive
quiet quiet down I'm trying to sleep
right now and that last prank was for
you guys thank you all so much for
watching subscribe don't actually sit on
your friend if he's inside the house see
you oh did you fart oh my God