today I'm going to build five Lego
Bridges using different techniques to
see which one can hold up the best
against weighted Lego cars but first
let's see how much weight Lego can hold
before it breaks starting with 5 lb 10
lb 20 25 are you kidding 30
lb uh 35 lb I'm all out of
Weights as you see Lego can hold up a
lot of weight so we're going to build up
some Lego Bridges starting with the most
basic bridge design an arch bridge it
literally just has an arch but ours is
going to need to be pretty long cuz we
have a 4T pool of water we're going to
be driving these vehicles
over now that we got a solid foundation
we can start building the arch we're
going to build this in two halves so
what I'm going to do is just grab a
brick and go out one stud and then we
can go maybe two out as long as we just
increase the number we can get an arch
going I'm just going to keep building
and hopefully we'll get something strong
enough to drive the cars over as you can
see we're getting some Headway here now
we're overlapping on this side by three
studs and pretty soon I'm just going to
do a band that goes across so Arch will
just be on the sides the science behind
this is actually super unique every
layer you go down it divides the weight
into the layers below it so any pressure
up top is divided all the way down kind
of similar to how a heavy object becomes
lighter when you have a friend to move
it with you if we build it like this
it'll be really strong so now we just
got to build one more of these and we
connect it with a road up top and test
it
out okay so we have the bottom part of
the arch bridge then I'm just going to
take the top of this bridge and snap it
down on top of here then we just got to
gently push this down on the edges here
that should snap in so here we have the
first Bridge the arch bridge all set up
I have the Lego Corvette as the first
car of the video and I've done two
things first I've built this little
adapter for the top here and that's
going to allow us to put different
weights on the car so we can see how
much weight each one of these Bridges
can handle and then the second thing is
I've built up this winch system using a
LEGO motor and a worm gear and that will
actually pull it across so if we touch
our little clip there we got to get our
ooot crash test dummy inside the vehicle
if we just Crush just a little bit like
that all right here we go let's test I'm
going to turn this on click the Switch
and we're going to see if it can pull it
across oh my gosh it's a nerve-wracking
is it going to move it's going it's
moving I'm so nervous I'm so nervous it
has to make it all the way across for it
to
count all right we made it all the way
across let's up it to 10
lb okay it's moving oh no I don't think
it's going to work I think it's going to
crash right when it gets to the
middle steer it back okay 10 lbs in the
middle of the bridge both wheels are not
happy right now they are not rolling
under that
weight dude this little winch is working
perfectly it just pulled 10 lb
successfully across this bridge the arch
bridge is a complete success as you can
see our U guy he's totally fine so let's
build up the next bridge and test the
next car for the next bridge I want to
build a tensegrity bridge which has
never been done before because it's
super unsafe and wouldn't work in real
life but it might work in Lego so the
first thing we got to do is build up a
road and then we'll build a tensity part
Underneath
It All right so now that we got the road
for the second bridge done it looks a
lot like the road for the first bridge
but now we're going to build the
tensegrity things that are going to
actually hold this up if you're not
familiar with the term tensegrity it's
this concept where you have two
platforms and three ropes and they link
together in such a way where it looks
like the top platform is floating so I'm
thinking we build a tensegrity on each
side of the bridge so it'll technically
be floating and possibly wobbly so we're
going to start with a base plate for the
bottom so let's build a quick base on
top of
this and I'm going to attach some
Technic bricks right here separated by a
couple of plates and that way we can put
the hook in it put two plates and
another techic brick and now this should
stand up
straight nice we just got to build a
sing up to be a little taller and then
go out in this
direction
now so now that we have this first hook
we just need to make another one that we
will invert and put upside down then
we'll build up a simple base on top
using plates and Link together the whole
thing with
ropes now that we got this we just need
to tie it together with ropes here and
then on every corner and theoretically
this top
part that was legitimate I'm so tired
theoretically this top part will float
so I've cut all these ropes and these
just slide onto here so if we hang this
top part by these four ropes as you can
see it doesn't float that's not how it
works so what we actually have to do is
take this rope here and tie it onto that
and then once we do that as you can see
there we have our floating tensity look
it's completely floating like just check
that out you could float it that's so
cool and my thought is we could just put
each side of the bridge on top of that
like that we got to make these arms a
little stronger but that is super
promising now just build one one more of
these and we'll put it on each side of
the
bridge I have absolutely no faith in
this bridge but we're going to take our
top and just uh put it right on top of
here it's falling apart already guys
this is the wobbly Bridge ever so here
it is we have our tensity bridge I have
no idea how this is going to work I'm
not going to put any weight on this one
because I don't even think the car will
make it across but we'll grab OT we'll
put him in the passenger side he doesn't
fit perfectly inside the cars but he
fits well enough to test and then we'll
take our hook like that will a bridge
made of tensegrity actually work here we
go all right it's
moving the weight is holding as you can
see this is held up entirely by
tensegrity wow I think it's actually
going to
work no way we made it to the other side
we're going to try 2.5
lbs oh no this is so so nerve-wracking
seriously got to turn the wheels so it
doesn't deer
off it's right in the middle dude this
is crazy now I'm curious can we add 5 lb
right
here 5
lb it's gone you know the actual Bridge
part held together a lot better than I
was expecting as you can see we have our
10 secrity it didn't actually break it
just came loose we got OT in the water
here how do he do
what apparently Lego cars float
Everybody by the way get your OT down
below Link in the description we just
restocked the crash test dummy buildable
figures so if you want one of these to
use in Lego crash tests it's really fun
to build and it's totally posable so you
can put it in like any pose link down in
the description we also still have a
bunch of Minifigures left so grab those
too that's 10 secrity on to the next
Bridge so the next bridge I want to
build is called a trust bridge and the
cool thing about this bridge is all the
structure is on top of the bridge so
there's really nothing under it to keep
it from falling down and the way it
accomplishes that is by using triangles
for example you can see here if I build
two shapes on the Square all these
points can actually hinge so when you
put pressure on it it collapses but on
the triangle none of these points can
move around so as soon as you apply any
pressure on it it is extremely sturdy
from any angle so for the trust Bridge
we're going to combine a bunch of these
all the way down which will turn our
floppy Bridge into a sturdy structure so
first I'm just going to build up a quick
Road for this and then we'll attach the
trusses to the sides always like to
start these off the same way just a
bunch of 16 x 16 plates which I can lock
together with
tiles you have no idea how loud it is
when I just have to build all these
[Music]
Bridges so we got our two Bridge pieces
and now as you can see it's very very
floppy so I'm going to line this with
two layers of Technic bricks and then
I'll add some to the sides as well so we
can attach the trusses and then as you
can see what it's doing is it's just
coming up right there so the whole point
of using these is we need to connect
them so what I like to do just grab some
of these three long pins and then since
we're already connected to the plates I
just like to push it
through from the outside sometimes I use
my hammer and you just got to make sure
you put four four in each brick so that
it has two points of connection on each
thing just got to do this all the way
down so now we need to integrate these
Technic bricks onto the sides here and
while we could just do that it probably
should cuz it'll be easier I want to
cover up all these colored things so I'm
going to use some bricks and then we'll
sandwich our Technic brick like that and
that'll give us a way to attach the
trusses inside there which should make
it pretty
strong so now we got our Bridge built up
and as you can see it is very wobbly
let's build up some trusses so we're
going to take two of these we're just
going to connect each end like this and
now we have our triangle structure the
bottom part of this is going to snap
right into the
bridge as you can see the rest of this
is bending a lot and this part is just
totally not so now we just continue this
technique all the way down on both sides
and I think that'll really really make
this strong check that out you can see
here on the top layer I'm just adding a
single lift arm or a couple that are
latched together to lock everything
together all right check this
out that is a flat bridge and that is
looking really really strong look at
that this one I'm super hopeful for it's
like the strongest one I built so far
for this bridge we have the red pickup
truck we're going to put it right here
and then I just built this little thing
into the bed so we could put our weights
on top I think he'll actually fit in
here you guys oh now there's a giant
door mechanism in the way well we can
get half of OT in there I'm pretty
confident in this one so I'm going to
start it at 10 lbs here we go the trust
bridge is such a cool technique oh it's
moving will it make it across the only
thing I'm a little worried about is the
plates on the bottom cuz they're 16x 16
plates that's the only weak spot I think
the sides will stay
together I love OT in there just
chilling here he goes it's in the middle
of the bridge oh it's kind of bending
right here something's about to snap oh
no oh no no the trusters have come off
the side
but did we break the winch no it just
came off oh man I'm going to call that a
fail there's no way that car was getting
across after that so hey but honestly lb
took it to the very middle of the bridge
and you can see I was just about to say
you can see the triangles haven't broken
but check out the
damage BL bl's good half the man he used
to be yeah you can see the plates and
the tiles just snapped here and then
these came off the sides but it worked
pretty well so that's a trust bridge for
you the next one though is going to
actually use motors to work so let's
check out that one so the next bridge I
want to build is a draw bridge which is
basically just a bridge that opens up
that way ships can go underneath it so I
think I'm going to repurpose our winch
system and build a couple more of these
for each side so we'll basically have a
base with a large tower that comes up
and then we'll have a rope attached to
that that'll actually bring up the other
side of the bridge I'm kind of Unsure
how we're going to make this hold up the
weight in the middle so let's start by
building a
base guys big brain move so there's
going to be so much weight on the center
of the bridge and we don't want it to
collapse since it's not attached we're
going to put weights on the edges to
kind of counterweight it so we'll build
like 10 lb in each side of this and that
should at least give it a good chance
now to make the bridge actually able to
attach to this what I'm going to do is
integrate some Technic bricks in the
sides here there we go and then we build
up the bridge we'll just make sure to
include some techn connections on it now
for the actual Tower structure I think
I'm going to build up two long arms at a
technic brick kind of like I did for the
tensegrity that way we can mount the
winch system to the
top this may not be pretty but it will
be functional you got to build up one
more of those on this
side so to make the winch on this thing
so it actually works I'm going to use a
worm gear we should be able to feed an
axle through somewhere to a motor to get
that motorized sh this long axle
through see now we take these guys and
go through just like that and we should
be able to connect this
that okay that piece goes there now we
turn this on this thing spins and we'll
make our winch actually pull something
up now we need to attach two ropes to
this axle and then once we attach it to
the bridge we will have a functioning
draw bridge last thing before we connect
this all together is just the bridge
part the important part and then
specifically because I want to and not
because they make base plates in that
color we're going to use green and once
we got our Technic bricks and our base
plates in place we just need to lock
down a bunch of bricks on top of it and
add some Technic in the middle to make
it strong so it doesn't fold guys leave
a like if you appreciate how many bricks
I've had to place this video honestly
it's kind of normal for the tips of my
fingers to have little indentations
where the studs are it's so much fun
though
all right we got the first one done up
here I'm thinking it might work all I
got to do is duplicate this and we'll
test it
out we're going to put our weights on
the inside of this here so we're going
to do 20 lbs in each now with those
weights in
place so sus all we have to do is just
use this little remote and that tells
the IR receivers in the winches to
unravel it
nice
hey boom here we go the next vehicle we
have for this is the Porsche convertible
it's convertible now because I had to
take the top off to put the weight thing
on we're going to put OT inside like
this and what I'm going to do is just
put this up slightly on each side that
way when it gets to the middle I'm
hoping the tension will push these down
enough to whe to be flat but it won't
break and now you just clip this
underneath the car for this one I'm
going to start with 2.5 lb here we go
start winding it up it'll go across I
think it might be able to make it over
the Gap but I'm a little nervous that it
just won't line up right oh no it's
creaking it's going down come on you can
do it you can do it
no it's still going wait it can bring it
out of the water it's pulling it out of
the water well I mean to be perfectly
honest half of it still there so there's
that there it goes dude this winch is
awesome this is so
cool
hey all right we made it across the
bridge but half of it fell so
technically it's a fail some would say
I'm a failure this bridge is half
successful you guys and my favorite car
is still alive which is the best part
let's build the next one the next bridge
I want to build is a suspension bridge
the Golden Gate Bridge is actually a
suspension bridge it's basically just a
long road with pillars in the middle and
then reverse arches that are all
connected to hold the bridge together so
first I'm going to build a road with
Technic bricks along the sides like we
did for the last one and that's really
easy and then we're going to build the
suspension arches which we'll have to
attach to two large pillars I'm just
going to do what I did for the
drawbridge basically build two long
pillars that come up out of Technic what
I'm doing here is just building up a
shell on the outside of the Technic
structure that way it'll be a lot
stronger I ran out of red Technic bricks
so my thought is we just build it down a
little bit further and that will attach
to the legs which will just go
underneath
so as you can see this is uh a little
bit wobbly which the whole point of
suspension bridge we actually make it so
it's not wobbly
anymore what we're going to do is use a
bunch of these Technic lift arms and
attach them to the sides to make ropes
that will Arch around and go to the
other side and we just snap all these
together with these little Technic
pins look we're getting the triangle
shape again that is how triangles
work okay now that we have the Arches on
there my thought is we just literally
take some lift arms and attach them at
different intervals if we grab some Lego
axles you can actually put these on the
inside of These
Bricks now we're getting something going
there check it out I think the looseness
of these Technic bricks is going to be a
problem because these can literally just
pull up so we're going to need to put
another layer of bricks over that and
then build it up on the sides but I
think once we get that locked down it
should be a lot stronger and hopefully
when we put it over the pool it'll
actually hold
together all right and now that we have
the structure of our Bridge all we got
to do is build two pillars down to the
floor under these two
areas all right there we have it we have
two little legs on the bottom so that is
strong there and that is strong there I
don't know how strong it is in the
center but we're going to test it out
and find out the last and probably
heaviest vehicle is the Lego Volkswagen
van so I'm going to put a little ooot on
the inside he's chilling and for this
one I'm going to put 10 lbs because I'm
super confident in this bridge here we
go click on the winch let's see if it
works this one took a really long time
to build but I'm so confident in the
technique oh it's moving it's crossing
the bridge this is so much fun literally
just watching each one of these go
across the suspense on this bridge is
crazy oh here we go it's about to enter
its weakest points almost past the
middle of the bridge dude no way we
might have to load more weight on this
actually you're so close to the end you
could do it it successfully made it to
the other side of the bridge I'm going
to add five more pounds all right here
we
go that's it we did it we've made it
across with 15 lb I'm really curious if
we set the car in the middle how much
it's going to take to crash this 10 15
lb 30 lb 35
lb 45
lb that was it 45 lbs on this Lego
bridge look at that that's so cool huge
thanks for watching this video check out
one of these two popping up on your
screen and make sure you check out this
video sponsor Crazy K brickling store
for your Lego brick needs you can check
them out by clicking the link down in
the description or this button right
here on the screen I'll see you in the
next one