workouts practicing you know getting
better is so rarely about what you do in
practice and really what separates you
and anything you want to do is going to
be the unrequired work and that's a big
thing that I emphasize with our guys
it's the unrequired work that's going to
ensure that you maximize what your
potential is we all have a potential
level we all have an expiration on data
on our basketball careers the guys who
push back you know basketball careers
are like yeah it's like a jug of milk
right you put it in the fridge you know
ii mean at some point in time that
things gonna it's gonna be bad right and
you go to pull pours you know and your
bowl of cereal right and you take a bite
right of your fruity pebbles or whatever
and that milk is sour so everybody's got
an expiration date on their career in
the game of basketball right the guys
who push it back are the guys who are
doing the unrequired work that's not
asked of you all right if you only show
up to practice and that's the only time
you work you might be the best player on
your current team absolutely you very
well may be but what you've done is you
put a cap on where you can't go and what
you can be because you're not doing the
extra stuff right so you know when I was
working for the Houston Rockets I'd get
to the Toyota Center at about 7:00 a.m.
right that's worth they play the games
and who would roll in at about 7:30
this was last year I didn't really know
him at that point I'm Chris Paul 7:30
every morning the guys there 7:30 he's a
hall-of-famer
he's already hall-of-famer isn't he
could stop playing he's already made all
kinds of money he's got you know wife
kids family and he's a family man
absolutely
but 7:30 every morning there he is well
who's the second guy that shows up in
the gym
well it's James Harden right so there he
is 7:45 right and they've got to kind of
different ways they go about things but
I tell you this they all are out there
doing this unrequired work they don't
you don't just happen backwards into
being or becoming as good as they are
now do they have some you know some
genetic qualities that maybe separate
them absolutely for sure right but Chris
Paul isn't that fast he's certainly not
that tall that long or that athletic
James Harden he's not fast he'd get off
the ground a little bit but you know
shoot if he stops working out for two or
three weeks he can gain quick ten pounds
and be a fat guy pretty quick you know
what I mean he knows that so that's why
you know he's getting in there
he's on the treadmill he's got like full
sweats on and he's hammering out a sweat
before he takes the court and every day
he does his work he practices and then
after practice he has his post practice
routine right so all these things that
come together there's no coincidence why
these guys are so good why they are as
good as they are after I got done
playing college I was fortunate I got to
play eight years professionally I played
in the NBA Development League won a
championship there when a EuroChallenge
championship in Germany played in Spain
Italy Portugal New Zealand traveled the
world playing and know wherever I went
was I you know one of those genetic-type
freaks right I wasn't the 6/8 guy with
the long arm so he jumped out of the gym
that wasn't what I was but I was a guy
who just outworked people and so I kept
doing that and I kept staying with that
so Clint was came into the arena last
summer right and he's Swiss and he's a
funny guy he gets to that he says I want
to work on my touches right he wants to
the low post I want to all the low post
okay no Clint
we're not forget about the low post when
I'm Mike D'Antoni's favorite sayings is
live by the post die by the post Hakeem
Olajuwon ain't walking through those
doors and it's a different style of game
so you know what we did with Clint you
can imagine this is the court let's say
this is the basket right here this is
the lane put a chair right here in the
deep corner area and put a chair right
here in the high slot area Clint stand
at half-court I'd be right there our
other coach would be right there Clint
would sprint to the low chair set the
screen spin out we throw a lob he dunk
it
he'd sprint back to half-court come over
to my chair set it spin out lob dunk we
had chairs over there we go to the other
side we do the same thing we do it for
30 minutes we shoot free throws and you
come and say what do we do now we do the
same thing again for 30 more minutes if
you want to make 90 million dollars all
you need to do is screen roll catch lobs
get rebounds blocked shots that's it
right what happened was I was working
with a guy a couple guys one minute his
name is Robert Covington the others name
is Tyler Johnson
so those were two guys who were
undrafted who easily could have said you
know Dan you know I didn't make it I
didn't get drafted everybody has
aspirations of that and you know what
next right well both of those guys
continue to work they both went to the
NBA Development League and then Tyler
signed at that point in time which was
what would have been the largest
contract for an underrated player in NBA
history 50 million dollars well then
Robert Covington had to one-up him last
year by signing a sixty-two million
dollar deal and making a second team
all-defense but what I can assure you of
right is the same qualities that these
guys demonstrated you know in terms of
work ethic unrequired work going the
extra mile and all those types of you
know things that are cliched are the
reasons why they are where they are
because none of those guys neither of
them have any sort of super separating
physical tangible ability that they just
woke up with one morning right so it
didn't happen then it fall backwards to
where they were they were they didn't
get there by accident if you want to
make 80 million dollars I know a guy
named Ryan Anderson you can barely walk
and chew gum you can pretend offend his
shadow barely his shadow sometimes it's
a little whoa you know what I mean
eighty million dollars all he's got to
do just make about 80% when he's open
shoot 45% from the three-point line
here's the thing about that if you think
about it good three-point shooters shoot
40% that means 60% of the time you miss
you fail right 60% of the time right
well extremes make 45% of all your
three-point shots you might make eighty
million dollars one day all right that's
all I got for you guys thank you for
your time
hey and I appreciate your guys's effort
I thought you guys did a great job thank
you thank you thank you
you