if he does a good job and cuts me off
and I go boom boom and I get cut off and
I cut me off right now the ball is
exposed if I go over my head here's my
option go ahead even if you play good
defensive cut me off right I go boom cut
me off cut me off cut me off right here
yes do it again so watch even if I go
over the head so boom cut me off Boom
the ball is above my head I still have
the option to shoot this floater or
shoot that little fade I have options
out of that high pickup whereas you go
low it's easier to go ahead and wrap
this up so one move here as you push to
me we're going outside a little pass
fake boom overhead let's create as much
separation as we can and either to
finish that left hand lay up a little
floater or get to the basket go ahead
one two good that'll give me a light a
nice pass fake off that one so sell that
corner pass yes sir
boom boom perfect just like that