have you ever wondered what it would be
like to fly it speeds over Mack
3 well this guy would not know but he
gets pretty darn close because he's
flying what is now the world's fastest
active fighter jet this is the Soviet
Mig 31 foxhound introduced in 1982 as a
blistering fast Interceptor to hunt down
enemy fighter bombers capable of hitting
a speed of mock 3.2 its rate limited to
Mack 2.8 as a means of preserving engine
Integrity it's the successor to the Mig
25 which was until recently the fastest
but the Mig 25 was designed for higher
altitudes and lacked maneuverability the
Mig 31 can hit low altitude Cruise
speeds of Mach 1.2 as opposed to the Mig
25's Mach 0.9 its primary Armament is
the r33 longrange missile but this one
here is the r73 short range missile with
a range of 20 mi and infrared homing
tracking