hey what's good i'm coach collin
castellaw with shot mechanics.com today
I'm gonna teach you the real secrets to
mastering the crossover now every player
wants to make the crowd ooh and I was
the shifty unstoppable crossover but
what a lot of players don't realize is
that they're doing things wrong when
they're practicing them and when they're
executing them in a real game so today
what I want to do is give you an
in-depth breakdown to make sure you're
mastering your own crossover but Before
we jump into it this video is brought to
you by my guys over at victory
performance insoles
victory is a revolutionary insole
technology that helps athletes run
faster jump higher and train smarter
whether you're looking to increase your
performance or enhance your injury
protections victory insole are the
perfect product made out of premium
materials like aerospace grade carbon
fiber they give athletes better shock
absorbing and even better energy return
for spring and bounce alright so for
Shoppach an experienced Peschel or if
you click the top link description down
below you're gonna get $50 off instantly
if you use the coupon code it shot
mechanics and for anybody who purchases
I'm gonna give a free copy of my custom
shot design my one-of-a-kind
revolutionary shooting systems help
every athlete find their perfect jump
shot and we're gonna make it even better
for you so if you click the second link
in the description down below you're
gonna get free instant access to my
explosive score or workout this is a
workout I put together specifically to
help you become more explosive each and
every single time you step onto the
court and it's brought to you by my guys
over at victory performance in Seoul now
when we're thinking about crossovers the
most important thing that a lot of
people don't realize is tempo chain
right the one of the biggest mistakes
that a lot of young players makes is
they think that going fast is always
better right they think fast equals
better but that's not actually true if
you look at a lot of the best you know
players with handles and crossovers guys
like Kyrie Irving and Steph Curry and
Kevin Durant a lot of those guys most
all of them use tempo to throw off the
defense right so instead of Kyrie just
going up up up up and hitting a bunch of
dribbles super fast instead he's setting
up tempo where he's going slow too fast
he's raising his shoulders he's looking
at the rim he's getting his defender up
and down because that joystick mentality
going left right forward back sideways
sideways with different speeds is what
really throws off the defenders right
I've guarded a lot of players in my day
and the ones who are fast aren't
necessarily hard to guard because you
know what they're gonna do you know
where they're gonna go the players that
are hardest to guard are the ones that
dictate tempo make you stop make you go
make you kind of go herky-jerky on
defense those are the ones that are
really tough to guard so think about any
time you're mastering your handle and
anytime you're working on your crossover
don't just work on one speed don't just
sit there and pound the ball back and
forth as fast as you can really work on
you know crossing over and then hanging
it and then going and hanging it going
right if you can work on that tempo
you're gonna be a lot harder to guard
gonna be a lot more shifty and I promise
you you're gonna have a lot more ankle
breakers as well all right so the next
thing that can absolutely explode your
crossover has nothing to do with
dribbling the basketball and there's
nothing to do with the actual handles
and it's this sell your dribble moves
with your eyes the eyes tell the story
that the defender is going to read so if
I'm getting ready to cross over and I
want to cross over to the middle if I
set up a crossover and I'm looking right
there the defender knows exactly where
I'm going I'm staring right at my path
right but if I go to hit a crossover and
I throw my eyes this direction
what's the defender gonna do it looks
like I'm going this way they're gonna
slide to cut me off that way when I whip
it I'm going by them so think about you
know a crossover and to really have a
shifty crossover it's more like playing
chess than it is playing checkers you've
got to set it up one move ahead so if
I'm getting ready and I know I'm gonna
okay I'm gonna quit crossover push the
outside I might throw my eyes to the
inside before I crossover going back the
opposite direction so really think about
and anytime you're working on your
crossover or working on your ball
handles think about selling your eyes in
the direction of the initial dribble not
the direction that you're going on the
crossover if you do that you're gonna
automatically have a much more impactful
crossover because the defense is gonna
jump on it every single time alright so
the next hidden secret to a crossover is
what we call ball control basically
meaning that is at an elite level ball
handler you've got to be able to control
the basketball in 360 degrees around
your body right so what a lot of players
do is they'll work on their handles and
they'll they'll do their crossovers and
they'll do their figure eights and
they'll do all their you know dribbling
drills and all that sort of stuff but
they don't really work on that
360-degree control at all levels so
basically an illegal elbow ball handler
can control the basketball in 360
degrees all around their body at any
height so from your ankle height all the
way up to your shoulder height so when
you're training and working on your
crossover really work on these different
levels and work on this 360 degrees if
I'm working on my crossovers I might
work on hanging it back out here by my
shoulder and then crossing it back
through I might work on putting it back
at a funky angle behind my legs and then
wrapping it behind my back right if you
can work on that 360 degree control it
doesn't matter where the ball bounces
you're always going to be able to make a
play
so work on that ball control and that's
gonna help you out - all right so now
it's time for the secret sauce I'm gonna
give you three drills to help you
absolutely take your crossover to the
next level because we're gonna work on
tempo we're gonna work on ball control
and we're gonna work on all the things
we did in this video so the very first
drill is what we call in and out lateral
crossover so all you're gonna do is
you're gonna sit stationary somewhere
you're gonna hit a roll dribble or an
in-and-out where you're breaking the
center line of your body you're gonna
hit it once you're gonna hang throw your
eyes stab your foot whatever you want to
do and then laterally crossover and
bound the opposite direction now we're
doing the same thing in and out throw my
eyes crossover bound each time Oh throw
my eyes so opposite direction hitting
that going back and forth really work on
tempo with this one here's a great one
to work on that tempo change and really
make sure you're getting that defender
moving going back and forth ice over the
in and out crossovers work side to side
now we're gonna go in and out pull backs
where we're working forward to backwards
so it looks like this we're starting the
exact same we're going in in and out but
this time I'm pushing my in and out
forward stabbing a foot and then I'm
yanking it back just like that
next when I'm rolling in and out forward
yanking it back really working on that
tempo see my shoulder height as I throw
it my shoulders going down now they're
going up down up write that down up his
shoulders is really gonna help you get
that tempo really throw the ball out
throw your head with it try to do a
little shimmy with your head
that's gonna get the defender moving as
well so this time instead of going
sideways we're going downhill downhill
downhill downhill if you're moving in
all directions
[Music]
all right so last time we use an in and
out going forward to yank it back now
we're gonna use it in and out to get
space backwards and then push it forward
with it behind the back so it looks like
this before we were rolling in and out
forward and yank in it now we're gonna
use an in and out to pull backwards to
get space and then we're gonna throw
behind the back going the opposite
direction from here we're gonna do the
exact same thing I'm gonna throw my
shoulders throw my eyes I'm gonna in and
out back I'm gonna go behind the back
board in and out back behind the back
board again we want to add some pause at
some temple add a little bit of
hesitation back there so as I hit this
in and out I don't just want to throw it
behind my back as soon as I can I want
to in and out heads you get the defense
to close the space and then go behind
the back go in that direction you can do
that we're going on 360-degree control
you'll be a master at ball handling
[Music]
I presume you hope to hit that like
button then ahead of the comment section
below let me know what sort of video you
want to see next and don't forget if
you're ready to explode your athletic
performance
check out the toppling description down
below and get your pair of victory
performance insoles today again I love
them I feel more springing every time I
put them in my shoes and you will too
and don't forget if you want to get
better click the second link in
description down below and get free
instant access to our explosive scorer
workout brought to you by my guys over
at victory performance ensel's again i'm
coach collin castellaw with shot
mechanics basketball thanks for watching
it until next time splash on