what
hi
no
what
welcome to demolition ranch i'm joined
by the reaper nick irving what's going
on man what's up dude how's life it's
pretty good what are you doing up to
working on the old brain box yeah
writing some books
just finished up drone strike and
working on
another book yeah so he has a very
valuable brain so i just wanted to
protect him so i got this hat
it has a bulletproof plate in the front
turn sideways
it's so goofy it's that's the it's the
easy version
it has a hard plate up here this is the
same kind of thing that you'd have
in like a plate carrier like a vest it
is a big
hard plate but it's just on the front
and it makes your hat
stick out it looks crazier on me because
i don't you have more hair than me but
like
yeah do i look cool or no i mean you
could go to the bar and
i mean i wouldn't say anything but if
you got shot knocked down
you'd look you look like that which is
not good
so today i have a very special new
gun nick hasn't even seen it i have not
shot it yet it's a race gun which race
gun means a competition gun so i brought
out three other competition guns that i
have
um this is a zev oz 9. it's
it's kind of competition kind of
self-defense and then going up the
ladder here
this is an sti dvc tactical same deal
mostly made for competitions though
very nice 2011 right here and then we
have the
glock 17l this is a taran tactical
combat
master i think you have shot this one
before these are all
competition pistols you can see they
have flared mag wells
they've got competition sights they've
got competition barrels
these guns are really nice they're all
nine millimeters they're great shooters
now nick i got i think a better shooter
okay and i'm excited for you to see it i
wanted i wanted to go ahead and film
nick's reaction to this so this is a
bull armory
this is the sas two you ready now the
only sass i've heard was the sniper
rifle so let's see
it's not a 308 it's not an ar-10 that's
for sure okay
ready oh my god
look at that thing so how crazy is it
this thing has like all the bells and
whistles oh my god
everything i don't even know like what
half this stuff is
okay oh check that out god oh my gosh
you look good with this thing oh my gosh
all right so this is a nine millimeter
as well it's made by bull armory and it
is the
sas ii you can see we have a giant
compensator on the front
and look it's even customized demo ranch
see the top of the barrel there
that's my emblem that's my little demo
ranch eagle and shield the weight is
perfect on here bro
yeah and so ideally in competition guns
you want them to be pretty heavy
because you want them to not kick back
at all when you're shooting you want the
big weight of the gun to absorb that so
it's not
popping up every time so they're made to
be heavy what i'm doing how do you [\h__\h]
this thing so
that's what this lever's for you gotta
you got a big charging handle there
isn't that crazy this is nice bro it's
cool right are you shooting this one
first
uh yeah i think i better do it no you
wanna you wanna i can't stop playing bro
i can i can shoot it first yeah you do
it you do it it's all you before
we shoot the ball armory we gotta try
the other guns first so this is the zev
have i shot this one yet i don't think
you've ever shot that one
such a nice bull man oh yeah i'm always
scared of that little
doling tree so i'm going to go for that
right here first
in the back row yup
little bowling pin
combat master
oh someone's been practicing
it is like that wow okay uh you got to
shoot 2011 now i like that one
i'm a fan of the 45 one of my this is
actually a nine
the fan i'm sorry the fan of the whole
1911 1911
yeah this is one of my favorite guns
you're gonna you're gonna fall in love
i like that i like to fall in love a
little bit i haven't bowled in a while
yeah see if you can make that strike
let's try to pick up the strike we're
doing it
pick up ah the spare i'm always a spare
guy mag dump it right in the center
ah are you in love whoa yes well if you
look up close i have goosebumps
that's you see that hairstyle that's a
good feeling i told you'd fall in love
all right i think now it is time to
try the one we all came here to see
shoot before we shoot this thing i want
to say i know that not everyone has
access to a range like this and those
that do may not have access to a gun
like this but never fear because in
warface you can shoot guns very similar
to this there's a gun called the cz75
checkmate in parrot gold
it's black and gold it has a long gold
compensator just like this one
it has a rig on the top with a red dot
just like this one it is a race gun that
you can use
to shoot bad guys and there's way more
the game's arsenal can be considered an
interactive guide to modern weaponry
featuring more than 400 realistic
military weapons and attachments warface
is a dynamic first-person shooter
available for free download on pc ps4
xbox one and on nintendo switch with
over 86 million registered players
globally warface features traditional
gameplay combined with an innovative
approach including dynamic pvp with 11
different game modes
and pve scenarios and solo missions with
12 raids in a game warface's latest
operation hydra has players defending a
terminal against waves of enemies with
each enemy wave being more dangerous
than the previous one
in total there are 20 waves in the last
one players will become engaged in the
final standoff of the powerful boss in
this mission players fight against
blackwood a private military corporation
which is engaged in the illegal arms
trade
spreading corruption worldwide testing
people and killing civilians
not okay released at the end of 2019 on
pc the new hydra pve operation is now
available for free on ps4
xbox one and nintendo switch hydra is
the new type of warface raid aimed at
three players instead of the standard
five for the game
the mission can be replayed multiple
times unlike new badges marks and
stripes play warface now on ps4 xbox one
and nintendo switch and try yourself out
in the new hydra raid linked in
description
below okay we can shoot it now we did
switch the charging handle to the left
side because we're both right-handed and
it seemed
like it would make more sense if our
left hand could grab it i could go
left-handed
i mean with this gun i feel like i could
shoot good you'll never miss with that
gun
i might give it a shot all right you're
gonna shoot the first shot left-handed
all right we have not fired this thing
yet so
let's see what you got left-handed i'm
gonna go for that top
circle oh my god
oh my gosh left-handed baby
you like it or no it's my left hand bro
[Laughter]
so this is for your thumb to go on that
safety and that is for your other thumb
so there is a place
so you always have the same grip wow
oh my gosh
hey see if you can hit that fox up there
on the hill the red one oh that guy
right there
this one he did he did oh my gosh
oh let me get my thoughts bro you hear
more of the
the the pop the concussion then you feel
the gun shooting really
it doesn't feel like you're shooting
what you're shooting
you know what i'm saying no not at all
it feels like
bro you just gotta shoot it all right
hey by the way your arms are looking
awesome
dude i've i did like 100 push-ups last
night knew it i knew it
i'm not gonna i knew it okay i'm gonna
try it out
nick said he loved it so
let's see if i love it i have a feeling
i'm going to i like the way it looks
i don't know if you guys know but i
really like gold things
okay oh okay that triggers
light
oh oh oh dude red dot is where it's at
bro that's pretty sick that's pretty
sick we are not going to shoot metal now
uh we have a few things to test
do you want to test the hat first yeah
yeah let's see if that hat actually
stops pulling
so i don't know if we really showed it
up close but so cool to see those
cutouts
in the slide that perfectly show
the etching on the barrel with my little
logo there and one other cool thing it
has
is the serial number is demo racer001
it's pretty sweet pretty sweet i i just
need to get good at it now
all right come over here this guy's been
working out look at those abs we have
our beautiful male model here
he is going to uh test out the old
bulletproof
noggin we'll see what happens the good
thing about it he's got
soft plastic skull so we'll really be
able to see how much damage
carries through even if it does stop the
bullet if it
would knock him out it should probably
would all right this thing should stop
nine millimeter
do you think it's gonna knock him out
though is there gonna be a hole in his
head
no i definitely think that cap's popping
off though all right
oh you nailed him right there so this
was like this
wow dude it just punched him hard right
there
it would have broken his orbit what do
you call that i'm not a medic or
i mean that's that's i don't know it's
over the lobe it would have broken his
brow we'll say that yeah so this was
right here
nick had a perfect shot right into it it
did not come out
it stopped that bullet is in there oh
this is cool
but you can see it spread out right
there so it went right in
stopped there but it hit him so hard
it's hard hard
it hit him so hard which is a nine too
like i think that was something bigger
he probably would have survived you
think so no yeah
oh you're being sarcastic no no he would
have survived you're serious yeah i mean
do you think
this guy's fiberglass he would have
survived but he would have been
knocked out yeah you think that would
have broke a fraction maybe a little bit
the skull
yeah let me see this piece
who are you waking up with a bad
headache that's all the tylenol right
there guys i'm going to say
if you're thinking about buying a
bulletproof cap
probably not worth it don't don't worry
about it just duck next we're gonna do a
little more
testing with a little homemade body
armor i guess
uh these were actually made by one of
you guys this was sent to us by a member
of the demolition
and it is glue and
it's it's hard i mean it's cured but
it's not hard hard it's like
soft and spongy so i'll show you what
happens when you
cut it with a knife it doesn't stick
like it's not wet
inside there it's just it dries very
spongy like that so it's pretty dense
pretty soft
it's self-healing so if a bullet does
pass through like
it'll close in after it so we're gonna
see we actually have
a lot of these we've got seven of them
we're gonna line them all up
see how many it takes to stop a nine
millimeter full metal
jacket i think it is stop three one nine
three of those so you think it'll be
stopped in the third
yes sir okay i think it's gonna go
through
i think it's gonna stop in the sixth
really yeah double
let's find out what also is weird about
this is it's squishy like if i
push my thumb down it'll go all the way
to the bottom and then it comes back
but if you try to hit it it stops
like it gets hard when it's hit fast i
don't know what kind of glue this is
like i said i didn't make it but it's
interesting
all right all seven lined up it's gonna
stop right there in the sixth we
are gonna fire one round through the
glue
and just see what happens little hole
right there
it definitely did not go all the way
through so where is it
i don't see i see a hole there still
going here
oh oh there's another one yeah still
going up
oh wow look how cool that is
wow so stuck in the fourth you were
closer
that is neat how crazy is that so that's
kind of like ballistics gel i mean
that's what it does it just
shows where it stops that is sweet i
just had a good idea so i put it back in
there it's still number four
i want to shoot a bunch of them in here
and then see what it looks like so we'll
just like dump a mag into it
and they should probably be mostly all
around that fourth one but some might be
third some might be fifth
that's science guys we're just a regular
science channel
no need to demonetize us
dude you're putting those like in a dime
which is cool because that means the
[\h__\h] will run into each other
hold that one low yeah pull it a little
oh that was it
oh one more one more wonder if you're
all dude no there's more
i don't you know what i think i am doing
you're flipping that safety i am
it's very delicate
there you go nice so nick is doing
this he's hitting it with that and so
that's a training thing
which i remember learning on my other
2011 that you learn
to always have downward pressure on that
safety when you're firing
so you don't rise up turn your safety on
so before you started dumping at the end
you were like just cutting up that spot
right there
so let's pull the tape off let's see
what we got oh look
dude that is so cool nothing in the
first
nothing in the second nothing in the
third
are they all gonna oh they're there
they're all going through kidding
oh crazy all right so the fourth has oh
man these are all just piled on top of
each other here
one two three there four five there and
then pieces probably where they were
smashing each other oh oh
some made it through so that's the fifth
oh there's all
bundled up there look at that wow dude
crazy so they're bent up because they're
all running into each other
that is that is neat and then we got
this one
that ventured into the sixth that was it
probably because these are these are
pushing it into it
ah that's a lot of force man yeah that's
cool
look how crazy that looks you could sell
that as art 400
on ebay right now that's just like
cutting grandma's steak you know
just hard oh that's how you do it right
there
there you go there it is oh
i'm stuck to it dude that's pretty crazy
look at them all matched together there
how many rounds is that 20 yeah i think
you shot like
20 23 or something okay nick has
two different hollow points we got this
little thing right here with the little
that and we have one of these right here
a little man-eater
we got one of that and one of these uh i
think they're stopping
in the second one definitely now that
would be something that
it's the first time i've ever shot this
gun yeah he's got a new gun new carry
gun
oh okay a little bit more punches go
ahead and fire that one too
okay what is this thing called uh oh
it's the nine shield
easy easy there you go the easy okay
it's got a grip safety
interesting got some cool sights high
vis stuff
very nice all right let's go check it
out so this is the second one he shot
it is stuck in the second piece so it
went in there
and it is right there totally opened up
what'd yours do oh i see it
you see it in there yeah it's right
there oh okay oh they both went through
one and a half we'll cut these out we'll
get them out so you can look at them
all right there's that little red tipped
one the whole hornady
opened up not a ton no but but it did
good i mean it's bigger than a nine
the other hollow point definitely opened
up better there it is look at that
that is nice beautiful little flower
there definitely bigger than the other
one you know what i'm rolling with now
yeah hey reaper you know what i would
like to see
i would like to see an epic montage with
slow motion and music of us shooting
that awesome gun i think we can do that
we can knock that out giddy up
we got partners
[Music]
[Applause]
please
go check out officialreaper33 thanks for
coming dude man anytime i appreciate you
this is awesome not gonna lie possibly
new
favorite race gun not not possibly mine
is i don't even shoot competition but i
might i heard you might be
speaking speaking of maybe i should go
shoot a competition
i haven't done a three gun match in a
really long time so now that i have
this beautiful piece of hardware it may
be time to go do it
let me know what you guys think we
should do thanks for watching
demolition ranch i love you and i'll see
you next
[Music]
that's a time idea what about the quad
bobby
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm a doctor ish hey
faisal uh love the tripod been using it
for years carbon fiber
today though it may have got hit with a
bullet we were doing some like epic
like slow-mo shots you guys saw it it
was amazing yeah one went through
not bulletproof anyway thank you for
sending this to me a few years ago
i wouldn't mind another one