foreign
[Music]
laughs
[Applause]
it swallowed a gas tank unfortunately
that mouth on its stomach warped space
which means it can eat anything that's
how we lost those Allied Forces spy
satellites two years ago back then it
just left on its own but maybe it
remembers there's food on Earth or
something whatever the case avoid close
combat King Joe Wyndham prepare to head
out
[Music]
psychology
so yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
who the problems
[Music]
Ultraman Decker final tour journey to
blazar
members of gut select are coming to
Indonesia Taiwan Malaysia Hong Kong and
Thailand
the tour starts in June stay tuned
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
Scarlet Flames the power of Courage
what is it hot okay it's
brother he says metal
uh-huh
[Music]
the sky huh
what is that
[Music]
okay
it ran away
Oh Come
[Music]
my only guess is it's a crack to a
different dimension
problem is it's getting bigger by the
second so then it's not fully open yet
does that mean when it is whatever was
enough to scare off bemstar will come
crawling through
probably
storage is officially on level three
defense standby understood
good
foreign
there's no doubt this is your pool the
extra dimensional being's doing your
pool they're the creators of the
Fearsome terrible monsters dimensional
demons that tried to take over the
universe you said try to so they didn't
and they were stopped
by Brother Ace
by Ultraman Ace
he defeated them
of the six Ultra Brothers
Ultraman Ace is the fifth
he fought a valiant fight against the
Apollo's forces
he's an ultra strong terrible monster
defeating expert
I actually uh owe him a personal debt
wait
then
what's this perhaps brother Aces metal
detected the presence of a terrible
monster and reacted
interesting
have you ever fought a terrible monster
no
but with our strengths combined there's
no way we'll lose
okay okay
[Music]
energy readings Rising
[Applause]
[Music]
space martial arts inherited technique
Master zero investor seven Master Leo
zero seven snail
okay I ask that you chant my name Ultra
man that Ultraman
[Music]
tournament set
so it's you
The Hitman terrible monster baraba
thank you
let's do this Haruki okay
oh
hey
[Applause]
is it talking
about
your face
are
you
don't tell me who thinks Windham is
brother Ace yes
I get it this thing's made up of
residual energy from yapua did
[Applause]
you
foreign
[Music]
failure
atrocious
okay I ask that you said my name
Ultraman that Ultraman
[Music]
Ultraman Delta rise call
eat this
[Music]
I shall have to defeat you and brother
Ace instead here we go hot okay
Mr Billy a rock help us out
I'm going to enjoy this
[Music]
awesome
[Applause]
how to stop me
okay
stop trying to get a picture
built across shot
[Applause]
[Music]
this is bad and we might lose
that's not an option
it looks it
[Music]
said do not give up
good morning
[Music]
brother eighth
it was the power of the metal that
guided me to this earth and I can see
why it did
is that an ultra two
like a friend of Lord sets
so this is Ace
Ultraman Ace
[Music]
[Applause]
laser
[Music]
all living beings feel pain when
attacked they grow fearful panicked and
lower their guard the terrible monsters
are the exception they feel nothing
[Music]
foreign
speed
[Music]
Miss allium
oh wow you must fight two sets yeah
ready to help him out Mrs that you know
it
beta smash
guard up and continue the attack until
it completely stops moving
thank you
[Music]
no razor
shots
[Music]
I'm trying resilient
set Focus your energy in the ultra holes
on your head
yes sir
God
yeah Paul you once said this pictures
must live on bearing the malice of those
who have fallen
that may be true but we Ultras will
fight on until the day this universe is
at peace we'll fight then
thank you
good
stop ring
[Applause]
now's your chance you space set
s
let's fire off an epic one okay
thank you
oh my God
[Music]
Barbara
barbecued
oh
[Music]
I didn't know I could do that
thank you for your guidance brother Ace
you've grown so much
say do you know why I chose the name zet
for you to begin with
oh what the wait hold on a sec
what does that mean what it sounds like
brother Ace was the one who named me
that
then what he's your godfather
oh on Earth zet carries the meaning last
My Hope was that you'll rid this
universe of conflict bring peace and
become the last hero we need
[Music]
brother Ace
thank you
[Music]
foreign
that can break the dimensional barrier
the possibilities
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
okay
the metal we're showing off today is
this
Ace one of the legendary Ultra Brothers
he's an ultra amazing guy and he gave me
the name zat that's so cool he sure used
a lot of different beings didn't he Mr
Zach he's actually known as the master
of beam attacks now that I know why he
chose my name I've gotta live up to it
till next time we'll see you there
M1 is the artificial life form created
by bako's Daughter Rudy but it soon
grows gigantic through a plot by an evil
organization
storage be able to stop m1's Rampage
next on Ultraman set
care and what lies Beyond
Ultra save it
[Music]
if you have nowhere to go would you stay
and master the cosmo Beast style the
cosmo Beast style
continue your basic training to
understand your true strength that's why
you must commune with a cosmo Beast
learn to control your emotions when you
fight
Spirit crane strike
work so we can be accepted and bond with
Cosmo beasts we're in this together
could it be I am bulletin Admiral the
magma invasion of anyone who wishes to
die step forward just you wait Vulcan
okay
please I need to get stronger will you
train me you are the cosmo Beast
Fighters and Planet Fitness
strongest fighting style of the universe
ends today
I am
the Grand Master of the cosmo Beast
Style
regulos of the red dragon white tiger
fist
s up
foreign