foreign
[Music]
hey stop right there it's storage
good to be home
this man is an enemy alien he's behind
every
ter the theft of ultroid zero it's all
his fault we didn't come here to fight
with you that's just what the enemy
wants I promise please just let us
inside open fire are you kidding they're
on arms that's in order just do it but
ma'am I I can't
Captain you see that's his real body now
so
[Music]
I never said I was unarmed
you okay yeah don't worry Captain
they're alive
laughs
seriously can I like have a sample of
your skin cells or something actually
some hair would be fine too
don't mind right let's move
all right come on yeah okay right
[Music]
allied forces are being wiped out across
the planet the only ones left are those
in this base all set okay I think
distrudos has detected us it's headed
straight here this is all a game to them
I figured if we set up a board it would
come to play launch prep is complete
good work
Haruki will take King Joe
I'll be in Windham
our goal is to rescue Yoko from
distrudos and take it out
this building may be targeted soldiers
from HQ might storm it
plus I'm a suspicious alien
if it gets dangerous get out of here
you're free to run
this will be storage's final battle
let's all make it home
so we can have a party and eat some of
bucko's tuna
good
[Applause]
[Music]
I came from a Blazer at the center of a
distant Galaxy a giant with an
unwavering sense of justice eliminate a
future Kaiju threat before no tremendous
prepare to launch the armored Kaiju
Earth care off no time to wait
this is the story of the people United
by the same will to protect the earth
and the battles they face together
Ultraman blazar
category huh I still don't get it
why did you do everything that you did
well I was trying to keep humanity and
celebro and checked while also making
sure neither side gave up what does that
mean forget it it didn't work out
whatever just can I trust you it doesn't
matter make up your own mind okay then I
do I mean still the captain former
Captain actually besides my Riser is
busted so I'm not turning into a monster
anytime soon can you go big as your
normal self I used to be able to but I
lost power
thanks perfect Mr Zed said I can't
transform either which is great in that
case
these two guys are the only weapons
we've got to work with
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
let's do it okay okay
time commencing offensive
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
he may be an antique but that doesn't
mean he can't contribute hey Baco you're
late
give me a break I'm here aren't I
[Applause]
[Music]
mean
okay Joko I'm coming for you here run a
spare batter
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
do it
foreign
[Music]
huh
and who are you uh it's me Haruki
I know would you maybe want to arm
wrestle
I'm wrestling
he liked you
don't you
yeah
I do
ready go
go
can't just win and leave
like
it's been a loser about it
and I've been training ever since so I
can beat you
[Music]
ready go
[Applause]
[Music]
laughs
all right
I did it
finally won
[Music]
I finally won
oh
[Music]
that's right
I won so
I guess this means we gotta get married
now huh
[Music]
seriously
hey what are you crying about
[Music]
laughs
this way
okay is that Yoko
yeah
I'm coming
[Music]
Mr said let's fight together one more
time I don't care what happens to me I
just want to save everyone
[Music]
zero and brother
put that metal in here
you can do it okay
[Music]
I ask that you shared my name Ultraman
sister
Ultraman set Delta rise call
Yoko Yoko
Haruki was Ultraman Zed
do it
finish it Haruki
let's go Mr set it's about time we show
him what we're made of yeah let's Ultra
Cut Loose Haruki okay
[Music]
whoa
another interesting opponent I'll have a
slice
[Music]
computer
[Applause]
[Music]
not good
is this the best you two can do no way
I got to cut a lot of interesting things
it's been fun
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my God
[Music]
[Applause]
you can still go right Mr said
even after tea
[Music]
get down
please
[Music]
let's show some Ultra spirits
thank you
let's go
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yeah
oh my God
okay okay
get up buddy
hey is he okay
I tried to make a cool exit but
I'm drained
dummy
you saved us all you know that oh
okay
it hurts hey uh
it's game over syllabro and you're on
your last life
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's the guy
hey uh captain
we'll see you again right
Maybe
okay I think it's satisfactions
[Laughter]
you're really leaving huh
we're gonna miss you man
thing is there's so many people in the
universe and they're suffering
so Mr Zedd and I have decided to go help
them out
sounds like you
once we make a robot that can go into
space we'll give you a hand
I guess we better get to work huh it's
not so simple
see you
[Music]
see ya
everybody
[Music]
farewell
I'll be back in summer and for New
Year's
are you sure that's even possible why
not
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
of course I'm Immortal plus if I stick
around you too I love my chances of
slicing more amusing things
[Music]
okay
let's find everyone Within Reach
protected are you with me
you bet
this is only the beginning Haruki
[Music]
if you have nowhere to go would you stay
and master the cosmo Beast style the
cosmo b style
continue your basic training to
understand your true strength that's why
you must commune with a cosmo Beast
learn to control your emotions when you
fight
I've been Spirit crane strike
so we can be
at bond with
we're in this together
could it be I am bulletin Admiral the
magma invasion of anyone who wishes to
die step forward just you wait Vulcan
okay
[Applause]
I need to get stronger will you train me
do you want that Cosmo Beast Fighters
and planet l77
full of strengths strongest fighting
style of the universe ends today
I am
Grand Master of the cosmo peace Style
regulos of the red dragon white tiger
fist
oh my God
he did not come here