Did you know that the James Webb Space
Telescope just uncovered something
extraordinary? Scientists have
discovered little red dots, mysterious
objects that could reveal how super
massive black holes formed in the early
universe. These tiny red hued objects
are scattered across deep space, hidden
behind thick gas clouds, making them
difficult to detect until now. Their
spectra reveal gas moving at over 1,000
km per second. A clear sign of a rapidly
growing black hole at their core. But
here's the mystery. They don't emit
X-rays or radio waves like normal active
galaxies. Instead, they shine brightly
in infrared, suggesting they are young
black holes trapped inside dense ionized
gas. This hidden phase of black hole
growth may explain how the first super
massive black holes in the universe
formed so quickly. This discovery
challenges our understanding of galaxy
and black hole evolution. To learn more
about this fascinating cosmic discovery,
watch our full video now. See you there.