[Music]
we sweat when the weather gets warm
as sweats cool down our temperature
drops
this is because sweats take the heat
away from our skin as they evaporate
when liquid evaporates and take heat
away from the surroundings it is called
latent heat of vaporization
the bigger the latent heat of
vaporization the more heat it takes away
an air conditioner uses refrigerant with
large evaporative latent heat
let's assume a refrigerant in a hot room
the refrigerant will take away heat from
its surroundings to evaporate
if we enlarge the area of contact of the
refrigerant to the air the refrigerant
will take away more heat
when we blow wine from behind the
refrigerant
air that lost heat becomes cooler and
the a cool breeze comes out from the
front
the refrigerant used in an air
conditioner tends to evaporate easily
and have high latent heat of
vaporization which make it perfect for a
cooling device
now to understand how an air conditioner
works let's follow the flow of a
refrigerant
first let's look at the general flow
this is a compressor
if we compare a refrigerant to blood a
compressor is like the heart
a compressor circulates a refrigerant
and compress it with high temperature
and pressure
then the refrigerant pressed by the
compressor flows to a condenser
while evaporation is the transition of
liquid to gas through heat absorption
condensation is the transition of gas to
liquid when it loses heat
a condenser serves to turn refrigerant
in hot gas state into liquid form by
taking away its heat
the refrigerant passed through a
condenser becomes liquid and flows into
expansion valve
there is a section in the expansion
valve where the piping gets narrow and
as the refrigerant passes here it splits
up into many pieces
what we see here is similar to the
principle behind water being spread from
spray
as the pressure on the refrigerant drops
its temperature drops dramatically as
well
the refrigerant with lowered temperature
then goes into an evaporator to steal
away heat
an evaporator is literally a device that
evaporates liquid into gas
cooled refrigerant steels away the heat
in the room and evaporates
the compressor and condenser are built
inside the outdoor unit of an air
conditioner
the evaporator and expansion valve are
built within the indoor unit of an air
conditioner which is what we normally
refer to when we talk about air
conditioner
now let's dive deeper into the functions
of each mechanical components of an air
conditioner
in the evaporator refrigerant loses heat
and is evaporated as gas into the
compressor
when a piston compresses the gas
refrigerant its pressure rises and so
does its temperature
we use products of spray type sometimes
you might have come across insect
repellent spray or butane fuel canister
whose surface of the can gets cooler
after use
this is because the pressure inside the
product has become lower if pressure is
lowered temperature is lowered and if
pressure goes up temperature also rises
now coming back to the case of an air
conditioner when gas with low pressure
and temperature is pressed by piston its
pressure rises and so does its
temperature
however more air conditioners nowadays
use scroll type of compressor rather
than piston type
in a scroll compressor there are two
scrolls of which one is fixed and the
other rolls constantly
as more air coming through the entrance
gets inside the scroll space becomes
crowded
as there is less space now gas becomes
more compressed and is discharged from
the middle of the scroll in a compressed
state
the reason for using such type of a
compressor is the efficiency of space
utilization this type of a compressor
allows the machinery to become smaller
in size and reduces noise as well as
vibration
compressed air is then sent to a
condenser to be pressed into liquid
the temperature of refrigerant passed
through the compressor is above 80
celsius which is in a hot gas state
this refrigerant passes through a
condenser and is cooled down slowly with
chilled air from fans
when liquid evaporates it absorbs heat
and becomes gas
as it transforms into gas its kinetic
energy becomes stronger
when the gas loses heat its kinetic
energy becomes weaker and it becomes
liquid
in other words chilled gas becomes
a refrigerant and gas state of high
temperature loses heat as it passes
through a condenser
as such it becomes condensed and at the
exit it turns into liquid almost
although the refrigerant has thrown off
some of the heat as it passes through a
condenser
it is still hot with temperature at
about 50 celsius
the refrigerant in high temperature and
high pressure liquid flows into
expansion valve
the refrigerant which used to flow in
large space now passes through narrow
area and its pressure drops as it goes
when the pressure drops temperature
drops dramatically as well
the cool refrigerant is now sent to an
evaporator
expansion valve are connected to
sensible heat storage that detects heat
sensible heat storage is installed on
the exit of an evaporator and detects
temperature
inside the storage is fluid sensitive to
temperature changes and as the
temperature at the exit of an evaporator
rises
the gas pressure rises which in turn
presses on a spring to send more
refrigerant to evaporator when the
amount of refrigerant going into
evaporator surges cooling emission
surges too when the temperature at the
exit of an evaporator drops
gas pressure drops and the amount of
refrigerant going into evaporator in
turn drops too
applying the above principle an air
conditioner controls the amount of
refrigerant injected into an evaporator
to prevent over cooling
a refrigerant passes through the pipes
of an evaporator and takes away heat in
this process
as the pan underneath starts to operate
warm air in the room is sent to an
evaporator and cooled air is emitted
fans used in the indoor unit of an air
conditioner is shaped as cylinder rather
than the more familiar version of
propeller
such type of a fan is called impeller
as wall mounted air conditioners cannot
take up large space impeller type of fan
is used instead of propeller type
when you leave a cold glass in the air
its surfaces is covered with water this
is because gas has lost heat to be
condensed
pipes flowing with cold refrigerant are
also covered with water drops on the
surface
the water here is stored in drain pan
and when there is certain amount stored
the water is discharged through the pipe
and out to the world
[Music]
you