[Music]
so today's how to build is on all these
new Block City
buildings so one of the first things I
want to talk about is that um many of
these buildings I built at various
different scales so these all appear in
the uh spelt interview when mfos is
using them like dominoes to knock each
other down and a trick I used is that at
the end of one shot I might have a
building this size being knocked down by
something and then next shot I would cut
to something that was this size which is
supposed to be the same building but it
allowed me to change from various scales
so that's how I uh sort of pulled that
off and um in the description I'll link
to a page where I talk about that a
little bit more but um this little guy
is just
uh alternating rows of uh clear 1X two
plates and tan 2x3 plates so Al together
it's 1 2 3 4 five six 7 eight nine 10 11
there so Al together it's 2 4 6 8 10 12
14 16 18 19 tall and then this guy over
here is just about uh three times that
size so uh around the clear level are
two tall um 1 by two clear plates and
I've got three
2x4s to make a uh
4x6 and down here I actually have a 4x6
so again it's just a whole bunch of
layers of that uh I think I just did as
many as I had tan plates to do it with
but uh you can see that these uh
basically same idea but on smaller
scales uh similarly this little black
building is uh supposed to be the same
thing as this big black
building hold on for a second
it's hard to see black of course but uh
so this little
guy he's got uh this is two 1x4 plates a
uh 1x4 Arch that's too tall those are
connected to two 2x4 plate or 2 by sorry
these are all bricks 2x4 bricks then a
2x4 plate on top we've got a 1x two
brick with a little uh roof piece on top
uh same thing on the other side and then
the middle is a cone with a chees slope
you can see that it uh has some of the
same ideas is this big guy but just in a
smaller
form and the big one
uh along the back is you know this is
just built up with a lot of
brick uh but the
bottom I've got this Arch on the inside
and then arch in front of that which
I've filled out with brick that connect
down through
uh and then just got you know this is a
five tall area so again I'm using the
tall bricks on the
edges so yeah this is just like a um 8X
4X five with a couple arches set into it
and up here uh pull off the stuff this
is just a big uh Castle piece and then
I've just filled in some
brick behind it
and then on top we got the uh big nose
cone
piece uh top with a cheese slope so same
as the little building but bigger scale
and this is this weird engine piece uh
with a cheese slope on the top and then
this weird like shoulder pad plate a 2X
two tile and this uh 2x3 plate with the
round hole on the end
and again doing the same thing on both
sides but in
reverse
and just sticking the bottom of the
engines on and you get that so yeah
that's that
building so to fill out the city I have
a lot of really small simple buildings
that are just one bright color uh you
know I like bright colors that's why I
play with Lego so when I was building
designing new Block City I wanted each
building to basically be one color so I
just took all of my bricks of each color
and then looked for cool pieces so in t
or in lime green I had this
cool uh sort of quarter Circle piece two
of those and uh put a little tie on top
to hide the studs and then these are
just some 2x3 bricks down there thought
that looked like a cool little building
um this is a weird shade of brown that I
don't think has been in use for a while
never really got used very much to begin
with or is this the new nougat color I'm
not sure but anyway had these uh big
slopes just made them go alternating and
then just filled out the bottom and top
with some bricks and again when it's off
at a distance it just looks like a a
building and then this is
a a weird shade of purple more magenta
than the dark purple but uh I had a cone
so 2 by two bricks and a
cone uh some other small
buildings uh my turquoise bricks I had
one of these uh weird guys and uh you
can stick a plate back into the hole
right there so I did that uh this is you
know another Hammerhead sort of shape uh
these are the pin connectors from
Technic I think these are all from the
old rock Raider series cuz they had
turquoise in it I had a bunch of 1 by
tws and uh just topped it off like that
this uh purple one you'll notice there's
a little blue in there cuz I didn't have
a lot in purple basically it's all held
together by an axle that's anchored on
those plates and then uh these wheels
are from the old Night Bus not sure if
they're on the new one haven't gotten
that and then at the bottom again I've
got a another blue cylinder plate so
this can actually attach and then I had
this purple roof piece so uh that just
makes a nice and I like the way the
holes you know the gaps between the the
wheels add some character to the
building uh you know and it does look
like a building whereas this doesn't
really look like a building but I think
it's cool
anyway uh so this red building is mostly
just uh this piece and uh you know this
is from the old mtron sets but I flipped
it around so it becomes a w
building and uh then I just filled out
the bottom here so that's a 2X two brick
some 1X two plates with a 2x3 slope and
some 1x3 slopes on the side so it fills
out and sort of looks like
something uh some other small scale
buildings getting a little larger now so
this guy is h a whole bunch of these one
by two plates with the little uh groove
on the side so so I had a whole bunch of
those and I also had bunch of this 1X
two plate that has a little ladder so uh
I just found out what
height uh you know I needed to have
between the ladders to make them all
line up nicely and that ended up being
uh five plates tall so I've got groups
of five of these that are in between and
then at each layer I've got a ladder
brick and a uh 1X two plate
and it's just a whole bunch of that unit
stacked on top of each other and then
uh hold on one second at the top I'm
using the uh grill plates cuz obviously
we want to continue all these cool lines
on the
top uh this dark green building uh you
know sort of has the shape of a
traditional
skyscraper uh I just had one of these
pieces you know so goes from 2x two to
1x one and I just stuck one of those
long uh 1ex one bricks and on some 2x
two
bricks this uh Brown building highlights
the uh Treasure Chest at the top which I
thought was a it's a cool piece to not
use for a treasure chest so thought it
had some architectural niceness and then
because it has the little handle on the
side wanted to mimic that some so uh
this is like a door hinge piece that I
had a bunch of in Brown cuz they used it
as a tree piece back in the old uh River
Retreat set and then you know we've got
an arch on a front and a door window
here and then the rest is just some some
basic bricks and again using grill
plates on the top because the studs just
didn't work with this
one um we'll leave that one for now this
one um so I made this to go on the
street next to the uh micro green
grosser and the micro scale movie
theater so it's supposed to sort of be a
building at that scale which is slightly
different some of some of these others
and I had that uh 1 by two brick with
the ice cream on it so I thought this is
sort of like an ice cream parlor and I
wanted to use the dark red that's in the
ice cream so I just got out all my dark
red pieces and put together this roof so
you know these are Technic axle bricks
some roof
pieces uh some of those curvy
slopes this plate is a a weird curvy
plate but I like the way it uh curves it
down and then these are some regular
slopes here so again you can see that uh
just sort of fit that all onto some
white plates and then uh or white
bricks and uh got some columns down here
but again the bottom just some arches
and some basic
bricks so yeah
that's that
one uh this yellow building uh is
actually built you know to stand up not
the way studs are so uh I had some of
the this piece and thought they would
make a cool front of a building and I
had this weird these weird pieces I
don't know it's a weird curvy slope and
again that 2 by two
plate that sort of Curves
down uh I just thought that gave it a
nice little top and just put a little 1X
two plate there and I just built a whole
bunch of plates to run along and uh fill
out the bottom and then uh put it all
back together and stands up has a sort
of nice
silhouette uh this eye building uh I had
a whole I have a whole bunch of this IP
from uh pick a brick and I thought it
would make a cool little building here
so uh again based on the eyepiece I just
pulled the color scheme from the rest of
the building uh for that so got one by
one
uh cylinder bricks in white and a bunch
of 4x4 plates in black and just built a
whole bunch of levels of that and then
it's uh again when you put it in the
background it doesn't look
as weird as when it's all by itself but
uh you know sort of interesting
building um these two are both built on
the same principle of uh these uh half
octagon plates so I have a whole bunch
of those in green and uh I had some in
transparent red so I wanted to
capitalize on that so for the Green
Building just pull part of level here
you can see that uh these are just again
a whole bunch of probably pick a brick
uh one by one transparent yellow
pieces uh stacked up and then I have a
2X two and a
1x4 freaking green so that the windows
are just along the sides here and then
uh a whole bunch of those plates and
then again just stacking up a bunch of
levels of
that uh and this works on the same
principle except I had enough
transparent red that uh I didn't have
any one by one bricks that were Square
so I have the column cylinder ones along
the edges and uh having the uh plate and
trans red and then uh some trans red
bricks in the middle and then this was
as tall as this building could be
obviously not quite as tall as this but
they uh you know work
well this uh gold building
I had a whole bunch of these gold 2x4s
from the uh 50th
anniversaries and then um you can see
actually that there's two different
shades of gold here but
um if we look at this level uh I also
had a couple 2x2s I think those all came
together so this is a 2X two 2x two 2x4
and then the top is some more 2x4s and
then uh you know I just rummaged through
all my gold pieces and had a whole bunch
of uh this slope topper and again this
weird curvy brick which I believe is
from the Indiana Jones uh Arc of the
Covenant piece so uh and then some gold
jumper plates with gold studs and just
sort of filled it out to uh look nice so
yeah and I really want to build this at
a larger scale but I don't have the gold
pieces for that so I'll just have to
stay at this SC for
now uh this Orange Building is really
weird doesn't really look like a
building but again I just had these
weird orange pieces and wanted to figure
out how to use them so I'll take this
one apart
actually so uh down
here we've got these
uh again I think these are exoforce
pieces maybe sort of a curvy down slope
got four of those with uh this curvy
brick
they're all sitting on um some
plates so basically there's two 2x4
plates with a 2x6 plate 2x two plates so
those are all sitting on top of that and
then at the bottom here we're just
filling it out with uh these
uh bricks that go out and then
uh one by two bricks then uh
the whole kitten Kaboodle how does this
go hold on one second that goes like
that right so then
um this is a 2x4 brick and a 1x6 these
pieces do not actually connect this way
so this will just sort of slide together
and be held on like that in a second and
so then this contraption over here you
can see it's a 2x6 plate and then I got
some Technic bricks here so some orange
with a hole in the Middle where I've put
in uh again our favorite little half
stud piece two of those sticking out and
this one's got the two holes in a 1 by
two
brick um and then 1x4 up there and then
uh this is some upside down slope pieces
that again might be from the SpongeBob
set or the recycling truck from town and
uh put a 1x4 tile on that and that's
what's going to slide into that space
down
there and if we top this off with 2x6
plate we got this uh piece to connect
these two together so they actually fit
together I like the way that the um you
know I built this so that the lines of
the weird pieces on the front would be
matched by the middle
stuff um so even though this is a crazy
looking building it still sort of has
nice looking lines
and again these slope pieces we're going
to put on so the hole right here fits on
the half pin and then on the top we've
got these uh little plates with wings
some more curvy
pieces and uh two of those and uh sort
of looks like a little person I actually
uh plan to during the Orange versus
green War have these two buildings fight
each other uh this one sort of looks
like a samur
guy and this one sort of looks like I
don't know someone with big ears maybe
but uh this Samurai
building also is a a strange little one
so let me take this apart so this one is
held together almost entirely by these
uh camera bricks right here so
uh basically just stacked three of those
together and then
uh this partial Travis brick down at the
bottom and then this is a uh
1x10 plate and then I've got some these
1 by two cheese grater pieces some more
plates in a brick so I made two of
these and these are the side of the
building and they
uh line
up uh pretty pretty
good into
here not exactly connected but so you
have to pull them apart a little
bit and then
uh put those there so that gives you a
nice solid base to work
on and then the front pieces so well at
the top these are the curvy Arch some
chees slopes a 1x two plate so that gets
to be our little Samurai
head then in front uh we're doing this
weird I guess it's for car
bumpers um and then uh 1X two plate so
that goes right there so then um this
piece has got two 2x3 plates a whole
bunch of these cheese grater plates or
slopes cuz I had a whole bunch of them
and this building was a way to use them
up uh 1x4 tile down the center this is
going to go on this top camera brick
this is just a little piece with some
cheese slopes on a plate that goes right
there this bottom one is a uh 1x4
2x4 uh and then I got this curvy slope
piece with a plate on the bottom more
cheese graters more cheese
slopes and then this fits right across
the bottom and then um you know you've
got this nice stud connection on the
bottom so you can actually connect it to
something so this is just a 2x6 plate so
that it has a little more stability
obviously 2x7 would be perfect but they
don't make that size so uh that's that
building then uh this big gray
one
um so uh it's only two studs thick but
uh got an arch piece here some big slope
pieces these are just basic bricks and
the back fills it out uh some window
train window pieces here that's a plate
um some little 1x3 arches and then you
know keeping that hole there with the
bricks standard bricks some taller train
window pieces some inverse of the big
slope and this deal at the top here sort
of looks like elephant
ears so
uh on top of all that there's a 2x6
plate the uh Wing seat piece it's a a
plate with some cheese
slopes uh again plate with cheese slopes
there then this big piece which is
sometimes used in
vehicles um just put in a 1 by two tile
there fits very nicely over this big
Contraption and gives some nice top and
then uh again this weird 2 by two slope
piece I like that little face there not
that you see that uh so that's that
building then the last three that I'm
going to
do um also exist as larger versions but
uh I think the way most of these was
created that I built the large building
first and then I just shrunk it down to
make the small building so this is the
blue Bank building it's got a big b on
the front so each of these is a technic
brick that I've just uh put a
transparent brick into plate rather so
this is a 1x4 Technic brick these are
two 1X tws a 1x4 2 1X tws 1x4 and then I
just made these three blue and the rest
yellow and then you get the little be
there um so that's the whole front and
then an arch and some bricks and a
little plate bottom the whole back is
just standard brick and uh we've got
these curvy arches at the
top so it's a 2 x two brick the curvy
arches some 1 by two plates and a 2 by
two tile the very top so that's the blue
Bank building then you get this hotel
Pink hotel which sort of looks like
Pepto Bisal um bottle um so this used up
a lot of my clear pieces so the interior
here is basically all um 1X two clear
plates stacked on top of each other so
sometimes they go back and sometimes
they go across and they alternate a
little bit to get it some
stability um and
then I had a mixture of uh so basically
in the back you'll see the the pink juts
in that's because otherwise this pink
side piece would not be connected to the
rest of the building unless you did some
slope on the bottom so I had a 2X two
pink piece here this is mostly 1X one um
pieces except for the bottom which is a
1x two there's a 1x two that sticks in
that's the same on both sides and then
this up here is all one by one pink
pieces and it's held together by these
uh 2x two uh downward slope transparent
pieces the center is a mixture of bricks
and plates that are
transparent and at the very top I've got
two 1ex one round plates that I'm
sticking right in the middle there not
the sturdiest con connection but it
looks good and then this uh I think this
is more of a residential building
probably an apartment
building this one I built the small
version first and then built the big
version
afterwards um but uh again these are I
got a whole pick a brick full of these 1
by two clear plates which is why I have
them in so many buildings but uh we just
got 2x3 plates and then these plates
which have the lines going either way I
chose to have them all
horizontal
um and then at the top here you've got
this handle piece and uh tile on the top
and then just a little 1 by two plate at
the bottom so you know there's like a
little doorway down there so those three
buildings hold on so I've also built
larger versions of these three buildings
as I said before
I can get them in the
shot so uh this red one is the most
recent and I don't think it's actually
showed up in an animation but basically
to mimic the lines on the side of the
building I
uh just took uh these are just you know
some clear bricks and then the rest of
it is basically red plates and here's an
arch to mimic the little hole at the
bottom but this is just layers of plates
stick sticking out alternating
throughout and uh at the top using some
big slopes to mimic that so um again
there's not much to this building it's
just basically layers of of patterns and
that's what a lot of buildings in real
life look like so you know I don't mind
doing that here uh this building I I
have gray pieces in here cuz I just
don't have big pink plates but all the
pink in this is side from this little
Arch is a 1ex one brick cuz I got that a
whole bunch of those in pick a brick and
then the windows here are the uh 1X twox
two tall windows again from pick a brick
and uh got a whole bunch of uh gray
plates as I said and then just built it
sort of telescoping up so you know each
different level is
uh gets smaller and smaller and then the
top I've used some
let me Orient it this way some wind a
windscreen piece and then I've got a
whole bunch of these uh 2 by two
downward slopes in
transparent um a couple bricks in there
and then topping it off with the little
witch's globe or crystal ball which uh
again is imitated by that piece down
there and then the blue Bank
building um so again again I had a whole
pick a brick full of these 1X two bricks
in transparent blue so I made that the
front and the back and the side of the
buildings sorry the front is um a whole
bunch of yellow uh transparent plates
and some blue transparent plates filled
in to make the be so
um I'll just sort of slowly pan up on
this so you can copy the pattern if you
want
to but uh you know I built the B first
and then
uh built the building around it the top
I decided to make it all transparent
even though the little one is not just
because I had more transparent blue
bricks so I had some the 2 by two
downward slopes again and the rest is
just one by two brick then I'm topping
it off with tile because uh
studs just didn't make sense down here I
just did some random detailing on the
door so I didn't have a big arch piece
so I used some upward slopes then inside
rather than just filling out with brick
I've got some downward slopes so you get
these weird
shapes and I just imagine that this is
its address it's number five on the
street rather than it being its racing
number these are those half octogonal
plates just three stacked on top and
these are the uh sort of wing brick
piece that we've uh used in other
builds so yeah and then there's just a
little doorway down there at the bottom
so
uh yeah that is uh basically how I've
built uh all these different buildings
uh so now you can put them all together
and have your own little uh downtown new
Block City
[Music]
[Applause]