you can't break this curse but there are
ways around it like a transplant spell
you thought about that but what ises he
know he going to trust me and annoying
clown I've studied with the master for
centuries before you these guys are fate
swappy runes find a relative willing to
sacrifice their life have them put one
Rune on themselves and the other on the
cursed individual and then instead of
him the relative would go
boom what are you doing I've decided to
swap my life for that of my sons the
stays between you and me ultimately your
sacrifice would just go to waste the
demon pill will bring disaster and the
Supreme Lord will never let him go I
will use the remaining two years I have
left to make him a warrior the people
shall see him as a hero no I can't allow
it if you won't allow it when the
lightning strikes during the Heavenly
Calamity I will die with Neja uh who is
Neja he is my son