hey guys welcome to prancing postcard in
tv kids workout series today we are
doing a super fun
spider-man workout i've got grayson here
helping me
if you like videos like these please
subscribe and hit the notification bell
also stay tuned to the very end and join
me for a spider-man
dance party
[Music]
all right before we get started we're
going to make sure we can do our
spider-man
sweat throwing hands so can you guys
show me your web throwing hands
awesome all right and the first move
we're gonna do we're gonna lunge to the
side and we're gonna
throw a web so we're gonna lunge and
throw the web all right and come back
let's do the other side
all right lunch on the other side show
me a deep lunge
awesome again
how deep can you lunge
good and again
one more time on each side oh you look
awesome
now we're gonna get down and we're gonna
do spider-man crawl
so let's get low to the ground here you
can put your
web throwing hand out and place one foot
forward and then we go
back foot front foot and glide across
the room
you can kind of stick your front foot
out as you go
let's try that on the other side
awesome switching sides again
and switching again
you look amazing
we'll try that one more time on this
side
and again this is hard work for the legs
and coming back up spiderman
can climb up walls so we are gonna do
some climbing up a wall and get ready
and let's show me how fast you can climb
up a wall
keep on going climbing a big high rise
awesome job we reached the top all right
now we're going to pretend to be the
spider that bit spiderman that turned
him into spider-man
so let's get down on the ground and
we're going to do crab walks but they're
kind of going to be spider walks
and let's go forward
backwards
[Music]
all right and let's kick our legs up
and let's go round in a circle
awesome let's go the other way
[Music]
amazing spider-man runs
super fast so let's get up and i want to
see how fast
you can run you can run around the room
or you can run in a spot but show me how
fast you can run
[Music]
keep going you are so fast
we're almost there
you made it all right now we're going to
do some spider-man
punches and kicks so let's put our feet
apart
get nice and low and we're going to
punch three times
one two three and then we're going to
kick to the side
punch one two three kick
one two three kick great
one two three yes
one two three same side one
two three one two
three one two three
kick nice one more time on this side
all right let's switch sides getting
nice and low
and punch one two three kick other side
one two three one two three
one two three one last time one two
three
yes now we pretend we've got a bad guy
coming towards us so let's get
nice and low and we can punch
and then throw a spiderweb
and duck because now they're going to
get us and duck low
all right and punch one two three three
spider webs
[Music]
oh looking good one two three
one more time one two three spider web
and duck down other side
awesome now we've got guys coming from
both sides so we're gonna have to
do a lunge and punch one two
three and other side one
two three other side
oh looking great one two three other
side
one two three other side one two three
we're protecting from all sides
one two three awesome the next move
we're gonna do is a spider-man
cartwheel so if you're not sure how to
do a cartwheel make sure that you have
an adult with you or you can do a
somersault
or another move instead but we're gonna
do a cartwheel but keep our hands and
our legs a little bit
bent all right i'll go first and then
grayson you can have a turn
pointing your foot and
all right grayson your turn
awesome you guys look great at home too
i'm gonna take another turn while you
guys keep practicing at home
awesome all right now let's take the
opportunity to do some cool spider-man
jump poses so we are going to jump up
and for example
you could go
whatever pose you think is cool
oh you guys look amazing
[Music]
yes all right now we have done lots of
working out we're gonna do some
spider-man stretches
we're gonna do a warrior three pose we
can turn to the side
and you can either leave your back leg
on we'll put our spidey hands out to the
side
and if you can lift off behind you
it's okay if you fall over try again
all right coming out let's twist to the
other side
finding your balance on one foot
lifting that back foot off
awesome all right let's do some
lunges side to side lunge
switching back and forth
let's add some spidey hands
[Music]
getting nice and low one last one
good now let's do some quad stretches
you can either hold on to a wall here
or a chair and let's grab one foot
and stretch pointing our knee down let's
stretch through our quads
we can point our spiny hand out if you
like
good let's stretch the other quad
[Music]
releasing out let's shake it out
you guys did amazing thank you so much
for joining us i hope you had fun on
that
spider-man workout if you want to see
more videos like these
please subscribe hit the notification
bell and give this video a thumbs up and
share it with another friend that you
think would like it
we also love to see you guys working out
on instagram you can tag us at pregnancy
and postpartum tv
thanks so much you guys are epic bye
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
good
bye