Hey guys this is Evan from EZ Origami!
And today I'll be teaching you how to
fold an origami Royal Rose Cube designed
by Maria Sinayskaya. This is a beautiful
modular design and it's perfect for
Mother's Day. This model requires six
square sheets of paper. Each unit is
folded from one square, and in order to
fold each unit you'll eventually divide
the paper into thirds. So instead of
approximating, I'll teach you how to make
a folding tool which will help you
quickly divide each square into thirds. You will need 6 squares to fold the
units and you'll need an additional
square of the same size for the folding
tool, so you'll need a total of 7 equally
sized squares. And I recommend using 6
inch or larger squares with the same
color on both sides to fold this model.
Using 6 inch squares will result in a
model about 3.5 inches wide.
Thicker paper such as tant and
stardream also seem to work really well
with this model. And I'm going to be
using larger paper with color on one
side and white on the other just to make
it a bit easier to follow along. And
we're going to start by making the
folding tool. So take 1 square and make
sure it's the same size as the other 6
squares that you will use for the units.
And once you've prepared your paper, then
we're going to start by folding in half
diagonally. So take this bottom right
corner and fold it up to the top left
corner. Align the corners on the edges,
then make your crease, and then unfold.
And now we're going to fold up this
bottom edge and align it with the
diagonal crease that we just created. So
I'm just going to pull up the bottom
edge like this. And we want to start at
the bottom left corner and work our way
up and over to the right aligning that
edge with the crease, just like this. And
once everything is aligned, then you can
make your crease and then you can unfold.
Then we're going to rotate the paper so
that the two creases we just made now
extend from this top right corner. And
from here we're going to fold over this
right edge and align it with this top
crease that we just made. So we're going
to start by pulling this right edge over
to the left. And we want to start at the
top right corner and work our way down
and over to the left until the entire
edge is aligned with that crease, just
like this. And then you can make your
crease. And then you can unfold. And now I
want you to notice this point here where
the crease that we just made intersects
with this bottom edge. And what we want
to do is fold this bottom right corner
over to align with that point. So we're
just going to pull over the right edge
of the paper,
just like this, until that bottom corner
aligns with that intersection. And before
you make your crease, you want to make
sure that the vertical edges on the
top and the bottom of the model are
aligned as well. And once everything is
aligned, then you can make your crease. Then we're going to rotate the paper 180
degrees. And this is your completed
folding tool. And once you have this, then
you're going to take one of the six
squares that you prepared for the units
and you're going to hold it with the
white side up. Then we're going to lift
up our first square and we want to slide
it in between the two layers of the
folding tool by pushing it over to the
left as far as it'll go. You want to push
it over until the left edge of the
square aligns with this left folded edge
on the folding tool. And from here we're
going to fold over the right edge of our
square and align it with this colored
edge on the folding tool. So we're just
going to pull over the right edge of the
paper, just like this, until both of those
colored edges are aligned. Then you can
make your crease. And then we can pull
our square outside of the folding tool. And then you can put the folding tool
aside. Then you can unfold this colored
flap and then we want to fold over this
left edge and align it with the vertical
crease that we just created. So we're
just going to lift up this left edge and
pull it over to the right until the
colored edge is completely aligned with
that vertical crease. Then you can make
your crease. And then you can unfold. And
now you'll see that you've divided your
square into thirds. Then we're going to
turn the paper over and we want to fold
up this bottom right corner and align it
with this rightmost vertical crease. So
we're just going to pull the bottom
right corner over to the left, and once
this small white edge aligns with that
vertical crease, then you can make your
crease. And now we're going to fold over
the bottom left corner and align it with
that same vertical crease. So we're just
going to pull that corner over to the
right, just like this. And once the white
edge is aligned with that vertical
crease and the flap that we just folded over, then you can make your crease. And
then you can unfold. Then we're going to
rotate the paper 180 degrees and we're
going to do the same exact thing. So once
again we're going to start with this
bottom right corner and we want to align
it with this rightmost vertical crease.
So we're just going to pull that corner over
to the left, and once the small white
edge is aligned with that vertical
crease then you can make your crease.
Then we're going to fold over this
bottom left corner and again align it
with the rightmost vertical crease. So
we're just going to pull it over to the
right, just like this. And you'll see that the white corner
will also align with this crease
intersection here. Then you can make your
crease and then you can unfold. And then
we're going to turn the paper over. And
now we're going to make a crease the
pivots from this bottom corner here. So
what we want to do is lift up this
bottom right corner, and we want to
slightly pinch the paper at that point just so that our crease starts there. Then we want to pivot this colored flap around that point, just like this. And we
want to adjust it until this colored corner aligns with this vertical crease
here. And once this edge reaches those
two reference points, then you can make
your crease. Then we're going to rotate
the paper 180 degrees and we're going to
do the same exact thing. So we're just
going to lift up the bottom right corner
and we want to slightly pinch the paper
at that point just to make sure our
crease starts there. Then you want to
slightly adjust this colored flap while
pivoting around that point until this
colored corner aligns with this vertical
crease. And once the edge reaches both of
those references, then you can make your
crease. And from here we're going to fold
over the right side of the model along
this existing vertical crease. And we're
going to do that by pulling the right
side of the model over to the left, but
we don't want to crease all the way. We
want to start at the top of the model
and work our way down until you reach
this point here where the diagonal
crease intersects with the crease that
we just made. Then from here we want to
fold this colored flap over to the right
along that existing diagonal crease. So
we're simply going to fold it over like
this, then you want to reinforce that
crease along the inside of the model,
just like this. And at this point you'll
notice that the model does not lie flat.
And the idea is to keep this edge curved
to give the unit a more organic shape. So
what we want to do is fold that edge
over to the inner colored edge here. So
we're just going to align both of those
edges, just like this. And as you're
making this crease, you'll notice that
you're just reinforcing a crease on a
layer below. And you want to make sure
that you don't completely flatten out
the model because we want to keep this
edge curved. And once you have that, then
we're going to rotate the paper 180
degrees and we're going to do the same
thing. So again we're going to start by
folding the right side of the model over
to the left along this existing vertical
crease here. So we're just going to pull
it over to the left like this, but again
we don't want to crease all the way. We
want to start at the top of the model
and work our way down until you reach
this point here where the diagonal
crease intersects with the crease that
we were just making. Then we want to fold
this colored flap over to the
right along that existing diagonal
crease. So we're just going to fold it
over like that, and you carefully want to
reinforce that crease along the inside
of the model. And again you'll notice
this curved edge here. And what we want
to do is fold that edge over to the left
along this white edge inside. So we're
just going to fold the edge in along that
white edge there, and again you're just
reinforcing an existing crease on a
layer below. And you don't want to
completely flatten out the model because
we want to leave this part curved to
give the unit a more organic shape. And
once you've done that on both sides then
we're going to slightly rotate the model. And now I want you to notice this white
triangular flap here. And what we want to
do is grab those layers from underneath
just to untuck it a bit. Then from here
we want to talk this white triangular
flap underneath this colored layer below. So we're going to do that by lifting up
the model, and we carefully want to slide
that triangular flap underneath the
colored layer like this as far as it'll
go. So just slide it all the way inside,
flatten out the right side of the model,
and then you can put everything back
down. And once you have that, then we're
going to rotate the paper 180 degrees
and we're going to do the same thing. So
once again, we want to untuck this white
triangular flap here by simply grabbing
those layers from underneath. Then we
want to tuck that white triangular flap
underneath this colored layer below. So
we're just going to lift up the model
and we're going to carefully slide that
white flap underneath the colored layer
just like this. And then you can flatten
out the right side of the model. And now
we're going to make two mountain folds
along these vertical edges here. But I
find it easiest to do that by turning
the model over. And you'll notice that
it's a similar shape to a Sonobe unit.
So what we want to do from here is fold
this top right corner over to the top
left corner. So we're going to carefully
fold all the layers over to the left
like this until both of those points are
aligned. And you want to make your crease
through all layers except for this outer
layer here because, as you can see from
the side, we want to keep that layer
curved. And once you've made that crease
all the way through then you can unfold. Then we're going to rotate the paper 180
degrees and do the same exact thing. So
again we're going to fold the top right
corner over to the top left corner and
we're going to carefully fold over all
layers just like this. Then you can make
your crease through all layers except
for that outer layer because again we
want to keep that curved. Then you can
unfold and turn the model back over. And
this
is one completed unit. Now you must fold
five more. And once you fold at all six
units, you're going to need two to start
the assembly. Then look at one and you'll
notice that it has a triangular flap
like this on each side and it also has a
pocket underneath these curved layers
here on each side. So once again we're
going to take our second unit, and what
we want to do is insert the second unit's
flap inside of the first unit's pocket. And we're going to do that by lifting up
both units and then we carefully want to
bring them together, again making sure
that the second unit's flap goes inside
of the first unit's pocket. Then we just
want to push the two units together
until they're completely aligned at the
top and the bottom. And now you've
connected the first two units. Then we're
going to slightly rotate the model so
that we're looking at the front face of
the second unit, and then we want to add
a third unit the same way. So once again
we're going to insert the third unit's
flap inside of the second unit's pocket
just like we did before. So we're going
to lift up all three units and then we
want to bring the second and third units
together, again making sure that the
third unit's flap goes inside of the
second unit's pocket as far as it'll go.
Then you just want to push the two units
together until they're aligned at the
top and the bottom. And now you've
connected three units. And now we want to
connect the first and third units
together. So we're going to slightly
rotate the model so that we're looking
at the front face of the third unit here.
And then we want to insert the first
unit's flap inside of the third unit's
pocket just like we've been doing. So
we're simply going to lift the first
units flap out from behind and we're
carefully going to tuck it inside of the
third unit's pocket just like we did
before. So you carefully want to bring
the first and third units together, and
you want to push them together until
they're completely aligned. And if you
turn the model over, you can see that
we've already assembled half the cube. So
we just have to add the other three
units the same exact way. So we're just
going to turn the model back over and
then you can pick any of the three units
to work with. I'm going to pick this
third unit here that we just added, and
I'm going to rotate the model so that we
can see the front face of that unit. And
then you'll notice this open pocket on
the right side of the third unit. And
that's where we're going to add our
fourth unit. So we're simply going to
insert the fourth unit's flap inside of
the third unit's pocket just like we've
been doing. So just bring the two units
together like this until they're
completely aligned. Then we're going to
slightly rotate the model so that we can
see the
face of the fourth unit. And you'll see
this unused flap on the left. And what we
want to do is tuck that flap inside of
the open pocket on the fourth unit. So
we're just going to bring those two
units together, just like we did before,
by inserting the flap inside of the
unused pocket. And just like that you can
see we've added another side to the cube. So if you slightly rotate the model, you
can see the four faces of the cube that
we already assembled. And from here we're
going to add a fifth unit the same way. So what we want to do is start by
inserting the fifth unit's flaps inside
of these two unused pockets on the other
part of the model. So we're carefully
going to bring those three units
together, just like this, by inserting the
fifth unit's flaps inside of the unused
pockets. And just like that we added
another face to the cube. And then you'll
notice this unused flap which we can
insert into one of the open pockets on
the fifth unit. So we're carefully going
to bring those two units together, just
like we did before, by carefully sliding
that flap inside of the fifth unit's
pocket just like this. And we want to
bring all of the units together until
they're completely aligned. And then if
you slightly rotate the model, you'll see
we've connected five faces of the cube. So we just need to place the sixth unit
down on top. And what we want to do first
is insert the sixth unit's flaps inside
these two unused pockets here. So we're
just going to place the sixth unit down on
top while inserting its flaps inside of
the unused pockets on the rest of the
model. So we're just going to bring all
the units together, just like this, until
they're completely aligned. And now we
simply have to insert these two unused
flaps inside of the open pockets on the
sixth unit. So we're just going to
carefully insert those flaps inside the
sixth unit's pockets just like we've been
doing. So we're going to do that on both
sides. Again make sure all of the units
are completely aligned, and now we've
connected all six units. But we want to
slightly rotate the model and you'll see
these points here where three units come
together, and you'll see these three
loose layers of paper. And basically what
we want to do is curl those layers of
paper just to give the model a more
organic shape. It may help to use some
kind of folding tool or a skewer just to
make it a little bit easier, but you can
continue this on all sides of the model.
And once you've done that on all sides,
then your origami Royal Rose Cube is
complete. I hope you've enjoyed this
video tutorial on how to fold an origami
Royal Rose cube designed by Maria Sinayskaya. Feel free to upload photos of your
completed model to the YouTube Gallery
on my website to be featured here in my
next video or simply upload your photos
to Instagram with the hashtag
#ezorigami to be featured here as well. Also, be sure to check out Maria's website,
Flickr, and Instagram feed for more of
her excellent work. I'll post the links
in the video description below. And if
you liked this video, definitely check
out some of the other similar origami
tutorials featured on my YouTube channel
as well. Again, I hope you've enjoyed this
video. Please comment, rate, subscribe, and
thank you for watching!