Raptor it's getting closer go ow fall no
it's getting
closer
uh-oh
ah oh man got
to
oh the
hill get hurry R oh R's getting
closer all right at this Twinkie
man this not going to be
good
twinky I know the
pool
oh oh that's
freezing
I
here hide my foot than I made and if the
dinosaur coming I'll hit it with the
rock so I'll just
wait where's that RoR
man whoo what's that it's an egg karate
jop wow it's a real dinosaur fossil I pr
I think I know which one this is but I
better check with park ranger aing man
that Raptor's coming
quick hey is that another one Wow Karate
Chop
again wow it's another real dinosaur
fossil wow man I got to think of
something to get away from that Raptor
ooh a tranquilizer
dart fire what keeps on getting
stuck there you
go
hey pork Ranger
lb hey were you dreaming again yeah hey
what were you dreaming about uh dinosaur
dinosaur fossils dinosaur fossils oh hey
speaking of dinosaur fossils I got a big
surprise for you where's he going
man oh
well man knew it was just a
dream guess I'm going to go back to HQ
hey Park R Trail B what was that all
about taking off running out of HQ like
that so I had a dream where there was a
raptor chasing me and I found these
dinosaur fossils that were real life
fossils in my forts but it was just a
dream dude that's what's so cool about
the surprise that I have come check it
out yeah let's go check out this bag of
surprises dude wow but why do I get this
big bag of surprises because it's park
ranger appreciation week oh I just
remembered I'm going to go get my stuff
for
you
cool oh oh wait
man my bag's not very big compared to
the bag I gave you how come uh because I
guess I'm a little kid that's why okay
fair enough all right I'll open mine up
here in a minute let's go ahead and
start with yours okay yeah wait wait
wait wait wait check out this new park
ranger hat that I got for you dude than
that's cool oh wait no you can't put it
on like that man you got to take the
other one off yeah there you go all
right put it on now we match huh cool
all right let's see what else is in the
bag okay wait wait wait wait no we wait
on that one I got something even cooler
than that how
about this awesome real life Mosasaur
tooth fossil wow that's so cool you know
normally we just have kind of like the
fake fossils this is a real life Ur
tooth man this is not one of those fake
fossils that we sometimes see this is
real from Morocco and it even comes with
the certificate of authenticity that was
sent to us by a real paleontologist wow
his name is Juan pablor and he runs a
business called Jurassic dreams.com
where he sells real dinosaur fossils he
sent it to us so we could show it to our
fans at home oh look what else I have
Tada you want to check it out with this
magnifying glass and see what it looks
like
yeah that's pretty cool huh oh I see
something yeah a big old Mosasaur tooth
huh does it look real yeah that's a
pretty cool fossil right there right but
I got an even cooler one in there going
to make you wait for it okay okay here
we go see what else we
got check out this Animal Planet dyo
transport Mission
set cool you want to open this bad boy
up okay so this is the Animal Planet
Dino transport mission what do you think
it does huh it just looks like a truck
to
me
oh that's awesome man oh no no no make
it go
[Applause]
again oh it won't stop it won't
stop okay now I've got in this box
another real life dinosaur fossil tooth
and I'm not going to tell you what
fossil it is you have to guess it okay
okay check this bad boy out right here
wow what kind of dinosaur tooth do you
think this is parasaur lus n it's not a
parasaur Alice it's a really big
dinosaur how about a Spinosaurus yeah
it's a Spinosaurus tooth man I think
this is actually one of the spinosaurus
small teeth this isn't even a fullsize
tooth man it's thing's huge look how big
it is okay and here's the spinosaurus
certificate of authenticity that on S us
from Jurassic dreams this is really cool
isn't it yeah okay you ready for the
last surprise yeah go ahead and take it
out check this bad boy out
man giant Nerf tranquilizer Blaster yeah
so see the other day when despicable G
let out that T-Rex I realized we needed
some more tranquilizer fire power huh so
I got this bad boy for you as part of
park ranger Appreciation Week okay it's
time for me to open the stuff in my
surprise bag huh wa there's one more
thing in there you think there is yeah I
don't oh yeah you're right there is go
down dig in there and grab
it okay oh yeah it's a new vest I forgot
I got you a new vest dude all right park
ranger Aaron park ranger lb ready for
action I'm going to zip up my zip you're
going to zip your zip up okay well yeah
you know I never zip mine anymore let me
do that there we go all right let's go
find some dinosaurs dude yeah okay oh
wait get dinosaurs I got surprises here
okay okay let's see what we got in here
you wrapped it was so nice of you
dude okay why don't you WRA it good here
oh you got me
a huge Nerf tranquilizer dart gun dude
huge except now your dark gun is bigger
than my D gun dude nobody has a bigger
tranquilizer D gun than park ranger
Aaron yeah what are we going to use this
thing for huh you can use it for the for
the little bad dinosaurs like Raptors oh
okay okay and the big one for T-Rexes
yeah that's kind of what I got and
Spinosa ources hey thanks this is
awesome dude let's go open it up okay
park ranger lb let's try out our Nerf
tranquilizer blasters oh wait a minute I
don't know if we should shoot each other
with these cuz they're tranquilizer
blasters oh you now you're going to go
to sleep huh uhoh I only got one
more I only got one
more
oh it's no
good oh s down the
water I'm getting out of
here o I heard that whis by my ear see
what's in here o
cool it's some more dino puzzle eggs is
awesome dude I love doing these things
hopefully these will be different
dinosaurs than we got before okay yeah
okay cool all right I'm going to open
this one up I get to put these together
you you did it last time
ooh I wonder what kind of dinosaur this
is okay it's all finished do you know
what dinosaur it is I think it's a wait
wait wait wait let's uh let our fans
watching tell us in the comments below
what they think it is I think I have an
idea it kind of looks like a worm with
legs okay you can open that one park
ranger there we go oh wow what is this
one wow ooh I think it might be another
skeleton all right we got it all put
together do you know what dinosaur it is
is yeah okay you know what I think we
should still let our fans at home guess
this one I think it could be a pretty
easy guess though don't you ooh one
dinosaur's attacking the other oh oh oh
his arm fell
off okay Park rrob we want to thank our
paleontologist friend Juan pablor in
Spain he's with Jurassic dreams.com and
he sent us the spinosaurus fossil a real
life fossil man this is so cool for
Morocco and that Mosasaur also MOS it's
also kind of called most asaurus too
both ways on the little certificate that
he sent us so thanks Juan for sending
those so we can show our fans all about
the dinosaur fossils that he has also
speaking of fans we've got fan
man yeah okay cool let's check out this
letter from this is
from Nicolas right Nicholas and Nicholas
is in Columbus Indiana okay so Nicholas
says he really likes watching us open
our surprise eggs and our Nerf guns
thank you Nicholas all right we got
another one here see who this was from
it's kind of like that envelope of the
Oscars Tim Sarah Oliver and Lily Bachman
wrote to us as well and they said park
ranger Aaron and lb we love your
dinosaur adventures and your ghost
Chaser videos cool thanks guys this is
so awesome and they are in Pennsylvania
that is so cool thanks you guys are
awesome toilet TV fans if you'd like to
send us fan mail check out our Facebook
page and our YouTube about page our
address is right there yeah hey fans tap
the toy lab tv smiley face to subscribe
and find out about our newest videos you
can also tap the pictures to watch more
fun videos right now don't forget to
give this video a big thumbs
[Music]
up