Today I'm going to test crazy Lego
vehicles in a customuilt wind tunnel to
see which shapes are the most
aerodynamic. If you guys didn't know,
aerodynamics is the study of how gases
like air can flow around and interact
with moving objects. It's the reason why
F1 cars and airplane wings have their
own distinguished shapes. With car
companies globally spending tens of
billions every year researching the most
efficient ways to reduce drag and
increase fuel efficiency in their
vehicles, all with the exception of one,
the biggest tire manufacturer in the
world, having released thousands of car
models to date, the Lego company. So,
not only are we going to build five
custom cars with different shapes to
test their effectiveness, but we're also
going to put 10 LEGO car sets to the
test to see if LEGO puts any thought
into aerodynamics at all or if they're
just built for looks. To start, we're
going to need a way to visually see air
moving around our vehicles so we can
rate them effectively. usher in the wind
tunnel. Invented in 1871 by Frank Wenim,
the wind tunnel was an enclosed box that
allowed high pressure air to flow
through from one end to the other,
allowing researchers to finally see the
aerodynamics of their vehicles without
testing. And with the added benefit of
modern technology, we can include a fog
machine in ours so we can actually see
the air
flow. I hope that doesn't trigger the
Uh-oh. So, the first step is to lay out
a base using 16x6 plates. I'm going to
create some angled walls using these
little techni pieces. So, let's create a
bunch of these braces and put them all
the way around the
plates. Then, we'll just lay down a
bunch of Technic bricks on the bottom to
hold this together so it's not floppy.
And boom. This thing should be pretty
sturdy. Look at that. Can you see our
wind tunnel yet? This is going to be so
cool. And now we just got to add a ton
of these little blue pins to lock
together all those Technic bricks. And
we'll finish up the top part of the
frame. Ah, running out of blue pins.
There we go. Now we got to build up some
vertical pillars that come up from here
about this
high. There's just one more thing I'm
adding to the frame of this and that's
because it does that which is not ideal
when you know we need this to be
structurally sound. Simple way to fix
this is just to introduce some triangle
shapes. So, I'm adding a few of these
lift arms in here to kind of cross over
and connect. And once we do that, you
can see just how sturdy this side
already
is. Now that we've got the frame for
this thing built up, the next step is to
build a really strong fan so we can
actually push air through our wind
tunnel. And for that, we're going to use
these Lego fan blade pieces. And we just
got to arrange these in a fan shape. I'm
going to snap on two of these Technic
pieces. And if we connect a few of these
little pieces, we should be able to snap
on our
propellers. Look at that.
We're going to need to connect a few
motors together so that we'll have
enough power to actually spin this
really fast. And to make this thing spin
as fast as possible, we're going to
implement what's called a gear ratio,
which essentially means if we connect a
smaller and larger gear together like
this, and we drive the larger gear, the
small one is going to rotate a lot
faster. So, it should give us the speed
we need. So, let's connect these guys
together and attach some large gears to
them. And then we'll stick our small
gear right here through the center.
Let's see how fast this goes. Safety
first, guys.
[Music]
That's why we have eye protection. We
need to lock all of these pieces
together so they don't fly off like
that. See, I kind of interlocked it all
together. And
now that is breezy, dude. Oh gosh. Well,
that's the suction. Wow, that's actually
impressive. You can see we can put our
fan on one side and that'll blow air
through this way. So, we basically just
need to cover all these walls with
plates and we'll add some cool designs
to it later. And the nice thing is
because we've used Technic bricks on the
outside of this, we now have studs to
add our plates like
[Music]
that. Okay, so we have all the plates on
the outside of the wind tunnel. The next
thing I'm going to do is build up a road
right here with a bunch of bricks so I
can get it level with this lip
here. Boom. I didn't forget to record.
So, we essentially just need to figure
out a way to mount this in here behind
some sort of wall so you can't see it. I
think the best way to do that is just to
take our Technic connections we have on
these motors and try and build something
that goes across and attaches to these
Technic bricks in here. Connect a few of
these. Then we can put this guy right
there. This guy here. Let's see if this
works. I just got to add a little bit of
something so this stops wiggling around.
Give it a little bit more stability. But
we have our fan mounted inside the
window. Now that we got our fan all
sturdied up, we need to add the fog
mechanism that's going to go on this
side. This little portable guy here is
awesome because all you have to do is
push one button and it makes fog. Except
we want little pin points of fog so we
can actually see layers of air. So my
plan is to take a few of these pneumatic
tubes that LEGO makes and glue them into
this little end piece here so it'll
force the fog through
them. Hot, hot, hot. Fun fact about me,
guys. Did you know I've been on the
carnivore diet for over 2 months? So,
literally every day my meals consist of
steak, eggs, lots of butter, and salt.
In other news, I've had five meals and
over 4,000 calories today and still feel
hungry. Oh, tube came out. All right,
forget the whole hot glue idea. I just
discovered something completely better.
We have this little wheel. It has six
little inlets, which means we can attach
our pneumatics. And then we take this
Lego tire that's supposed to fit but
doesn't, and put it just on the end.
Stick this on the top of this. And boom.
Look, it only comes out of there.
Just need a few more tubes for the top.
That thing should be
spewing. Perfect. Now they're all going.
That is exactly what we need. So, I'm
going to build the fog machine into a
rack that we can actually slide in and
out of the wind tunnel. And then on one
side of this rack, I'm going to build up
a wall using a bunch of these long
Technic bricks. And because they have
these little holes, it's actually going
to directionalize the air flow. And we
can take each of our little tubes and
put it in a specific hole to test
different things. Now, we can plug in
all our pneumatic tubes.
All right, that's what we want. Now we
just got to mount this in here. This
part should be
[Music]
done. Now we can slide this guy in the
back here. And now we just got to
connect our little button to the outside
so we can access it. So to do that, I'm
just going to add a long axle that goes
through the wall. And that should press
the button. Perfect. So, now that we
have the fog machine installed and a way
to turn it on and off, we need to just
install one more mechanism to this
before it'll be fully functional. And
that mechanism is going to be this
little tiny food scale. My plan is to
put this on the inside underneath the
road. And since this one's actually
wireless, we'll be able to see how much
weight is being lifted off of the car by
installing this over here, and that'll
wire connect to the scale underneath the
road, which I've just simply built up
out of a few plates and technic pieces
on the bottom to make it strong. All we
got to do now is just finish the details
on the outside and build the glass
window that's going to go on the front
of
this. Look at that. So, now that we have
all the mechanics done, all we have to
do is just add some exterior details on
the outside and then some lights on the
inside to make it look really cool. We
can finally test it
out. After 10 hours of work, I finally
completed the Lego wind tunnel.
You can see on this side we have the
giant fan which we can flick on with
this switch here and that will activate
our wind tunnel. And now that we got
this built up, we can finally test some
Lego
cars. As you see, we have quite a few
cars to test. Let's start with the
Ferrari F40. It's going to take me a
while to build all these, but this is
going to be
[Music]
fun. And there we have the Ferrari F40.
This thing is absolutely beautiful. Just
some of the connections on these cars
are really, really interesting. Let's
test this out and see how aerodynamic it
really is. All we got to do is push this
button and it should start kicking out
fog. Dude, look at that. That is so
sick. Wow. Yeah. Okay. The F40 is very
aerodynamic. You can even see it kind of
going through the rear wing there, which
is really cool. So, there's a few
different forces at work here. First, we
have drag. Drag is the force that's
acting in the opposite direction of our
object moving through the air. So, to
design a vehicle to move as fast as
possible, we want to decrease the drag
by getting the air to move out of the
way or over and around our vehicle as
easily as possible. There's also lift,
which is when the pressure underneath
the vehicle exceeds that of the pressure
on top of our vehicle, causing it to
flip. In order to test lift, we're going
to actually use a leaf blower and blow
it through this side. So, we can take
out our fog machine. We just have this
guy, which has two pins. These will
actually go right into those little
holes right there. And now, as you can
see, if we push this down, we have a
reading. For the lift test, it's a pass
fail. If the scale drops under its
original number, we know we're achieving
lift, and we don't want that. And if the
number on the scale increases, we know
we've achieved what's called downforce,
which is the byproduct of the air moving
over the vehicle, pushing it down to the
ground. We're getting about 10 points of
downforce on the scale, which is great.
I'd give this one a 10 out of 10, but
let's build up the rest of the car sets
so we can test them out. Next up, we
have the McLaren Elva, the Nissan
Skyline GTR. We have the Ferrari SF24.
This is a Formula 1 car. Even have
prints on the tires.
[Music]
Next up, we have the Ford Mustang, the
Toyota Supra, a classic for car lovers
everywhere. The Kennes Jesco, the
Lamborghini V12 Vision. This one is
super sick. Like, what the It's upside
down. That's what the actual car looks
like.
The next car we have is McLaren Senna.
And this is a larger F1 car. It's still
minifigure scale, but this one is why we
built the wind tunnel so
big. Just look at it. It even has
working steering if you turn the wheel
in here. I'm excited to see how the
shapes actually perform in the wind
tunnel since it's so large. Next up, we
got the McLaren Elva. Guys, before we
test out the next one, make sure you
subscribe so you can become a member of
the Brickside Stud Army. That way, you
won't miss any of our future videos.
Test this out. Pop that
on. Dude, look at that. It's got like
those sunken doors on the sides. I feel
like that's really going to help with
the air flow around the sides of the
car. You can even see it going
underneath the car below the under tray
and through that little rear diffuser
right there. If we turn the fan off,
what happens? Does it just completely
fog up? Turn it back on.
I'd say the McLaren Ela is definitely
aerodynamic. I'd give this one an 8 out
of 10. Let's test the lift of this
[Music]
one.
Uh-oh. It went down by like at least 10
points. Unfortunately, I got to say this
one fails the lift test. Next up, we
have the Nissan Skyline. It's got a
little wing on the back here. It's also
got a little air intake in the front.
However, the Lego air intake doesn't
actually have holes, so it might just
stop the car up. We start by filling it
with fog.
And boom. Look at the air just flowing
right over the top. So you can kind of
see how it's cutting through the fog
there. What if we angled the rear wing?
What will that
do? Wow. You know, for some reason, I
want to give the Skyline a 10 out of 10
for the aerodynamic test. Let's see how
this one
[Applause]
does. Our Skyline does not pass the lift
test. I don't know. It just it really
wanted to go. Next up, we got our F1
car. I'm going to put our little ooot
crash test dummy in
here. Here we go. Push our little button
here. Like, this is working exactly how
it's supposed to. I'm going to turn it
up a little bit cuz, you know, F1 cars
are going a little bit faster than that.
You can definitely see the air going
around that rear wing and over it. So,
it's working good. And I also want to
mention the under tray on this car. It's
extremely welldesigned. So, you can see
here there's no space for that air
underneath, which is supposed to
increase the grip on the road. Looks
like we got 134 to start. Let's bump
this up slowly. Wow, that we're getting
a lot of downforce. 134, 150,
160. That's pretty good. We're getting
about 10 to 15 points of downforce. I
was expecting this one to kind of fly up
just because it's so thin, but this one
definitely passes. I'd give it a 9 out
of 10. Also, it's really beautifully
designed, so great job, LEGO. Next up,
we have the beautiful Ford Mustang. This
one I'm excited to see. It's not as
aerodynamic or like angular as the other
cars, but ooh, look at that. You can
totally see how the air is just going
right over the front of the hood and
then actually cutting underneath the
spoiler. The cool thing is if we control
our fan speed with this guy, we can
actually simulate by filling it with fog
our car accelerating. So there we are.
It stopped and now it accelerates and
that is the air moving around the car.
Oh, that is so
cool. Wow.
[Music]
We got about 179 at the highest there.
And no lift at all on this one. So, I'd
say the Ford Mustang performs really
well. I give it a 9 out of 10. Next up,
the Toyota Supra. A very popular car.
Here we go. Ooh. Yeah, look at that. You
can see it flying over the back of the
spoiler as well. So, I feel like this
one is shaped very aerodynamically. Also
want to mention, I don't see a whole lot
going underneath the vehicle and exiting
at the back. And if we pull this guy
out, you can see the under tray on this
car is super flat with this front. So,
if we put this on a flat surface, you
barely have any clearance, which
probably isn't a good thing on bumpy
roads, but it's a Lego car. Let's do the
lift test on the
[Music]
Supra. Yeah, there we
go. Go down. Toyota Supra passes. The
next car up we have is the Kennes Jes.
This thing is so cool. Yeah. I just I'm
so excited loading each one of these in
here cuz I want to see how well it's
going to
do. Hey, that's pretty aerodynamic. Ooh,
and check out that rear wing. You can
totally see the air moving back
there. It seems like at the front the
bumper is kind of trapping a bit of that
air. If we bring up the speed, I wonder
if that'll get
better. Not really. It is going over the
top, which is what we want. That is
really, really cool. We got 130. Slowly
bring this up.
35. Wa
wa. We just got about 65 points. That is
some amazing downforce. So far, this is
the best performing Lego set for
downforce. I think it's because the air
was getting caught in this little piece
right here, which is like the little air
intake on the front and it was just
pushing it down. Wow, that is really
good. That definitely passes. This is
the Lamborghini V12 Vision. It is
absolutely beautiful. I'm genuinely
curious to see how all these angles and
curves will do against wind. So, we're
going to fill the room with fog and then
we're going to simulate a acceleration.
Here we go. Turn the fan on and boom.
This is one of the most aerodynamic cars
I think we've seen. It's really hard to
see from this angle, too, but it's
actually flowing through the hood of the
car because there's some holes in it.
That's sick. Yeah, this one's just
cutting through the air like butter.
Here we go.
116 wa
140 about 130 that's about 20 points
which is really quite good really cool
car design and on top of that it's like
really aerodynamic 10 out of 10 guys I
just had an idea what if we built a wind
tunnel but for planes and we could
actually test the aerodynamics of like
jets and planes if you guys think that'd
be cool comment down below I'd have to
rebuild this and make a completely
different one but I think it'd be cool I
want to give a little bit of comparison
with this car so we have the Mercedes G
Wagon This is shaped like a brick with a
sloped hood. Will it work? It doesn't
seem to be having a problem with it,
honestly. Look what's happening at the
very rear of the vehicle. The air is
kind of gathering there, and that's
creating what's called dirty air, which
is basically where the air gets
disrupted and moves around all funky
kind of like this. It's like creating
like little wavy patterns, and
apparently that's a lot harder to drive
through. I think this one might just
blow away back into the jet. Let's see.
Wa! 225. That's like the heaviest one so
far. Here we go. 230.
Not bad. Whoa, that's over 110
[Music]
points. Oh, it's gone. I think that was
the best performing one still. Here we
have an interesting one. This is the
Batmobile. I think the Batmobile is
going to go pretty well cuz it's
designed to go fast to stop grime. Let's
start with the acceleration test. Ooh,
there we go.
Wow, this is kind of weird. I'm not
sure. This one just looks a lot
different than the others. It's like the
air is flowing around it quite a bit
differently, which is strange. I can see
that the back two wings are cutting
through the fog, which is kind of cool,
but not too
[Music]
[Applause]
impressed.
Wa! We're actually getting quite a bit
of downforce on this one. So, the
Batmobile definitely passes the lift
test. I'd give it 6 out of 10. That's
pretty cool.
Next up, we have the large Formula 1
car, McLaren Senna. This one I'm excited
for. Fill her up with our fog. And
three, two, one,
accelerate. That was so cool. Already,
I'm going to say this one is a 10 out of
10. You can really tell. It's weird.
It's like a visual that you can just
tell it's cutting through the air better
than other cars. You can see the front
wing on this one is really designed
well, cuz it is cutting through the air
quite nicely. Straight across
5.
Whoa. All right, that's
120. I find it really cool that even if
I blow it right underneath the car, it's
still designed so well that it doesn't
achieve lift. I definitely give this car
a 10 out of 10. So, it turns out LEGO
does design their cars to be somewhat
aerodynamic. They all seem to utilize
different common shapes like triangles
and wedges combined together in
different angles to make them fast and
reduce the drag on the vehicles. So, I'm
going to take those individual shapes
and see if we can turn those into cars
themselves just to see which ones will
perform the best. For this first custom
car, let's just build a triangle and add
some wheels to it. This is like the
cheese wedge of cars. Then, what if we
did like a tube shaped car? So, it's got
a big hole in the middle for all the air
to pass through, but it's shaped like a
circle and it actually can hold a
minifigure on the inside. I also want to
try building a teardrop. So, sort of
like an air foil on an airplane. It
looks like the boat from Spongebob.
We could also do one that's like just a
circle but like horizontal. So, the air
will kind of flow around the sides.
Look, it's like a little drift car. What
if we built up a rocket car? That might
be pretty
cool. All right, there we have our
rocket. Let's see how aerodynamic it is.
I'm interested to see how this one's
going to react to the
fog. Seems to be working pretty well.
Well, a lot of the air is just going
right underneath, right? But yeah,
that's definitely an aerodynamic shape
for sure. However, I don't know how fast
this is going to be because it's adding
a lot of downforce because of such a
steep angle. Started off slow. Wow, it's
already
up. About 60 70 points, that one
definitely passes the lift test. So, for
aerodynamics, I'd give this one a 10 out
of 10. Still though, you're driving
around a triangle. I don't think it's
the best car design. Here we have our
air foil car. As you can see, it's
completely symmetrical with the top and
bottom being the same. And this is based
off an aircraft's air foil, which
essentially is just a cross-section of
the wing. It's pretty big. It might just
blow away.
Accelerate. Oh, yeah. I mean, it looks
just like an air foil. It's doing what
it's supposed to be doing. I feel like
this one just wouldn't work very well as
a car, honestly. The air is definitely
flowing around it for sure, but if you
just have a little wind gust, the car
will just flip over. Let's do the lip
test, though, and see if that's actually
accurate.
Uhoh. That's not good.
That one's a fail, too. Unfortunately,
don't design your car like an air foil.
You don't want it to fly. That seems
kind of obvious. We probably didn't have
to test that. I'd give the air foil a 3
out of 10. Here we have our rocket car,
which sort of made sense as an idea, but
not for aerodynamics because there's a
rocket engine on the back. And
accelerate. Ooh, I can see it going
around the top and the bottom of the
rocket. So, I think it's working pretty
well. However, again with the symmetry,
that's not the most ideal thing if
you're going for speed. This isn't an
aircraft. You want to actually have
traction on the
ground. I give the rocket car a 5 out of
10. This here is probably my favorite
car I've designed, the tube-shaped car.
The idea with this one is the air will
just go straight through. Bound to be a
very windy ride. Speed of that air is
going to be blasting at the guy's face.
So, take a huff. Whoa, that's sick. Look
at that. It's just flowing right
through. But again, if you have just the
wrong angle of air, it could actually
lift up the top of that tube and you'd
go
flying. Oh, that's not good. Oh, no. Oh,
that's terrible.
[Music]
Yeah, it's gone. If you were in a car
driving like this and then you flipped
over, that's like a double whammy. So,
the tube car is a fail. I'm going to
call this one like the Spongebob car.
The idea for this is that the air would
just go right around the sides and kind
of bounce off, but it's also perfectly
flat, unlike a regular saucer. I like to
fill it up first and then take off cuz
it just looks sick. It looks like the
car is moving cuz the atmosphere stays
in the same place, but okay. Yeah. So,
for this one, it's definitely going
around the edges. It's also catching a
lot of it underneath. I think it's
actually coming up through the cabin.
The windscreen's also not bad. That's a
very aerodynamic windscreen. I'd give
this one probably the lowest of the
video. Three out of 10. Let's see the
lift test here.
O. Well, on that note, now we know what
shapes not to use for Lego cars. Huge
thanks for watching, guys. Check out one
of these two videos. This one is where
we crash tested Lego cars, and this one
YouTube recommends just for you. I'll
talk to you in the next one. See you.