the real reason the professor isn't in
the NBA with over 7 million subscribers
the professor's killing it on the
streets and on the screens but have you
ever wondered why he's not in the NBA
see in 2003 he was just 19 years old
when he tried out for the and one
mixtape tour and much to his surprise he
made the team then in 2006 he took his
talents to the Salem Stampede of the
international basketball league but
despite his efforts he went undrafted in
the 2007 NBA draft despite mastering a
rare aspect of the game ball handling
Scouts were skeptical of his height at
5'7 fans weren't exactly oozing at the
professor's physical attributes but
that's not even the real reason that
Grayson buet didn't make the NBA because
the NCAA has a rule you can't receive
money and play college basketball once
he signed with and one he never got a
chance to impress the NBA Scouts on the
college stage