the reason your crossover never works
and you're not Shifty like AI is because
you don't do these three things so the
first mistake that people make with
their crossover is they never get their
front foot outside of their defender's
frame so he never feels threatened in
the first place so when you lean into
this crossover it's important to get
this first step outside of his frame so
he feels threatened and actually shifts
over and then you can counter him the
second mistake that people make is when
they get their foot wide here they never
shift their torso or turn to get over
this leg in any way so the defender
doesn't feel threatened by that shift so
when I make this move it's important
that I get my foot wide and I get my
torso leaning and shift it over to this
leg with my eyes selling everything
before I come back this last part is the
key to every single Shifty player's game
when I sell this move and I Steep and
lean like I just talked about if you do
this correctly your back foot is going
to cave in and drag that signals that
you have all your weight on this front
leg which will get the defender to
commit and then you can counter back