to be honest it's not them it's you the
reason why you keep getting the ball
stolen from you and you getting locked
up the team's best defender is not
guarding it's just because your handle
is weak so here go two things to help
you strengthen your handle first you
guys actually have to be able to dribble
the basketball without dropping it a lot
of you don't know how to dribble the
ball without losing it the second thing
is having the ball actually keep up with
your body when you're moving so when you
start to move that's when you guys start
to lose the ball because now the ball
Gets behind you and your footwork is off
so you guys need to learn how to move
with the basketball going four speed