if you're shooting percentage plummet as
soon as you step back behind the three
I'm coach meech and in this video we're
going to go over and fix a few common
mistakes that are killing your range
remember Shooters are made not born and
if you stay to the end of this video I
have a special surprise for you that you
do not want to miss the first Common
mistake people have is they mess up
their preparation our preparation is the
first Domino when it comes to our
shooting process so we want to get nice
and low with our chest up chin up eyes
up so now we're in an athletic stance
and then we want to make sure our hands
are in the right spot too so we don't
want to have our hands on the side of
the bath basetball we want to have our
hand behind it with our guide hand in
the right spot so from here we want to
have our elbow in line with our body so
we're connected to the basketball with
our feet nice and wide so we have a good
stance now we're in the best position
possible to be able to move through our
shot later with in your preparation I
see a lot of mistakes when people have
their hand on top of the basketball so
their wrist isn't fully loaded and their
elbow is too far away from their body
this will cause issues later on within
your shot another issue I see is with
their arm away from their body so when
they get set up a lot of younger players
like to have the ball higher and further
away so now this will cause a pull
within your shot as well we want to get
nice and low bring that elbow back
aligning it with our body with our hand
behind the basketball now we are fully
prepared to be able to move the ball in
the best way possible so if we get set
up in that proper position so we're
preparing ourselves with a chest up chin
up eyes up with our hands in the right
spot we have now set ourselves up for
Success now we're flowing into our
second portion which is in how we move
now when we want to move the basketball
but we want to have the ball lead first
keeping our hips low so once we get to
our set point that's when we use our
legs common misconception people have
when it comes to shooting is they like
to think about everything being in one
motion it's less about one motion and
more about the order and how you move
within your shot so a lot of people mess
up because they get low and then when
they go to shoot everything raises up at
the same time your hips have a shorter
distance to travel than the ball does
from your hips to your set point also a
lot of people pull the ball away from
their body and then they have to bring
it back so we are trying to create One
Direction within our shot and move in
the proper way how we really want to
move within our shot what we want to put
our focus on is getting low in that
proper position getting prepared right
now when we move we want the ball to
lead once we get to our set point now we
have stacked our power points on top of
each other this is where we are strong
at with our arms we're powerful here but
we also are powerful with our legs in
this position so we want to make sure we
stack both these on top of each other so
when we go up all the energy goes into
the basketball at the same time remember
this basketball has no power on its own
so it's all up to us on how we create
energy with the ball a common
misconception people have with this
thought process about shooting is they
think you have to get to your set point
and stay here and pause for a second or
two and then jump at the same time
that's not true it's about passing
through this point but letting the ball
move and lead to this point first so as
your low when the ball gets gets here
now it gets to about a set point as it's
still traveling that's when you start to
jump up and then extend into your shots
so you're not pausing down at the bottom
which some of you might need as a
beginner to introduce this but as you
advance on you no longer pause and you
just flow through that shot so our next
topic is in how we finish so if we've
prepared properly we've moved through
our shot in the best way now we need to
finish our shot so as we go to flick our
wrist we're want to finish with our
elbow above our eyebrow a lot of people
have issues with finishing the shot in
the correct place because they started
moving wrong in the first place so like
we said we want to start here move the
ball first pushing it up and then
getting to our set point a lot of people
like to start with the ball out and then
pull the ball in when you do that that
creates more of an opportunity for you
to just push the ball out at a flatter
angle we want to start low with our body
in the right spot push up to get here
now once we get our wrist underneath we
can finish our shot by pushing through
the middle flicking through our wrist
and finishing High remember the ball
needs to do three things to go in the
ball needs to go up out and straight so
if we can follow through at the correct
angle that will ensure that the ball
does all three of those things so if we
can get our elbow to our eyebrow that
makes the ball go out but it also makes
sure it gets enough Arc to go Above the
Rim and then we just want to push
through the middle to make sure it goes
straight the last thing we're going to
dive into is how to properly practice on
how to increase your range a lot of
people do this wrong they like to come
into the gym and just jump to where they
want to start shooting from so super far
behind the three you want to first start
out in the mid-range establishing a base
and connecting with all of your proper
principles so you want to make sure
you're in the proper spots with your
chest up chin up eyes up and you're
moving the ball in the correct way so
you're establishing the right things to
do before you jump out to where you want
to be able to shoot from so you guys
made it to the end of this video now I'm
going to hook you up with a free workout
all you have to do is go to the pin
comment below fill out the form and the
shooting range injection is yours those
are some of the most common shooting
mistakes that kill your shooting range
if you still struggle with shooting
inside the paint or maybe your for for
just so a little off just click this
video that I made on how to shoot the
perfect jump shot